Chapter 189

Zhang Dong gritted his teeth while looking at his injured leg. His body refining technique was primed towards defense more than regeneration so it wasn't healing that fast. He was lucky enough in the sense that this attack didn't go through fully and he managed to keep it.

'Damn... those demonic energies are eating away at my leg'

He could feel and see some black Qi entering his body, thankfully his spiritual energy that had a second holy attribute was managing to fight against this invading force. The combination of powerful defense and healing capabilities from his upgraded cultivation method was proving to have been the right choice.

He used the time gained from the confusion to push his holy Qi into this thigh to stop the bleeding. He worked fast while activating his spatial ring. A transparent thread flew out and quickly pierced the flesh of his thigh muscle that got severed. He used this suture that was made from special spider silk to sew up his wound. The cut was quite deep and the demonic energies made it hard for him to just heal up without any help from external items.

"Blasted, he is recovering, don't let him!"

Yang Guanyu shouted while pointing his thin finger at Zhang Dong's direction but before he could fire off his demonic spell he felt a large amount of spiritual energy coming his way. He protected himself with a similar bloody moon defensive spell against the beam of golden light. This beam was the breath attack of Zhang Dong's soul-beast that was now able to aid its master, the other soul-beasts were now clashing with the two belonging to Feng Liena and Huo Qiang.

The dragon roared while placing itself between Zhang Dong and Yang Guanyu. It looked banged up, one of its eyes was missing, its webbed wings were pierced in a couple of places and one of the horns was broken. It had done its best and lasted to this point but it was also quite tired. Zhang Dong wasn't fairing much better as he had burned through a lot of Qi while he was trying to free himself, he also had already taken a lot of hits.

"You think this changes anything, Grand Elders attack!"

The Dark Palm sect leader proclaimed while shouting out, the problem here was that two of his elders were suffering backlashes from their soul-beasts getting mangled up by the other two that appeared. He forgot that they have been tangling with this white-haired cultivator for so long and were tired from holding him in place with the trap formation. For some reason the enemy was still standing, normal cultivators would have run out of Qi by this point. This was all thanks to the grade his cultivation method was, thanks to which he had multiple times more juice to run on than other people did.

The Plasma Ifrit and Ascended Storm Phoenix were proving to be more than a match for the Dark Palm sect grand elders. Two of them were vomiting copious amounts of blood while their respective beasts were getting mauled. The ones remaining were the large spiky turtle that belonged to the strongest grand elder present, grand elder Wan. The other was the Ox with the fiery mane that was used by the cultivator that was using the large hammer.

"I'll leave those four to you, keep them occupied while I take care of this bastard over there!"

Zhang Dong called out to Feng Liena and Huo Qiang that already in speaking distance. The two had managed to push into the nascent soul level not too long ago but needed some time to get used to it. The two did it at almost the same time and rushed out of the medallion treasure just in time to destroy a large armada of ships that were trying to cut a hole into the large protective formation of the newly created sect.

"Yes Senior brother, leave these old farts to me, I was itching to test out my new abilities!"

Huo Qiang was glowing red and his already muscular body looked as if it reached a new high. He charged forward the closest opponent that in this situation was elder Wan throwing a fist forward. His opponent felt a massive spike of energy in the surrounding area along with scorching heat that almost caused his beard to catch on fire.

After finishing up with the crane looking soul beast Feng Liena appeared next to Zhang Dong while causing a massive cyclone to appear around them. The battlefield got even more hectic with the appearance of these two young nascent soul masters. They were still green behind the ears but thanks to their cultivation manuals being at the immortal grade they were a notch above these four old farts.

"Let me aid you Senior Brother Dong, here use this to recover some strength."

Feng Liena threw over some recovery pills that Zhang Dong chomped on. The pills were meant for core formation cultivators, but Matt was happy for the gesture. He nodded at the beauty that looked even more enchanting now than before and then charged at his enemy. His cut leg was still hurting after the quick patch job but it would have to do, the enemies wouldn't let him recover any more than this.

Feng Liena nodded while looking at Zhang Dong. He looked beat up, his pure white robe was soaked in blood, his hair was messed up and he looked a lot paler than usual. She pressed her lips together tightly and then turned around, she looked at two of the grand elders. One was the female cultivator while the other one was the larger elder with the great hammer.

She showed the two an icy stare the two battle fans that were gifted to her by Zhang Dong already clenched tightly. She moved one forward while producing a mini cyclone that flew forward at the old lady. She then moved her other fan that produced a similar cyclone that attacked the larger man. The two wind twisters charged forward expanding in size, besides sharp blades of wind you could spot small lightning bolts inside of them.

"You dare harm my Senior Brother! This offense must be paid in blood!"

She strode forward, her soul-beast was already fighting its own battle in the back. The two grand elders got swept away by the powerful winds, unable to evade them.

"Is this all you got? Are Dark Palm grand elders this weak?"

Elder Wan retreated, he looked down at his palm that was sizzling and smoking after he received the attack of this red-haired cultivator. The man was old and had lived through many battles but had never faced anyone with such pure fire energies. This was true as this wasn't any simple fire Qi that Huo Qiang was using, he was using plasma that could burn hot as a star.

Elder Wan wasn't alone, the fourth grand elder that suffered a backlash a moment ago was aiding him in battle. The two were somehow able to contend with the burning cultivator as he seamed inexperienced. This was the only reason that they were alive as he outperformed them in any other aspect, be it speed or power of his attacks.

"You had your fun fighting five against one, I hope you can at least give me somewhat of a challenge, I'd like to test these new techniques of mine!"

Huo Qiang laughed while charging forward. His eyes were glowing red and his breath was pushing out condensed fire Qi that scorched anything that got in its path. The tables were slowly turning, with the added help of his two friends Matt was now able to face their leader on his own and he wouldn't let this chance be squandered.

Zhang Dong gritted his teeth while slamming back into Yang Guanyu to engage him into a close-range battle. The man looked paler than before, the previous attack had drained him of some spiritual energy but he was still able to defend himself. Matt was the one that was looking far worse now, each time the two clashed he could feel his leg throbbing. The quick suture patchwork that he had performed was somehow holding but due to the clashing energies, his leg wasn't healing fast enough.

Even though he was in pain, he didn't shy away from using that injured leg. Far too many people had already died in this battle and he was frantic to end it as fast as possible. The exchange was similar to the previous one, the two clashed but this time around Zhang Dong had his golden dragon to back him up. Yang Guanyu found himself on the defensive, his own soul-beast was still behind his back just blocking the combined attacks of the Zhang Patriarch and his large dragon beast.

In the distance among the destroyed city, the other cultivators looked on. The Dark Palm sect members that were in the remaining flying ships were now in disarray. No one could have predicted this outcome. They were already fighting against this puny clan and its weak allies for hours and their elders weren't able to even kill off anyone. Even worse, two other powerful cultivators that were able to contend with their grand elders appeared, the whole situation looked grim.

"Commander, what should we do? Should we aid the elders and retreat for now?"

One of the core formation cultivators from the Dark Palm sect asked. The man he was talking to was the impromptu leader after the general died. The general was in the largest flagship that was now a pile of debris on the ground after those two nascent soul monsters appeared.

"We... we need to alert the council of the ancestors! This is a dire situation, if this continues all of the grand elders might die today!"

The person that was asking the commander about the next line of action nodded. He directed the orders to the communication expert that started calling for help from the main sect. They wanted to ask for help from the old monsters that were living under the main sect, if all of them acted these three young nascent soul cultivators wouldn't stand a chance.

"Some of the ancestor elders are on the same level as the sect leader, if they act our victory is assured!"

Everyone nodded and awaited a positive reply from the sect, the stakes were just too high. The communications officer came looked at the communication device with a solemn expression though, something was off.

"What's wrong, report!"

"C-commander... I can't reach the main sect... something must have gone wrong... no one is responding..."

"What! Impossible! We must reach the main sect, the communication devices are probably damaged or these blasted Zhang bastards are doing something! Quickly examine it and get rid of the problem!"

The man shouted with large veins popping up on his forehead and his eyes bulging. The Dark Palm communications officer nodded and quickly got to work, he needed to get to the bottom of this, otherwise, he could kiss his life goodbye.

While the battle was raging, in the distance a couple of robed figures were standing. They nodded at each other while concealing their presence. They were clearly looking at the battle that was taking place in the distance while waiting for something. After a couple of moments, one of the cultivators approached the person that was standing in the front along with some others.

The person was handed a communication jade and started going through the report that was handed down. The person nodded and handed the communication device back to the person that gave it to him. He slipped his hood down while revealing his face, this face was full of scars.

"Fan Ping, how is it?"

"You don't need to worry Senior Brother, everything is going according to plan. I propose we wait some more, maybe that man can take out Yang Guanyu for us."

"Yes, I agree."

The people nodded at each other while slowly getting ready. Everyone here knew that this battle was slowly approaching its apex and that they would be reaping the rewards in the end.

Chapter 190

Unbeknownst to what was happening in the background, the battle continued. This time it was in the favor of the Triforce alliance and the newly established United Element's sect. There was even the first casualty from the nascent soul monsters, the man that had lost his snake-like beast was looking down at his chest, or to be exactly what was left off it.

The hole exposed the leftover from his lungs and part of his heart. Even though this wound was massive it wasn't bleeding all that much as the flesh around it had melted. This was due to the attack that caused this having quite a high temperature. The Dark Palm elder could feel his vision getting hazy, the last thing he was seeing was a large muscular man with red hair smirking at him.

"Heh, was that all?"

Huo Qiang laughed while cracking the bones on his fist that went through his opponent's chest. The other grand elder that he was fighting with was somewhat to the side and looking distraught. His eyes were bulging and his forehead was sweating due to the sight he was seeing.

"Im...imposible!"

The man with the massive wound in his body started spasming and twitching. Huo Qiang quickly injected his plasma Qi into his opponent's body and was now ready to see the fireworks.

"Haha, explode!"

Almost on cue the man's body gave out one last quiver and exploded into many smaller chunks. His nascent divinity was already damaged due to his soul-beast early departure. The cultivators watched as it crumbled soon afterward and evaporated into tiny soul molecules. The man was dead and now it was four against three.

"Nothing is impossible for this Lord Qiang! Now it's your turn!"

Qiang shouted out, he was aching for a good fight and now after having slain the injured opponent he could finally let loose in a proper one on one. His Ifrit roared out along with its master and started forcing his opponent back, which was a spiky snapping turtle. The fire beast's claws dug into the hard shell and started to slowly melt the hard exterior thanks to the massive heat.

A bit away from this battle there were two other nascent soul cultivators. They were back to back and they were holding their hands in a strange fashion while glowing. They were inside the eye of a tornado, every second or so a green lightning bolt would randomly shoot out from within the thick winds. The two would frantically protect themselves from both sides, never knowing where the next attack would come from.

"Who is this, I've never heard about anyone being able to produce such a lightning storm... and what is that soul-beast!"

The female grand elder shouted out while protecting herself from a stray lightning strike that went for her head. The more they stayed inside the eye of the storm the more lightning strikes came.

"I don't know junior sister, but we must escape from here, this is a death trap!"

The other person was the man that had bothered Zhang Dong with the large hammer. He was now holding performing some hand seals along with his sect sister as they combined their strength to defend against this onslaught.

"You wish to leave? There is no escape!"

The moment the two tried to move the thickness of the winds increased. The sharp green wind blades were keeping them from diving into the twister and the lightning bolts were slowly whittling away their defenses.

Feng Liena was hovering above in the clouds in a lotus position. Tiny wind spirits were dancing around her as she was concentrating. The wind cyclone was slowly closing itself around the people trapped inside, the longer she kept them inside the easier it would be to finish them off with her final attack. Though in reality, she was prolonging the whole situation quite mad at the opposing cultivators that brought death and destruction here. Though she was mostly angry at the fact that they dared to attack her senior brother.

'You think you can have an easy death? Think again!'

She narrowed her eyes and pushed more of her Qi into her attack, she was intending to shred the two opposing cultivators with her blender like attack. She was still best at ranged attacks and with her increased cultivation things like this weren't a problem now.

Yang Guanyu wasn't looking all that well either. Since the battle started a couple of hours had already passed, he was burning through his reserves and there were no fresh bodies to absorb his dastardly Qi from. He was getting continuously pushed back by this bright glowing opponent that even managed to somehow heal and recover from one of his strongest attacking techniques. He was slowly realizing that this might not have been the brightest plan.

The skinny man looked to the sides as he tried to look to his sect members for aid. When he turned he noticed that one of them was already dead and the other was getting pummeled by one of the new arrivals. He could sense the remaining pair trapped in some kind green Qi cyclone and unable to escape. He was truly alone and would have to get himself out of this situation by himself.

'Damn useless cretins! This battle is lost, I must flee... the council of ancestors will protect me!'

His eyes started moving left and right as he looked for a way to escape. He still didn't use his trump card, unwilling to put himself in danger after the backlash. He was more or less certain that his remaining sect members wouldn't last for long so he needed to act fast.

"Don't think that this is over!

Guanyu ripped out one of his pinkies and threw it at Zhang Dong. He in response encased himself in a golden barrier while realizing what kind of attack was coming his way. The small digit exploded into a strange cloud of dark green corrosive gas that encased Zhang Dong's body that was now protected by his barrier bubble. The Dark Palm sect leader then flew back while taking out a talisman from his spatial ring.

He quickly threw it forward and activated it. The talisman glowed in a blue light and transformed into a small teleportation portal that was big enough for one person to pass through.

"The next time we meet, I will crush you and everyone that you know! Remember this you whelp!"

Yang Guanyu snorted and dived towards the opened portal, escape the only thing on his mind.

"God damn, is he going to just run like that?"

Matt was surprised by the sudden turn of events. His opponent just turned around and started escaping, he thought that he would remain here till one of them was dead but the old fart had other plans apparently. He was an old monster that knew when to give up, he was just that type of person and this was what kept him alive for this long.

Matt looked on while grimacing, he was covered by the corrosive fog and couldn't fire off an attack against his opponent without dropping the barrier, it looked like the old cultivator would escape. The Dark Palm grand elders realized that their leader was abandoning them but they couldn't follow suit as they were being held back by the two nascent soul cultivators.

Yang Guanyu was moments away from escaping, his hand was already close to touching the portal. Before he could pass through though, a flash of energy blocked his way. The old man pulled his hand that was ready to access the portal back but not before his fingertips got incinerated by the invading energy. The reddish bolts of Qi were aiming at the portal and the moment they connected with it, the portal sizzled out of existence.

"Who dares!"

Guanyu backed away with fear, he could already tell that the attack didn't come from any of the three cultivators that his group was fighting against. No, the attack came from much further away and the people that were responsible were already rushing over here.

"Why shouldn't we dare?"

A group of people appeared out of nowhere. Some of them were hiding high up in the sky, some were hidden behind the trees or rocks in the distance. More and more of those cultivators started flying over and they were all at the nascent soul realm.

Matt managed to get out of the poisonous fog and looked around. He had also noticed the sudden arrival of the new cultivators, their allegiance was something that he was worried about. They were just popping out of everywhere and slowly surrounding the area that he and the Dark Palm sect elders were fighting.

"Qiang, Liena!"

Zhang Dong called out while retreating towards his allies, those two had also noticed that there were unwanted nascent soul cultivators coming towards them from all directions.

"Let us retreat towards the city."

He called out while the two nodded, their fights were interrupted. Elder Wan had a bloodied nose and a burned palm print on his back. His other two allies that were previously fighting finally managed to get out of the lightning twister after Feng Liena retreated with their two sect brothers.

The two enemy parties didn't get far as before they could regroup they heard a booming voice and at least twenty nascent soul cultivators surrounded them. Their energies encompassed the area and made it difficult for the already tired and injured fighters to escape.

"Halt, you shan't go any further!"

One of the people called out while flying forward, he was wearing a golden robe with a gate pattern that showed it opening, two serpentine dragons were above the gate. After this man appeared another joined him, this one was wearing a different kind of robe that was red and had various flower patterns sewn into it. Finally, a third man appeared that was holding onto an exquisite looking sword. His robe was pure white and reminiscent of what Zhang Dong liked to wear, on the back it had two Chinese symbols for 'limitless' and 'sword' put in.

"Dragon Gate Sect?... the Demon Subduing Sect? and the Limitless Sword Society!?"

Yang Guanyu shouted out distraught, his eyes going red and his whole body shaking while his allies slowly moved over to his side. Even though this sect leader had abandoned them just a moment ago, the other elders knew that they stood a better chance if they fought with him.

"Yes, you have seen better days... Dark Palm Sect Patriarch..."

One of the men called out, it was the man in the golden robe. He was a handsome looking older gentleman with a sharp gaze and quite the chiseled chin.

"Why have you come here Xu Qing... and you brought those two over..."

Matt and the others were floating closer to Spirit Spring City now but they couldn't go any further as the twenty so nascent soul cultivators had surrounded them from all sides and they were looking at five of them now.

"Yes, you do remember brother Cheng Yang from the esteemed Demon Subduing Sect and let us not forget about Lord Zhan Jie from the Limitless Sword Society."

The two men just nodded while staring at the beaten up Darp Palm sect leader. The three people that had moved forward were all in the late stage of the nascent soul realm, equal in power to him.

"How is this possible, you never crossed the border how did you get here so fast!"

Yang Guanyu shouted while spitting out, both his arms closed into a fist and the one without the finger was bleeding black blood profusely.

The three sect elders looked at each other and smirked, one of them motioned with his chin to the side to one of the people there. This person flew forward and when he was seen by the Dark Palm members they clearly recognized him.

"We had a bit of help from one of your elders, you didn't think that you are the only ones with spies?"

Zhang Dong and his allies looked at the happenings from the side, apparently one of the border guards from the Dark Palm sect had changed sides and this was how they managed to slip in unnoticed.

'This doesn't look good... I'm not sure if those guys will let us be after they clear up those four...'

Matt gulped while moving his spiritual sense into his spatial ring. He had prepared one last surprise, his last-ditch effort he would probably need to use it soon as he didn't think that these cultivators would just let three new nascent soul elders just establish a new sect without a fight.

Chapter 191

"Damn, traitor! As long as the ancestral council exists, the foundation of the sect remains!"

"Even if you kill me this doesn't change anything!"

Yang Guanyu shouted at the man that appeared to be the traitor from his sect. Zhang Dong and his allies were to the side, they were being watched by the nascent soul realm cultivators from three various sects. While this was happening Matt was concentrating most of his attention on healing his leg. The wound was still hurting like crazy but the holy energies were slowly removing the demonic Qi while healing.

"The ancestral council? Hehe, you should probably worry more about yourself."

The man in the golden robe replied while smirking, Yang Guanyu furrowed his brows.

"What do you mean? What did you do!"

"Do you think that you are the only sect with hidden senior elders? Use your head, why do you think that we are all here?"

The conversation in the distance continued while Zhang Dong and his comrades waited in the back.

"What do you think their intentions are, Senior Brother Dong?"

Feng Liena asked while glancing at some of the old men and women floating around.

"We can be certain that they are here to get rid of the Dark Palm sect..."

This group of cultivators must have been waiting for them for a while. They only reacted when Yang Guanyu was making a run for it. From Matt's point of view, they were probably waiting for both parties to weaken or kill themselves before pouncing on the survivor. The sudden escape attempt of the Dark Palm sect leader made them do it prematurely as only one person had died.

"Yes, they were waiting for us to tire."

Feng Liena agreed.

"Hey, stop prattling!"

One of the nascent soul cultivators shouted at the trio, he was wearing a similar robe to the first person that spoke out with the dragon gate on it.

"Or what?"

Huo Qiang answered and pushed his killing intent along with this nascent soul aura in the direction of the person. The man backed off after feeling the large man's superior aura but soon his friends moved in to back him up.

"What do you think you are doing!"

The group of five had increased to six and they started glaring at Zhang Dong and his allies, they weren't attacking just yet though. They had seen the fight from start to finish and were wary of the man that was able to contend with Yang Guanyu. Most of the nascent realm cultivators here were in the early stage and the three main ones that were now holding a conversion with the Dark Palm sect members were all in the late stage.

"That's enough Qiang."

Zhang Dong stepped in as he placed himself between his group and the new arrivals.

"Everything depends on you... what are your intentions here? If you are after the Dark Palm sect then we won't stop you, but we would like to know your intentions towards us."

Zhang dong asked while trying to get some more information, would these guys turn hostile the moment they took care of those weakened Dark Palm members. He had already burned through most of his Qi reserves, he was holding out for the last blow against Yang Guanyu but he was unable to finish the job.

"You don't need to know, the three seniors will decide, just stay still and wait!"

Another man from that group spoke out, he was wearing one of the whiter robes and belonged to the sword sect. Matt frowned as these people weren't willing to give them answers.

'Should we wait or make a run for it? Will those people let us go just like that?'

There were a couple of ways that things could go here. In most of them, his side wouldn't be getting out unscathed. From his point of view, the powerful group of cultivators would either try to dispose of them or demand some payment. He didn't think that they would just let three powerful nascent soul realm cultivators just roam the land under their noses.

'They might even try to force some of those soul contracts on us...'

He glanced back into his storage ring and then to Spirit Spring City. The Zhang Clan headquarters were still standing and the large defensive formation was working fine.

'Think I'll have to use that to get out of here... but first I want to see what they will do to that skinny old fart...'

Zhang Dong had to place his hand on Huo Qiang's shoulder to pull him back. His red-haired friend just wanted to charge forward but he knew that fighting this sect alliance here and now wouldn't be the smartest thing to do.

"Sister Liena, Brother Qiang let us wait for now... we should see how it all plays out first..."

The two others looked at him and nodded, the group of cultivators that were around them backed away slightly but they were still glaring at them while on their guard. It wouldn't take long for the matter to be resolved as everyone felt a rise in demonic energy followed by shouting.

"YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST KILL ME, ME!?"

Apparently the talks have broken down and they were ready to fight. The Dark Palm sect elders found out that while they were talking their base was getting assaulted by similar ancestral elders from the present three sects. They were all dead set on destroying this demonic sect and taking their riches for themselves. This was all thanks to Zhang Dong that managed to divert their attention to himself.

While the Dark Palm sect was distracted, the three other sects slowly moved their masters through the borders unnoticed and waited for the battle to start. They didn't believe that Zhang Dong's side would be actually able to last for so long but they were happily surprised and could now come in and just take the rewards for themselves.

Yang Guanyu wouldn't just sit back and let himself be killed though. The old man started glowing purple, the glow was mostly concentrated on the gem in his forehead that was spitting out more and more ghastly apparitions.

"THIS CHANGES NOTHING, YOU WILL ALL DIE HERE!"

His body started changing, it expanded in size and became immaterial. The change was similar to how his disciple transformed during the Dao Festival. His monstrous appearance was much bigger and the dastardly Qi radiating off him was far grander though.

"Ha, do you think that we didn't come prepared you fool?"

The three commanding cultivators gathered together and surrounded the demonic cultivator. One of them took out a necklace that was made out of white beads. He threw it directly at the monster of a man, the moment the beads collided with the blackish purple energies they started absorbing them.

"What!?.. are those devil sealing beads? Where did you get those!"

The bead necklace broke apart after it absorbed more and more of that demonic Qi. The round orbs that were pure white started to dim and take up a dark purplish color the more of Yang Guanyu's energy they absorbed. The man that looked more like a lanky monster with blades for fingers started shrinking back as quite a chunk of his energy got absorbed by the items.

The three leaders that were up against this demonic cultivator used this chance to attack. Each one quickly performed one of their strongest attacks.

Cheng Yang performed a lengthy chant before pushing his palm forward, a large golden hand appeared that descended on his enemy. Xu Qing roared out and punched out, a large illusionary gate appeared behind him. It opened up and you could hear a dragon's shout escaping from it followed by a surge of flames that flew at the Dark Palm Sect leader. Zhan Jie brandished his blade and with one swift move cut forward, his sword energies carrying his Dao were at a collision course with his opponent.

The attacks came from three sides and they had killing intent behind them. In his weakened state and after his trump card had failed Yang Guanyu looked around not sure what to do, his eyes moved separately from each other as he searched for a way out.

The three nascent soul elder's attacks finally collided with each other, exploding and causing everything in the area to shake. It looked like a nuclear explosion took place as a giant mushroom cloud expanded to the sides bringing around dust and destruction.

"Is he dead?"

The other members of this ambush party kept the explosion contained in the area with their spiritual energy. They looked with attentiveness at the spot that the techniques collided with themselves, hoping to see a dead Dark Palm Sect leader. What they saw though, was a slightly different scenario.

The monster of a man looked hurt but he wasn't dead. He was holding three bodies pierced by his claw-like fingers, even now they could see those bodies squirming and getting drained from their vital energies. These were the three remaining grand elders from the Dark Palm sect. Their glorious sect leader had used the confusion to pierce them in the backs in hopes of absorbing their energies to recover and it had apparently worked.

"YOU CAN'T KILL ME!"

The ambush party didn't have enough time to react as the man bolted forward in one direction, he was going for some cultivators and trying to absorb them as well. The boost in energy was apparent as his strength had apparently recovered. Zhang Dong and his allies were to the side watching, he in particular squinted with his eyes as the lanky monster was heading their way.

'It looks like he had recovered... but his body is deteriorating... that technique is probably incomplete or he absorbed energies past his limit... he probably won't last for long.'

The group of nascent soul elders from the other sects started backing away at the sight of the monster coming their way. Huo Qiang, Feng Liena, and Zhang Dong, on the other hand, looked at each other. The three just nodded at each other and started concentrating, their Soul-beasts appearing behind them while roaring.

"IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT, DIEDIEDIEDIE"

Yang Guanyu sounded more like a crazed person now, his eyes had gone fully black and he was drooling from his mouth. He focused on Zhang Dong that holding two fingers out towards his incoming enemy, the tips were already glowing with golden light while arcs of electricity crackled to the sides.

In a similar fashion as the three nascent soul elders before, Qiang, Liena, and Dong fired of their respective techniques. The three energies, red, green, and gold intertwined with each other to form an even larger attack. The giant torrent of spiritual energies looked like a massive pillar. The elemental energies collided with the incoming monster and bathed it in spiritual Qi of the three nascent soul masters.

The screams of Yang Guanyu that had transformed into a beast were heard by the twenty so nascent soul cultivators in the area. They looked with astonishment at the giant torrent of energy that washed the demonic cultivator away. He dissolved into particles and not even his nascent divinity was able to survive after this massive attack. The large column of flew upwards and into the sky, it parted the clouds and escaped into the atmosphere exploding in the distance.

The Dark Palm sect leader was no more, his grand elders slain by his own hand. There was a moment of silence, the remaining people that were in the area looked up into the sky. The energies that had detonated in the sky looked like a blooming flower which then shattered into many tiny whisps of light that scattered.

The battle was finally over, the people in the Zhang headquarters wanted to cheer for the victory but instead, their faces were solemn. This fight had ended but another one looked to be upon them. Their three new sect elders were now hovering above the mostly destroyed city, twenty or so nascent soul masters looking at them with various expressions.

Chapter 192

'This doesn't look good...'

'I used up a lot of spiritual energy in that last attack, I don't think I can fight those three late-stage cultivators even with the help of Liena and Qiang.'

Matt looked at his surroundings. He was hovering close to the Zhang Clan headquarters, underneath him was a desolate wrecked city that used to house ten million people in it. It was now deserted and most buildings were destroyed during the assault by the Dark Palm sect.

'I guess I should try talking with them first... maybe not everyone is so unreasonable like those Dark Palm guys.'

Zhang Dong straightened out and placed his hands behind his back. He hovered forward while Feng Liena and Huo Qiang supported him from the back while flying half a step behind him.

"Greetings honorable Daoists, we are thankful that you have aided us in this time of need."

He bowed slightly in a show of respect while the twenty so nascent realm cultivators approached. The previous group of six flew to the back after they saw what these three young cultivators were capable of, they were now on their guard. Zhang Dong continued talking as the group wasn't answering him quite yet.

"As you can see we are a new sect, I'm sure we can work something out..."

Matt was even willing to pay tribute to the three sects if that got them out of this situation. Finally, the three main elders showed a reaction as they gathered in front.

"Work something out? You have a strange way of speaking friend..."

Xu Qing from the Dragon Gate sect spoke out first as before while glancing at the three people before him. They all felt that he was scanning them with this spiritual sense and they were quick to block him out. This also let the man know that these people were close to his strength.

Cheng Yang and Zhan Jie were also feeling them out. It looked like they would attack them if they showed weakness and backed off. The atmosphere got stuffy and the other cultivators waited for the decision of their leaders.

"This is quite the conundrum my fellow Daoists, these circumstances are unique..."

Cheng Yang said while placing his hands behind his back in a similar fashion as Zhang Dong. Zhan Jie didn't reply but he had his hand close to his sword, his intention was obvious to everyone gathered there.

Matt gave out a sigh and then asked.

"Right... what are your terms..."

Xu Qing smiled at the question as it looked like the situation could be resolved without bloodshed.

"I'm sure my friends from the Demon Subduing Sect and Limitless Sword Society will agree on the usual."

"You will sign a soul binding contract with our sects. You can keep most of your belongings besides anything at the heaven grade that will be shared among the sects. Who goes to which sect will be discussed later."

'Figures, they won't let an upstart sect be created. They want to absorb us into their sect and take everything for themselves... if they see that we have immortal grade techniques there could be a problem...'

Matt didn't know how these people would react if he tossed out one of his immortal grade cultivation manuals. Would they start infighting, or would they torture him to get his secrets?

'Sign my life over to them or go with plan B instead...'

He looked to Feng Liena and Huo Qiang. The red-haired man was clenching his fist tightly, Matt didn't need much intelligence to figure out that the man was holding himself back from attacking the cultivators in front. Feng Liena just held one of her fans in front of her face before giving Zhang Dong a small nod. Both of them were willing to go at it with this group of old farts if he decided on it.

'They trust me too much on making the right decision...'

He wanted to give the two a hug for trusting in him so much but also wanted to ask where that unshaken confidence towards him was coming from.

He straightened out, his eyes narrowed slightly as he looked at Xu Qing from the Dragon Gate sect. His eyes started glowing and some lightning escaped from them for more of a dramatic effect. The older gentlemen flinched and backed away at the display of power as he noticed that this white-haired cultivator was reacting in an unfathomable way.

"Sign a soul binding contract? ... I don't think we will be doing that, we can offer you some spirit stones and secret techniques but that's as far as we are willing to go!"

He replied, his voice getting deeper and deeper the longer he talked as it got backed by his cultivation. While talking he made sure to grip a certain item in his hand, he had taken out this device that he had created in preparation for something like this. It was finally time to unleash its power and bullshit his way through this dire situation.

"You dare go against the three great sects?"

One of the nascent realm elders in the back shouted out clearly surprised by the outburst from this white-haired man. Xu Qing moved his hand up so that the man behind him would quiet down before asking.

"My friend, do you think you can go against our sects, we are giving you a lot of face already, don't be unreasonable."

The Dragon Gate sect leader didn't think that Zhang Dong would be able to come out on top. He saw him fight Yang Guanyu and thought that the man was at his strength level. That was at the beginning of the battle though, he was sure that at this point he or the other sect leaders wouldn't have a problem in winning in a one on one battle.

The only way that those three could come out on top, would be if they were hiding something. It didn't seem like they had any trump cards anymore though, from his perspective they would have used them by now as Zhang Dong had almost died during that trap formation. The two allies that came to aid him should have been the ace in the hole.

"Xu Qing, if they want to lose their life it's their decision."

Zhan Jie from the Limitless Sword Society proclaimed while moving his hand to his sword to unsheath it. He wasn't a man that liked to debate for long, he liked to have his sword do the talking. Cheng Yang gave out a sigh but he also prepared to do battle, he floated next to Zhan Jie and was also ready.

"If more blood needs to be shed, then so be it!"

"You think this will be easy?"

Huo Qiang snorted while unleashing the full extent of his cultivation. His whole body began burning up and he looked like a person made from pure fire. Feng Liena wasn't far behind as she also started releasing copious amounts of her spiritual Qi into the surroundings. The nascent soul elders that ware at the early stage gulped hard, they could tell that this man and woman were also quite strong, at least in the middle stage maybe even on the cusp of the late stage.

The three sect leaders jumped back, the air around the area got filled with copious amounts of Qi and even the defensive formation in the background churned to block it from entering the Zhang headquarters.

"C-can the seniors win?"

"T-there are so many nascent soul realm cultivators there..."

The people that were hiding behind the barrier focused on their allies, this looked to be the final challenge between doom and survival. Before the battle could start though, something peculiar started happening. Zhang Dong's whole body started glowing, it wasn't the golden glow, as usual, it was more of a colorless glow.

His body slumped forward as if he was a puppet with strings getting cut. His hands and legs dangled about while he flew upwards. The cultivators from the other sects looked on with quite the interest at what was happening.

"What is he doing?"

"That Qi... it's massive... its that the great circle? How is that possible, he shouldn't have any Qi left!"

The other nascent soul seniors took up defensive stances, everyone was ready to defend against anything that this unknown cultivator was going to throw at them. His power kept rising, everyone's eyes started going wide as Zhang Dong was reaching the apex of what a nascent soul realm cultivator could be.

"Was he hiding his strength... no... what is that?"

Cheng Yang pointed up into the sky, behind the shining Zhang Dong there was someone and it was he that was radiating this power. The man looked like a ghost, he was semi-transparent and looked quite familiar to some of the people gathered there. Mostly to the ones from the Zhang Clan police unit that had visited Moonlight city before.

"Wait isn't that that that mysterious senior..."

"Yes... what is he doing here...could he be here for..."

The glaring glow of the light started subsiding, what was left was a floating Zhang Dong with his head down low and with his body unmoving. He was radiating light and behind him stood a phantom of another person. This person looked like an old man, his beard white and lengthy. He was wearing an exquisite robe with many dragons sewed into it, his body looked in shape and he was smiling down while looking at the people below.

"Greetings young ones, I'm afraid I can't just let you continue with this. My disciple's life is at stake, why won't you give this old man some face and just forget about this?"

The three sect leaders backed off, they could feel that this ghost or illusion of the man wasn't anything simple. In their eyes, this must have been some kind of safeguarding function. This wasn't anything new as strong masters usually gave their core disciples ways of defending themselves while they were away.

"Honorable Senior is?"

Xu Qing cupped his fists as he reevaluated the whole situation, it was one thing to battle against someone with no backing and another if they had a strong force behind them.

"Oh me? It doesn't really matter, but if you must you can call me, Wei Hung!"

The man smiled cheerfully while replying to the question, the others took their time to rack their brains. From what they knew, there was no one by the name 'Wei Hung' that was known in the Empire and that was this strong. Before they could ask any more questions they felt a massive surge in spiritual energy getting exuded from that transparent figure.

"I won't take up much of your time, young ones. As you can see, I'm not really here, this is only a sliver of my true spirit that I have left with my disciple. I hope you will let my silly disciple be. If he wishes to establish a sect on his own so be it."

"You can have what is left of that demonic sect, I just wish for my disciple and his companions to be safe."

"If for some reason, you cannot go along with this old man's wishes..."

The old man paused and narrowed his eyes at the group of cultivators. Everyone shrunk down after they felt his overbearing power wash all over them. They all felt like small mice getting looked at by a ferocious lion, they were unable to utter a word or move just shocked by the display of his might.

"If you don't, well... let us just say that the number of sects will decrease by three in this empire, understood?"

The three sect leaders turned to each other and then back to the man that was talking to them. They just nodded out of sheer fright, knowing well that there was no one close to this man's strength even back at their headquarters.

"Then it's settled! I hope we can meet under better circumstances next time!"

The man's illusionary figure started flickering out and it soon exploded into many tiny particles of light. He wasn't there for more than a few minutes but he had left an impression that wouldn't be forgotten. After leaving Zhang Dong's eyes stopped glowing and he managed to awaken from his trance. His face showed confusion as he started looking around, the enemy cultivators were now slowly backing away unsure of what to do.

Chapter 193

People were standing with their mouths opened wide after the illusory figure of the man disappeared. His massive spiritual pressure was still on their minds. The nascent soul cultivators here were all on top of the food chain, so they knew that the senior that had just appeared wasn't anyone simple.

The gears in their heads started spinning around, trying to figure out this Wei Hung's true identity. There weren't many masters on the continent that were at the great circle of the nascent soul. Just as with core formation, there was a difference with someone at the beginning stages of it and at the end stages when they reached close to 100%.

This man had clearly shown power going beyond the beginning stages, which caused these cultivators that were at most at the late stage to be concerned. While they were thinking, that seniors disciple was floating down, his expression showing confusion.

"Wait... did my master take over my body?" What did he say?"

He looked around between the cultivators there, but wherever he looked the people from the other sects would evade his gaze, too scared to offend someone with that amount of backing.

"Senior Brother, I didn't know you had such a powerful master, now it all makes sense!"

Feng Liena moved closer, her big eyes were sparkling with admiration while looking up to her sect brother. Huo Qiang wasn't far behind as he also nodded whit agreement.

"Such power! Such presence! Now that was a true master!"

Zhang Dong glanced at his two friends, his mouth twitched slightly. He knew well that the master that showed up was something he came up as a defensive measure and he wasn't a real person. How he managed to do it is thanks to the holographic technology he came up with that was slowly spreading through the city along with the cubes that stored spiritual energy.

This was also why he had moved closer to the city where the holographic projector that he previously prepared was. He purposely made his body glow in a blinding light to get everyone's attention. He then activated the device that had a model of his Wei Hung persona inscribed into it. He could control what he was saying remotely and he used the cubes that stored large amounts of spiritual energy to create the illusion of the man behind him being really strong. From the look on the three main elders faces, it seemed to have worked.

"W-well yes, that's my master for you! No one can go against him if he makes up his mind!"

Zhang Dong laughed awkwardly while trying to hold a poker face. This little stunt had cost him most of his Qi reserves as he needed to add some juice to make it look realistic.

The cultivators from the three large sects looked at each other with worry. The leaders had to make a decision, would they risk offending some unknown entity to irradicate this upstart sect? Would the risk outweigh the gains? They only faced three enemies and this would probably be the best moment to strike, but the unknown backer was making these three leaders nervous.

"Brother Yang...brother Jie... I think this requires more time to discuss, why don't we consult with the other elders in our sects..."

Xu Qing was the first one to speak out, he was unwilling to risk his and his sect's life. Even if the risk was small, they could also gain new allies with these people if they showed mercy.

"Yes, that might be the wise path to take..."

Cheng Yang nodded as he replied.

"Hmph!"

Zhan Jie was the only one that looked maddened by the decision but if the others weren't willing to risk it, he wouldn't either.

"Zhang Dong was your name, right fellow Daoist?"

After everything was decided Xu Qing looked to Matt that was clearly the leader from this new sect.

"I hope there won't be any bad blood between our sects, we will allow you to reside here, but we will be taking the resources from that demonic sect. Don't think you will have anything against that?"

Zhang Dong nodded, he didn't really care about the cultivation resources of that sect. He had the cultivation manuals from the secret ground which were far superior to anything these sects could offer. It was enough for them to be able to survive, with time they would rise above the others.

"That is fine, we don't care about those demonic techniques or their resources. We just wish to establish our sect in peace, I'm sure we can decide on the land distribution at a later date."

Matt moved his hands behind his back as always, his body was slowly reaching its limit as he was feeling tired. He wanted to end this and end it fast, he could think about everything else after he had rested.

"I see that Daoist Dong is a wise man, yes let us decide on that later."

The three sect leaders nodded at each other. The siege of the main Dark Palm sect was still ongoing, there were also many large cities spread through this vast land that would be taken over. The help of these nascent soul masters would hasten everything and would lower the death count on their side. They had already spent some time here, so they wanted to resolve everything with haste.

"Yes, let us aid our brothers and sisters with taking down that demonic sect first, we will discuss everything later."

Everyone nodded and they bade Zhang Dong, Feng Liena, and Huo Qiang farewell. The two kept staring daggers at the invading cultivators all till they were little dots on the horizon.

"Sigh..."

"We should go back, let's keep the grand formation working, for now. We don't know if they will have a change of heart after they discuss everything with those so-called ancestral elders of theirs."

Matt said while gently floating down towards the remaining large structure. The two brand new sect elders agreed and continued after him, somehow everything got resolved with less bloodshed than anticipated. In their hearts, they knew that this wasn't over though. The three sects would probably keep testing them until they saw a chink in their armor. They needed to get stronger and they needed to do it fast.

With a wave of his finger, Zhang Dong created a little opening in the barrier and gently floated into the defensive formation. His two allies went in right behind him and closed it right after. This formation was intricate enough for it to record the energy signatures of some cultivators. Thanks to that it could be opened and closed without having to fully deactivate it.

The three were greeted with sounds of cheers, everyone was shouting the names of the new sect. The three elders' names were also called out, Zhang Dong's was of course the most prominent one. All three of them descended down to the ground as they did the crowd finally managed to calm down.

Everyone looked to their new leader, the man that made it happen. This, of course, caused Matt to sweat bullets internally, he had to yet again act his role and straighten out. Hands behind his back and his posture straight as a sword, unnoticed to most though his hands were trembling slightly. Not because he was nervous but because he had used up almost all of his spiritual energy and was now having a hard time keeping himself on his feet.

'I can't show them weakness...'

He wanted to laugh at himself, here he was a big sect leader now, looking out for his face as he was unwilling to show a flaw in front of this crowd of people. His motive was a bit more honorable than this as he wanted to present himself as a powerful leader that doesn't falter. If his people saw him stumble or throw up, they would probably see him in a worse light which would affect the morale.

'I can do this...just nod a bit and get this over with...'

He steeled his resolve, a few more minutes should be fine.

"My sect members this battle is over but we still must remain vigilant, the other sects will probably take some time with what remains of the Dark Palm sect."

"We require more information, we must gather up our forces and bolster our defenses. The grand formation will protect us for now but it's not the answer to our problem."

He continued talking rapidly while everyone was listening. His eyebrows quivered as he was close to falling asleep.

"M-my Master had bought us some time, but we don't know for how long the other sects will remain neutral. They might test us in the future, so I expect you to not cause trouble for your sect but remember to not show weakness. We will hold a meeting with all the senior members, we will discuss everything then."

Zhang Dong nodded after his quick speech, talking it over more throughout later would be the best option for now. The other's nodded without saying anything, how could they interrupt or ask questions when a senior elder like him was talking.

"There is still much work to be done, we will not be holding any banquets or victory events, it is still too soon for such things. Now go! there is still much to be done, I must retreat to my chambers to prepare!"

"Yes, Patriarch!"

"Yes, Sect Leader!"

"Yes, Senior!"

People bowed while giving him variously honorable titles, people like Zhang Jin and his two disciples were also there. Right in the front, their eyes were sparkling with so much admiration that he could probably light a football field with it if he could harness that power.

"Master!"

"Dong'er!"

Matt took a step forward while almost falling over, he had to stop himself as the people closest to him walked forward. They started praising him and he even received a firm smack to his back from his grandpa, which almost made him faceplant onto the cold hard floor.

'Don't you donger me you old fart, you want me to die?'

He wanted to shake his family member off and his disciples but they surrounded him from all sides. There they were, his two pupils with their mother, then there was gramps that even brought over his two wives. There were some other family members that he wasn't sure about, by this point he had no idea how many relatives he had. He would even believe if they told him that he was somehow related to Yang Guanyu that they just killed.

"Ah yes, dear grandfather and my two disciples I bet you worked hard, but your master has to..."

Before he could get himself out of it they all moved in closer and started barraging him with praises and questions. They all wanted to congratulate the man that made it all happen why also asking about this elusive Wei Hung that was pulling strings in the background. Before they could continue though, someone interrupted them. It was Feng Liena that stood right in front of the crowd that backed off after seeing the second nascent realm master of the sect.

"Senior Dong is a busy man, we still have preparations to make!"

She covered part of her face with a fan while speaking. The people that were in a circle around Zhang Dong moved apart a bit scared of this new senior elder. They were familiar with their Patriarch but this woman was still unfamiliar to the people close to him. Zhang Dong nodded at Feng Liena.

"Ah yes, I must take care of a few things that can't wait. Junior sister is right!"

He was finally able to leave, the people didn't dare to stop him after Feng Liena got involved as it seemed that he had some important things to tend to. He quickly walked towards his bed chambers, the corridor towards it was now empty as every able-bodied person was working.

Just before he could open the door he felt a bout of drowsiness washing over him. His vision got blurry and he felt like he was going to pass out. He buckled under his own weight and had to keep himself on his feet by placing one of his hands on the corridor wall. He slowly inched towards the door, he couldn't pass out in front of his room he at least had to make it inside where no one could see him.

He tried hard, yet he would not succeed. The battle was over and the tension was gone, his body started giving out as there was no reason to stay conscious. So he fell forward but he didn't land face down on something hard, instead, he felt like something soft had damped his descent. He couldn't quite put his finger on it, but he smelled a familiar scent of cherries. Soon everything faded and he passed out unable to hear the voice of the person that had caught him.

"It's okay Senior Brother, you can rest now..."

Chapter 194

Matt opened his eyes and looked around. He was sitting on a small island in the middle of nowhere, the sun was up and it was warm. He looked to the side, crystal clear water was surrounding him from all sides and he could hear the relaxing sound of the sea. He was wearing a pair of blue swim trunks and was relaxing on a lawn chair, in his hand a tall drink with a straw.

He didn't say anything and just looked up into the sky, fuzzy white and like cotton, the clouds were dancing. This seemed a bit out of place but he couldn't remember why so he just took a sip from his drink and leaned back in his chair, not a care in the world.

"Ah, this is the life... but I think I'm forgetting something... It's probably nothing."

He closed his eyes and started listening to the calming sounds. The wind was slowly pushing the leaves of the coconut tree by which he was sitting and some birds were squawking in the distance.

The calm day was suddenly interrupted though, by the same coconut tree that he was sitting under. A pair of coconuts fell down, hitting him on the head one after another and landing in his lap. The funny thing about those coconuts was, that they weren't hard at all. The hit to the head didn't hurt at all as the two-round objects bounced onto his legs.

"Hmm?"

He grasped one of those coco fruits that weren't actually nuts. He gave the left one a grasp and could feel it squishing uncharacteristically, you'd expect one of these to be hard as a brick but no, both of these coconuts were soft to the touch.

"Something isn't right here...I should investigate!"

He grabbed both of the nuts and brought them over closer, one of his eyes opening further than the other as he stared. He moved his hand closer and gave it a flick with his finger, the coconut wobbled in an odd fashion. The moment the flick occurred, he heard some kind of womanly voice that was strangely familiar.

"Ahhhh...n-nooo!"

He backed off for a moment, astonished by strange voice after the finger flick. The feeling he got was quite pleasant, he even reached out to grasp the large coco fruits with both hands. After a moment of feeling them out, he got the strange urge to bring them closer to his own face and so he did.

'Hm... what are these made of, marshmallows?'

"Ehhhh...w-what are you doing!"

The familiar voice was heard once more, this time it felt even closer than before. He wasn't sure why the coconuts were talking, but they sure felt soft against his manly face. He leaned back with the two round objects against his face and hugged them tightly a silly smile on his face.

"S-senior you...you mustn't, what if someone walks in!"

He stopped for a moment, why were the large squishy coconuts calling him a 'Senior?', he wasn't even that old. Also, why did these two smell really familiar. The more he hugged the more he remembered, the more he remembered the more the beach he was in shook and distorted.

Then he finally remembered. He recalled the battle with the nascent soul elders from the Dark Palm sect and then about the other group that came to clean up afterward. The world around him turned dark and he opened up his eyes, the beach he was in was just a dream he was having.

The moment his eyes opened he saw blackness but he wasn't blind, no he just had his whole face pressed into something. This something was immensely soft and squishy, blocking his view from all sides.

"Huh?"

He was finally awake. His hands were holding onto someone and this someone was on top of him. He could smell a characteristic perfume that one person that he knew liked to use it. He started sweating as he finally realized his transgression.

"S-senior brother...."

He slowly pulled his face back and looked up, he could see the blushing face of Feng Liena and her large blue eyes. Finally, the truth had been revealed, it was only a dream and the squishy coconuts belonged to his sect's junior sister Feng Liena. He was in his bed with his hands around the woman, hugging her tightly. His whole face was pressed into her large bosom that was bulging out due to the fact that he was pressing into her hard.

"Uh...this is..."

The moment Matt wanted to explain himself he heard a creaking sound. The sound was his bedroom door opening, he instinctively moved his face to the side to look at who had entered. Due to this sudden movement of his face Liena gave out a cutesy high pitch sound that echoed through the entire room.

"Senior Brother my father wishes to speak with yo..."

It was Huo Qiang walking through, his father had begged him for an audience and so he was here. He wasn't alone, Zhang Jin and his two grand-kids Zhang Liu and Xue used this chance to peek in as well. What they were greeted with was a half-naked Zhang Dong, that for some reason had his robe down. He was hugging a blushing Feng Liena and looking at them with his face between her globes.

The two quickly separated but what had been seen couldn't be easily forgotten. The group of four had different reactions, Zhang Jin just nodded with approval. Huo Qiang rubbed his chin but then just gave this senior brother a thumbs up. The two youths were a bit more bashful, Liu moved his head down while blushing and used his sleeve to cover his sister's face so that she wouldn't look at their master doing naughty things.

"Take all the time you need..."

Zhang Jin was quick to react, he pulled his two grand-kids away with haste and also whispered something into Huo Qiang's ear that made him grin and retreat as well. The others had left and Zhang Dong and Feng Liena were back to being all alone with each other. The girl was facing away from him with her face covered by her hands, blushing and not sure what to do.

Matt needed some time to process what had just happened. The last thing he remembered was trying to walk to his bed chambers so that he could pass out without alerting anyone from his sect members to his moment of weakness. He didn't make it in time but he recalled feeling someone's presence there before he fully lost his consciousness. He put two and two together to get his answer.

'It must have been Feng Liena that was there, she probably brought me to my room. But why am I almost naked in my boxer briefs...'

Yes, Zhang Dong was wearing undies made by himself as he couldn't get used to what the people in this world used instead. They had various ways of covering their nether regions, some even only wrapped some cloth or used some baggy underpants.Now he was all down to his undies and in bed, was Feng Liena always this bold?

"Y-you were sweating a lot so I've tried changing your clothes S-senior Brother..."

The woman noticed Zhang Dong looking at his robeless form wit confusion on his face, so she gave him a quick answer.

"Ahhh...well... uh..."

He rubbed his head slightly while quickly going through the room, he saw his robe to the side. There was a bowl with some spirit water there and a damp cloth was right next to him, it probably fell down from his forehead the moment he stuck his face between his sect sister's bosom.

"I think I have to apologize... and also, thank you..."

The woman clearly just tried to help him out, he probably had a fever from spiritual energy deprivation after the big battle. He still felt weak but he was slowly recovering. The thing that he did was probably seen as something shameful in this society, but his junior sister that was actually older than him didn't seem to mind. She finally turned around, her hands covering her eyes parted away to reveal her large blue eyes, her face slightly pinker than usual.

"You shouldn't get up senior brother, you are still suffering from Qi deprivation, you need to rest!"

Matt looked at Liena that had recovered her composure, he did feel slightly weakened but it wasn't anything that he couldn't walk out at this point.

"Ah, no need. I think I'm alright now, thank you for..."

Before he could finish his sentence the woman moved forward, her head shaking in disapproval.

"No! You must rest!"

He got surprised as she raised her voice by a note and more or less ordered him to rest. He wasn't really in the mood to argue with anyone and the danger was gone so he just nodded.

"Um, alright... I'll rest?"

He nodded and wanted to pull the bedsheets over himself but then Liena moved closer while holding a damp cloth.

"Senior Brother before that... I think you need to get cleaned... I couldn't finish before we got interrupted..."

"Interrupted?...oh..."

He recalled sticking his face into a large valley and just coughed into his hand.

"Finish what?"

He asked while looking to the woman, she in response took out a white cloth that was already moist from some of that spirit water. She held it up while looking at him, their eyes meeting.

"C-could you turn around, I'll clean your back..."

"My back?"

He looked down to himself, he was indeed sweaty. Luckily he didn't exude any kind of bad odor. He looked to the damp cloth and then to himself knowing what the woman intended to do.

"I could just wash up in the springs... there is one right there..."

He looked to his private springs where he even used to cultivate. It wasn't far from here so he could just soak in it if he required too.

"No! You shouldn't be walking and straining yourself, what if something happens just like before!"

Matt blinked a couple of times before nodding, Liena was uncharacteristically persistent this time around. She stared at him intensely as if she would tackle him down if he dared to stand up and go to the spring to soak in. He finally relented and nodded, she moved closer and placed the damp cloth against his wide back and started cleaning it up from the sweat.

He felt a bit strange with someone washing his back, he couldn't remember anyone doing such things besides his own mother and that was in his early childhood. He followed the instructions moving his hands up so she could take care of all the crevices. Unbeknownst to him, Feng Liena was seriously blushing all the way up to her ears while performing this task. Even though she was older than him, she had zero experience with men. Though as time passed she started getting more comfortable with the task.

"Junior Sister?"

There was a moment of silence between the two, he noticed that she was done with the task but for some reason, she chose to stop while placing her hand on his shoulder from the back.

"Senior brother..., thank you... for everything... for trusting in me, if it wasn't for you..."

She suddenly started thanking him out of the blue, he felt a bit uncomfortable and not sure how to react.

"You don't need to thank me, you also helped a lot. If it wasn't for you I would probably not be here either."

He tried deflecting the praise as he wasn't good at receiving compliments. Feng Liena smiled and moved her free hand to give the man a gentle tap on the shoulder, which of course took him by surprise.

"Senior brother, you should learn to accept other people's gratitude, even more, if it's coming from a beautiful maiden."

"Ahh, sorry..."

"If you're apologetic than prove it, Senior Brother."

"How would I prove that?"

He heard a giggle from the back and then felt the wet cloth moving away from his back. Feng Liena moved to the front a smile on her face.

"How about inviting this beautiful junior sister to some tea next time?"

She asked while slightly fidgeting, but the red on her ears didn't go unnoticed.

"Tea?...ahh..."

He would be quite dense if he didn't realize where this was going. He thought for a moment before nodding and looking straight into the beautiful woman's eyes.

"It would be a pleasure!"

The two looked at each other while smiling. In the background there stood a small group of people, they were all pushing against the large door with their ears. This was, of course, his two disciples Zhang Jin and Huo Qiang eavesdropping. If Zhang Dong and Feng Liena weren't so focused on each other they would probably feel them being there but they were blissfully unaware.

Chapter 195

Zhang Dong took a sip of some green tea while still being in bed. He was looking to the side through the windows at the destroyed scenery. The whole city was trashed and only a small circular spot where the grand defensive formation was placed remained. There was much work to be done and his face was solemn. It cleared up instantly though after he looked at the teacup in his hand.

"Tea huh?"

This was left by his junior sister Feng Liena. She was now part of the sect he was running and also part of the big three along with him and Huo Qiang. He thought to what transpired a few moments ago which put a dumb smile on his face.

'Well... I guess she is interested in me?'

He thought back to the interaction that they just had but most of his thoughts were pulled to the moment that he hugged her while sleeping. That soft sensation against his face was hard to forget along with that nice smell that she had.

'Does this mean that I have a girlfriend now?... What do you do with girlfriends? Wait, she only asked me out for tea...am I getting ahead of myself?’

He moved his head up and stared at the ceiling, he had agreed to go get some tea with Feng Liena later. This was akin to going on a date in this world and showing interest in a person of the opposite sex. He was someone with zero dating experience, not in his previous life or this. He had that small encounter with the merchant lady two years ago, but that couldn't be considered as dating but more of a one night stand.

'What do people do for fun here?'

He had no idea how relationships worked in this world, he only knew his grandfather and Huo Qiang that had many wives. They would probably not be the right people to ask about help unless he wanted to build a harem. He wasn't really the type of person to go for such things and having multiple wives felt like the road to disaster.

'I'm probably worrying too much about it... I should get dressed, there are many things to be done.'

His date would have to wait, the sect problems came first. There were also millions of people waiting in the woods probably hoping of returning to their homes. He needed to figure out if he wanted to still stay in this location or to move to a different area to establish a proper sect. This city was already destroyed and they had to rebuild it but the spiritual energy concentration here wasn't really adequate for a large sect.

'I promised them a meeting, it's already the next day.'

He had been forced to sleep it off by Feng Liena, the woman was apparently more strong-willed than he anticipated. He didn't want to argue too much so he decided to take the day off and just sleep it off. After a good night's rest, he was feeling much better, his spiritual energy wasn't fully recovered but it was enough to move around without needing others to look out for him.

He chuckled while thinking back, Liena had remained in this room and had scared other people from going in. She finally left in the morning after keeping watch, making sure that no one disturbed his rest.

'Wonder if she will be so overprotective if she has any kids,... why am I thinking about kids?'

He shook his head while standing up, he used his spatial ring to remove a fitting white robe for himself. He would need to design some uniform sect robes for the future.

'Hm, should I make them have different colors depending on the element a practitioner is adept at?'

He had the system with him, finding out what a person was talented at wasn't a problem. Still, no one was really locked to an elemental proficiency as even his disciples could train up in his lightning Dao. But it was still faster to progress in something you were naturally gifted.

He called over Zhang Kuo and Zhang Ya, he had to clear up some things with his two main retainers. The two looked a bit concerned and had their heads dropped, they both knew that the time came for their punishment.

"The main crisis is over... but there is still much work to be done."

"You two..."

He looked at them with a stern expression. The two withheld valuable information from him, they didn't inform him about the city his clan members were going to and that it was ruled by the Dark Palm sect. Still, no one knew that they would meet some kind of crazy young master there that would then lead into a full-blown war.

Could the clash have been avoided if he knew? He felt that even if he knew, his grandfather would probably have convinced him into allowing his clan's juniors to participate. He might have even put off his ascension into the nascent soul if he knew which would spell instant disaster. He wouldn't have been able to go against Wu Ming or any of the other nascent soul masters, running would have been the only option then.

"You held back information from your Patriarch. Do you have anything to say in your own defense?"

The two dropped down to their hands and knees.

"We are sorry Patriarch... no Sect Leader, we deserve death!"

The two nodded, Matt raised his brow at the instant death sentence that the two gave themselves. In their eyes, they caused a massive disservice to the whole clan that almost caused their downfall. Matt on the other hand didn't really blame them, they were only following orders that Zhang Jin gave. Those orders weren't actually wrong as he might have caused a bigger scene if he ever went together with their small expedition.

"Death? Do you really think that I want to see more people die?"

He was slightly ticked off by their response, why were these people always so quick to go to their demise for things like making their superiors look bad.

"S-sect leader?"

"There have been enough deaths already! You two, I want you to work hard, harder than you ever worked before!. After the sect is well established and doesn’t need you, you have the permission to die, if you so wish."

These two were talented managers, they had already lost people to this useless war. There was no reason for two loyal people like this to be sent to their deaths over a small mistake.

"Do you think you can do that? The Sect needs you!"

"Yes, Sect Leader!"

The two started smashing their heads into the hard floor tiles.

"That's enough, go and call over all the elders for a meeting, we must discuss our next move, stop hitting the floor with your heads, it's going to leave a crack..."

He was more concerned about the holes in his floor than about the damage these two would suffer from hitting it. They were both close to reaching the end stages of foundation establishment so they were really resistant, the floor wasn't.

After some more apologizing and bowing he managed to get rid of his two unruly retainers. He fixed his clothes one last time and went on with the day, he moved to the large auditorium looking room where they had their meetings. His people worked hard as even before he got there almost everyone was there and waiting.

"We greet the sect leader!"

"Welcome, Patriarch."

He got the usual greeting from his Zhang family members, the Feng clan women were quite enthusiastic as well, though the people from the Huo clan looked a bit reserved from how they handled themselves. He could see Huo Qiang waving at him, next to him was an old man that he saw before, he was even more muscular than his red-haired sect brother and the two looked alike.

Before he could start the meeting the two moved over and he got a nice smack to his shoulder from his little bro. Thanks to having his body refining upgraded, he didn't feel the hit all that much.

"Ha ha, hard as fine spirit metal, you see that father, that's what a real man should be like!"

Matt looked at Qiang and then to his so-called father. The man was big, but due to his musculature, he was even more imposing. He didn't look pleased, he didn't even bow his head at Zhang Dong which bothered most of the people from the Zhang faction.

'Oh he looks mad... well, we did pull them into a war with the sect and it's still unclear if we will be left alone...'

From Huo Gang's perspective, his son was at the same level of power as this man now.He was the father of a nascent soul senior, so he saw himself above the others by association. His son was right next to him, so he felt reassured while talking to Zhang Dong.

"Zhang Clan Patriarch... what are you planning, my Huo Clan never agreed to any of this! My son isn't the clan leader, I am!"

"Hey, you old fart, what are you talking about!"

Huo Qiang looked at his father with a frown on his face.

"Quiet, I am still your father!"

The man shouted out loud, he was obviously mad for the way this all played out. From his point of view, this was all too risky. There weren't enough nascent soul elders and he didn't trust Zhang Dong at all. He hadn't seen the immortal grade techniques either, so he had no idea why his son and so many others were following this white-haired man.

'Uh...if I explain everything this guy will probably see reason, but...'

He did a quick scan of the room. Every person from the senior generation was here, they were all leaders and future elders of the sect. Some of them could probably reach the nascent soul level if they got the correct techniques and more time. His authority was getting questioned by this man if he pulled back he would probably look weak in front of these old fashioned cultivator types.

'I bet he is banking on me respecting Qiang's authority and not going overboard...'

To Matt, it looked as if this man was doing some kind of strange power move. He probably wanted to show that he was the father of one of the core sect elders and that he wasn't afraid of the sect leader. Maybe he was even convinced that Huo Qiang would jump into his defense if Zhang Dong went on the offensive.

‘Maybe he thinks that I wouldn’t dare to offend the father of an important ally as Huo Qiang?’

'I guess I need to make a show of force… this is the way these old farts operate…’'

He also noticed Feng Liena fuming in the back, her eyes were staring daggers into the man's back and she was ready to pounce.

"How dare yo..."

She shouted out but Zhang Dong moved his hand up while looking at her with a gentle smile. He then looked to the man while still having the same smile. Huo Gang then felt a rise in spiritual energy in the area and it was focusing on the place he was standing in.

Zhang Dong's eyes glowed with golden light and small lightning bolts started getting expelled from his eye sockets. The man felt a massive amount of weight getting put on his shoulders. He was unable to resist as he collapsed to his knees, sweating under Zhang Dong's aura. Huo Qiang was surprised by his senior brother's fast reaction and by reflex tried reaching out to help his own father. He felt a jolt to his hand the moment he leaned in, the suppressive aura was even strong enough to push him back who was a nascent soul cultivator.

"Your son agreed, that was enough at that time. I will not keep your clan here if you wish you may leave. Though, I'm not sure the other sects would allow you to do this after your association to the United Element sect is known."

"The Zhang Clan, Feng Clan, and the Huo Clan... those names won't matter much in the future. We are a sect now and as a sect I expect everyone to work together, I might be the Sect Master but I will still consult the senior members on important matters."

"I do not wish for this sect to eat itself from the inside as the Dark Palm sect did."

He released the pressure allowing Qiang's father to stand up, he patted him on the shoulder while continuing to speak.

"Your son is like a brother to me, I do not wish to see you using him to further yourself. I know that you are afraid about your position and your clan's in this sect. I assure you that I will not treat your family with scorn. Everyone's place will depend on their individual achievements and nothing more!"

He finished his speech and moved over to the spot of honor at the helm.

"Well then, let us start this meeting, any questions?"

Everyone looked a bit bewildered by Zhang Dong's outburst and most of them were now afraid to bring up any personal matters.

Chapter 196

The meeting finally started after the small dramatic exchange between the new sect leader and Huo Qiang's father. He was pacified now and in the corner with a stern expression on his face. From Zhang Dong's perspective, he looked to be sulking but he didn't really want to argue with the old man anymore.

"Give me a full report on the situation... I can feel that we are being watched..."

Matt could sense that there were some nascent soul elders far away but still close enough for him to sense some of their spiritual essence. They were probably keeping watch on the small locked off area, ordered by their elders. Zhang Kuo stepped forward, everyone in the room looked to him as he was going to give the report.

"As the Sect Leader says, we have sighted some of the nascent soul elders from all of the three sects that were here previously. Each one of them left a senior behind, probably to keep watch over us."

"Regarding the Dark Palm Sect, their main sanctuary is being attacked by the combined forces of the three sects. They have not yet fallen but they stand no chance against the combined strength of those three large sects."

They still had some spies that were outside Spirit Spring City that could relay some information through their communication jades. The demonic sect that was here the other day was now on the defensive. They were huddled up behind their defensive formations and fighting for their life.

"We are not sure what is happening inside as it was far too dangerous for our spies to go in closer, we can only speculate on what is happening."

"Hmm... they'll probably last a bit before they fall, what about the people that evacuated into the forests?"

"They are safe and are being guarded by some of our sect members, they have enough food and water to last them a couple of months."

Zhang Dong nodded, his people weren't in any danger at the time being which was reassuring.

"What about the city?"

"Spirit Spring City has mostly been destroyed... the Dark Palm sect bombarder everything with their cannons. The city has been leveled, there is nothing left to salvage, besides rubble."

The Zhang Clan members were unhappy, to say the least about this turn of events. They had spent the past two years upgrading the whole city infrastructure to the peak, they had hospitals, police stations, and even a fire station all in working condition. They knew that rebuilding everything would cost a lot and their Patriarch had burned through every single spirit stone that they had saved up.

"So only the Zhang Clan main compound remains..."

Zhang Dong shook his head, not happy that two years of work went down the drain just like that. He wouldn't be getting any spirit points from his system from Spirit Spring City anymore if it was like this. He was now contemplating moving his base of operations elsewhere, somewhere with more spiritual energy.

"If the Zhang Clan needs a place to stay they can come to our Red Lotus City."

Feng Liena interrupted while smiling at Zhang Dong, who nodded at the proposition with gratitude.

"Red Lotus City? That place is too small, we can just go to my Qingliang City!"

Huo Qiang shouted out while smacking his broad chest with his large hand, if his senior brother wanted a new base of operations he wanted his home to be it.

"Ah Qingliang City, is it?

Surprisingly his father didn't reject the idea, instead, he moved his hands over his chest in a cross shape and nodded.

"I agree, what better place for the new sect than in Qingliang City!"

"Red Lotus City has a better location and it's closer to the Zhang Sanctuary as well, I think it would be a better option!"

Feng Maling interjected on Liena's accord as she could see that her granddaughter was fuming with anger after Huo Qiang interrupted her.

"Patriarch, why should we move, we can just rebuild the old city and make it better and stronger than it ever was! Like a Phoenix, it will rise from the ashes!"

This time Zhang Zhi shouted out, some of his clan members also nodded as they were hesitant about just leaving their old home behind. The main sanctuary of their clan was still intact and it was even protected by a very powerful defensive formation. Not even nascent soul seniors could muscle their way into it.

Matt put his hands together while nodding at the propositions. To spend resources and rebuild, or to move on to greener pastures? He wasn't sure but he was leaning into another direction then the three main forces in this room. A small shouting match ensured where the Zhang Clan, Feng Clan, and Huo Clan were trying to convince Zhang Dong of seeing it their way.

"The United Element Sect, what is it?"

He asked, interrupting everyone in the room.

"It's a gathering of our three clans?"

One of the older members called out while the others nodded.

"Is it? I don't think this sect will have a future if we are just that..."

"Do you wish to conscript more people into the sect, Sect Leader?"

Another elder asked.

"That's a given, you saw those large sects, we pale not only in the number of nascent soul cultivators, but we also have fewer core formation experts and our foundation establishment juniors aren't enough."

"I don't think we should move into any of those two cities, and neither should we remain here, we need a more suitable spot."

"Where would we find such a location, Senior Brother?"

Feng Liena asked a bit saddened that her proposition was denied.

"That is something I can't tell just yet, I must go through the lands to see..."

Matt's mapping feature had gotten a boost since he reached the nascent soul level. He could now check to see below the earth as well, he wanted to scout the area's out. He wanted to find something akin to the spiritual veins that could be found in the deeper regions in the empire. He wasn't hoping for that much but even another spirit stone mine would be enough.

He had heaven grade spiritual energy gathering formation in his library, so he didn't need a place with a high concentration of it, he just needed it to be manageable.

"It would be best if those three sects allowed us to stay at the area where the Dark Palm Sect was located but don't think they will let us."

The people nodded, the large sects had their bases located in places with strong spiritual energies. It wouldn't be odd if those clans left some of their members there after they conquered it.

"Maybe if the honorable Wei Hung acted, we could gain that land for ourselves?"

One of the Zhang Clan Elders asked the others nodded with approval while looking at Zhang Dong. In their opinion, if that strong master acted even the three sects would have to listen. Wei Hung's illusion had left a big impression on these people, they thought it was just a slither of his true might and it was already that strong, how powerful was Zhang Dong's master in person? He might have even been on par with the Azure Emperor that ruled the land!

Zhang Dong just shook his head side to side while answering.

“My master won’t act unless it’s really dire, he only acted when my life was in danger, I fear he doesn’t care for this sect of mine. I wouldn’t put my faith into him that much, personal strength is always better than borrowed one.”

The elders in the room sighed out after Zhang Dong’s reply. They knew those types of masters that weren’t concerned about anything besides their disciples. Wei Hung was apparently one of those, only taking action when his pupil was in danger but not caring about the people involved with him or her.

“That’s… understandable…”

“Regretful…”

The elders voiced their concerns but still encouraged Zhang Dong to seek out his master for help. He just nodded at the request, though he knew no help was coming as he was his own master.

“The main concern is the three large sects, Dragon Gate, Limitless Sword, and Demon Subduing… we don’t know what they will do but I don’t think they will let us have any of the more bountiful lands.”

“I agree with Senior Brother, they probably won’t allow us into the mainland that is closer to the spiritual veins.”

Feng Liena responded while everyone in the room nodded. It would be quite foolish from the three powerhouses to let them reside in places with a high concentration of Qi. The spiritual veins were something that formed naturally in this world.

Cultivators in this world liked to place their sects in areas with spiritual veins with high concentration. This was also how things in this empire were constructed. The spiritual veins with the highest concentration were further into the mainland, the closest place to it was the Empire’s Capital city.

The Azure Emperor lived there with his clan, he wasn’t part of any sect but that didn’t matter if you were the strongest person around. His clan had many powerful experts and even if they had fewer people than some of the sects they excelled in quality over quantity.

“Yes, they just might make us remain in these lower lands where the spiritual energy isn’t high enough to produce nascent soul cultivators…”

Everyone nodded, that was the likely scenario and they wouldn’t be able to go against all three of those sects even if their three nascent soul elders could contend with the opponents.

‘Hm, the improved versions of the techniques are superior which mostly means that they require more spiritual energy to cultivate in.’

Matt rubbed his chin, he needed to get his sect into a good location, otherwise it would take decades until they achieved anything.

‘Should I sneak into their territory and raid their spirit stone mines?’

Matt didn’t really want to do risky things like that, even with a spirit stone mine converted into points he couldn’t produce that many nascent soul masters, unless he dropped a grade with their cultivation manuals.

“Yes, that is probably what they have planned but not like we can do anything about it.”

Zhang Jin commented from the side with a frown on his face.

The meeting continued well into the night. While they had Zhang Dong’s attention the other members from the new sect were sure to ask him many questions. Some of them were even trying to reel him into their families with marriage proposals. This of course earned the scorn from the Feng Clan side of the sect.

They went over the death reports and decided on giving all the warriors a proper send-off. Their families would be getting some monetary compensation and could even get a position as a disciple.

Further discussions were halted as no one knew where their new base of operations would be. They needed to plan the internal structure of their sect and also needed to build the proper facilities to house the outer, inner, and core disciples.

They decided that a merit-based system with incentives would be the best. Every new disciple would be put in an age bracket and tested. The average recruits would be outer disciples, above them were the inner disciples with more privileges and even further were the core disciples that were the true elites.

They didn’t go into much detail about the merit system and rewards as no one knew how much resources they would have to spare.

“Then it is decided, we will wait till the situation with the Dark Palm sect is resolved, we will bolster our defenses and me and the two Grand Elders will continue cultivating in preparations.”

Zhang Dong went with the term ‘Grand Elder’ just like their enemies did as it was something easy to follow. Soon enough everyone dispersed and went to prepare for the future tasks of making the sect.

While Zhang Dong was heading out he came across his female grand elder, she was apparently waiting for him. She gave him a smile, her face beaming as she just stared into his eyes.

“Ah, yes!“

He straightened himself out a bit, it was time to get some tea. The future was uncertain but it also held many wondrous possibilities.

Chapter 197

The days passed and the news about the Dark Palm sect issue reached everyone in the land. The word of a new upstart sect taking them out and that the three similar-sized sects that were close by were now besieging their Harmonious Peaks. Everyone was curious about the new upstart that had formed but even more curious why it hadn't been eradicated by the three powerful sects.

The Dark Palm sect was in shambles, some of the peaks had crumbled before the combined might of the enemy alliance. The ancestral elders did their best to keep the defensive formation working but they were at an impasse. They were trapped in a defensive battle, unable to flee and far too old to last a prolonged battle against multiple nascent soul masters at a similar level.

Without much else to do, Zhang Dong and his allies had to wait. They cultivated with diligence, increasing their understanding of the newly gained Dao they were cultivating in.

The tensions were high, no one knew what would happen. Everyone was on edge, preparing for the worse while trying to bolster their personal might.

With more time passing news of the evil sect's demise reached their ears. After two months of continuous struggling, the demonic sect was announced vanquished. The ancestral elders were all slain and everyone associated with the evil sect was sentenced to death.

As it goes with large sects like these, there were many stragglers left outside. There were just too many members to eradicate and not enough time or manpower. There was a slight chance that someone could try taking revenge on the three sects but it was highly unlikely that they would succeed. The best they could hope for is a quiet life in the lower levels or being taken in by other sects while hiding their identity.

The war was finally over. The giant sect was no more but life continued. Demon Subduing Sect, Dragon Gate Sect, and The Limitless Sword Society they were the true winner of this short war. They had used the confusion that began with Zhang Dong's appearance and managed to vanquish a long time rival.

They all wanted a piece of the pie now, the alliance wasn't one that was build of friendship or necessity, it was built on profit. Any one of them could have been in the Dark Palm Sect's place if things went differently. They didn't voice it but everyone knew that they would betray each other at a moment's notice if it proved profitable and safe.

Back at Spirit Spring City or what was left of it, Zhang Dong was sitting in the lotus position .He was in the Dimensional Regalia along with Huo Qiang and Feng Liena. The three of them used this opportunity to strengthen themselves, they did some light sparring while increasing their cultivation bases.

'Mmm... it's not as easy as it used to be...'

Zhang Dong grumbled while opening his eyes. When he was in core formation he could just progress with the help of the ambient Qi energies in the surroundings. Now it was different, his progress was slow and going at a snail's pace. Even after two months had passed he had barely managed to push his cultivation past 1%. At this pace, he would reach the middle stage realm in about 16 years.

He gave out a sigh and decided to take a walk, sitting around for hours while just taking in energy was still a boring past time. Luckily as a cultivator, he entered a type of cultivation trance that made the time seem to pass faster.

The floating island had gotten larger than before as well. He had convinced both his friends to donate some spiritual energy each day along with him. Three nascent soul cultivators that had immortal grade cultivation methods were infusing this island with their power now. It went from a couple of kilometers in diameter to close to twenty. With high-quality Qi it was growing steadily and could now truly be used as a secret space of the sect.

Before plans to further this place could come to fruition they still had to resolve one problem.

Zhang Dong didn't interrupt the others with their cultivation and stepped out, which was just in time to hear someone running up with haste. He could tell with his spiritual sense that it was Zhang Kuo.

"Is there any news?"

The man looked a bit more frantic than usual, his body temperature was also higher and he was clearly sweating.

"Yes Patriarch... the Dark Palm Sect... is no more!"

Zhang Dong nodded, this was about the time he thought it would take for them to get through their defenses. He straightened out while giving his reply.

"Any word from those three sects? Did they send someone or made any demands?"

Kuo nodded at the question and gave a swift reply.

"Yes my lord, they have actually sent word, although..."

Zhang Dong could see the man clench his fist tighter as if something was bothering him, his body language was making him look angered.

"Good, what do they want? What are the terms?"

Kuo took out a jade slip and presented it to his Patriarch. Zhang Dong raised his eyebrow before scanning the jade slip with his spiritual sense. He was actually expecting them to send someone in person to do some negotiating, he received a message via jade mail instead.

"Hoh? I kind of figured this much but they don't take us very seriously, do they?"

Zhang Kuo nodded while taking the jade slip back. The three sects gave their terms, the United Elements sect would be allowed to exist but they were to remain in the regions previously occupied by the middle-sized clans. This meant that they wouldn't actually be getting any land that was previously used by the Dark Palm Sect. They were also required to pay a large sum in spirit stones or other resources like herbs or weapons. The explanation given for that was that it was a payment for the land they were graciously given.

"Mmm, you can leave."

Zhang Kuo nodded and left, Zhang Dong on the other hand was just glad that it was now over. Even though it looked like their new sect wouldn't go far, he knew that things weren't all that bad. He still had all those high-level techniques and he had his system. With him being the sect leader he was now the proud owner of a vast tract of land. Many people lived there, many people that if treated right would give him many spirit points which he could spend to improve his techniques even more or even increase his own cultivation or from his sect members.

It was time to stabilize his new faction. Even though the other sects weren't taking them seriously, he preferred that. It was easier to go against someone that was underestimating you.

'I bet they fear my Wei Hung persona more than they fear me. They will probably place spies all around the place to keep watch over us. Well not like it matters...'

Thanks to the Medallion treasure he was content. No spies would be getting their hands on their cultivation manuals, he had ways of catching those types of people. The screening process that he was planning to implement would catch them in the act, only loyal disciples and elders would be allowed inside, growing in power through the years until they were strong enough to break away from the shackles.

He continued walking outside, his gaze on the still destroyed scenery. He had come to this world over two years ago, he was slowly integrating himself with the people. He sometimes asked himself about why he was even going so far. There were many occasions for him to just leave, he would have been safer as a solo act but he decided to stay.

He never felt like he had a purpose in his life before this. He lived his life alone, he didn't depend on others and no one else depended on him as he led his boring life of going to work and playing games. Somehow he ended up in here, many times stronger than an average man and many times over his head.

He somehow managed to survive until this point but he attributed it to luck and his system. Going forward he wanted to further his relations with these people. They were quirky and strange but somehow they grew on him. He was slowly growing into the role of a leader, caring more for his people than his own well being.

He floated up into the sky, going past the defensive formation that opened a little hole for him. He didn't go unnoticed from his sect members that offered him bows.

If he was an original resident from this world he would have been quite maddened. The three other sects just dumped their demands on him without giving any space for negotiation. This would be considered a big blow to the face for the entire sect and could even evolve into a full-blown reason to go to war with.

Zhang Dong on the other hand didn't care as much for this so-called face. Regretfully, he was still a flawed human and sometimes he would feel like being petty. He closed his eyes and released his spiritual sense into the area making it travel far and wide to find someone.

It didn't take long for him to spot his target, his enhanced system map made it appear as a dot. He opened up his eyes and without much warning bolted into that direction. His colossal nascent soul immortal grade aura blasting into all directions as he kicked up a storm.

"What is the Patriarch doing?"

This was the thing the people down below were asking themselves. They just saw their leader take off in a certain direction, one of the more informed elders from the sect took a moment to realize where Zhang Dong's destination was.

"Oh no... why is the leader going towards that person... I must report this to the other two grand elders!"

He took off running while sweating profusely.

Zhang Dong on the other side was close to arriving at his destination which was a person. The moment he arrived he could see an old man wearing a Dragon Gate Sect robe. The man was very old and was looking at Zhang Dong with a frown on his face and with a raised eyebrow.

"What is the meaning of this?"

"Oh? What do you mean honorable elder from the Dragon Gate Sect? Can't I greet such an esteemed senior from such a profound sect in my own lands?"

The man was even more confused than before. He was a nascent realm practitioner left here by his sect leader to keep an eye out. He was now trembling slightly as Zhang Dong's massive overbearing aura was causing him distress, from the look of things this man had come to cause trouble.

"Why don't we invite your other two friends?"

It didn't take long for the leftover elders from Limitless Sword Society and Demon Subduing Sect to arrive. Both of them were on guard and unsure of what this man was up to. They were all early stage, nascent soul cultivators, ones of the weakest from their sides as the more prominent ones had left to help in the war efforts.

"What do you want! Are you trying to go against us?"

They didn't take out their weapons but they were on guard. Zhang Dong just smiled while hovering in mid-air, his aura becoming even more overbearing after the three had gathered together. He was someone who jumped realms, even at the early stage his Qi was above a middle stage practitioner. If he added his empowering technique on top of that he could contend with late-stage cultivators.

The three started feeling dizzy, he was clearly too much for them to handle. They saw this man fight during the war and he was at the level of their own sect leaders, without them around they didn't feel confident.

"Why the long faces? I've just wanted to greet you, three esteemed friends. Just trying to be a proper host, you are in the United Element Sect's lands, even your leaders agreed to this."

He nodded while the three men shrunk back. He was clearly threatening them with his aura while saying those friendly words and the three were smart enough to get the memo. Don't get overboard in my land was the message he was trying to give.

"Don't think you look interested in tea... how about I escort you to the borders, they aren't that far, think they start off at Jade Grass City."

The three were getting crushed under the overbearing pressure and knew well that this man wasn't willing to negotiate. They just nodded and turned around, he at least made some sense as the war was over and it was considered rude to have other sects come to your lands uninvited.

"We shall leave, but don't be unreasonable, your sect might not last long otherwise!"

The three snorted while leaving, Zhang Dong just remained in mid-air while smiling he even waved them goodbye. His waving hand changed into a fist with a middle finger raised, no one really knew what this hand gesture meant though.

With a resounding sigh, he then turned around, there was more work to be done.

Chapter 198

Not much came from Zhang Dong's little power move. The three sects set up their new borders and kept their word while taking all of the best lands that the Dark Palm sect possessed. What the United Element sect was left with were the usual middle-sized cities that were previously ruled by clans like the Huo or Feng clan.

The new sect had to momentarily pause their spiritual formation as the power cubes were slowly running out of juice. There were spirit gathering formation set up to lower the burden on them. Regretfully they couldn't keep up with the Qi usage this grand formation had as it could keep most of the nascent soul realm cultivators at bay.

The main base was left with Feng Liena while Huo Qiang had to be moved closer to the border region as a defensive measure. Zhang Dong on the other hand was now flying around the large piece of real estate that he has graciously received from the three sects.

"Still nothing..."

He gave out a sigh, he made sure to fly as close to the ground as possible. He did it so that his mapping feature could pick up on spots below the ground that were high in spiritual energy. He had been on it for a week now just zig-zagging between locations while hovering half a meter above the ground.

To his dismay he wasn't able to find anything worthwhile, the best thing he came across was a tiny spirit stone pocket that wouldn't be more than a million spirit points if he converted it. It could be used to pay the high taxes that the other sects were putting on them, so it wasn't all bad.

Zhang Dong stopped and was looking at his new 3D map. He could see his movement patterns, he was sure to inspect all the places and he even made sure to have the borders selected so he didn't anger the other sects by going into their territory.

"I was hoping that I'd find something by now..."

He rubbed his glabella in concern. He wanted to create his new sect home base somewhere new, somewhere where there was a lot of spiritual energy for the sect disciples to flourish. He would even take a spot where there are some other resources like herbs that could be used for pills at this point.

He stared at his map once more and then looked at the scenery, he ended up in a forest area. The trees could be seen for kilometers without end. He blinked while thinking back to the past, he knew this area.

"Hey, isn't this..."

Part of his lip raised itself into a small smile, he remembered this area. This was where it all started, the same forest that he appeared after being stuck in this world. He had flown all the way back here while being preoccupied with looking at his system map.

The memories flooded in, he recalled getting scared of an angry looking horned bunny. The creature looked quite ferocious for a first-timer, recalling it now just brought a blush to his cheeks. He wondered if the people from that tribe were still living here, he released his spiritual sense into the surroundings as he tried finding where that old village of the Tatar Tribe was.

"Found it...but..."

He furrowed his brows, he had located the place where he spent a couple of weeks at hunting monsters and grinding points. The problem was that he could feel some uncharacteristic Qi signatures there. For one thing, there were people at the foundation establishment stage as well as someone at core formation there.

"Could they be..."

It didn't take him long to figure out who these people were. He took off with haste worried about the outcome if he didn't interfere. Luckily he detected that there was no bloodshed just yet, he would probably make it in time. He was hiding his presence so the cultivators below wouldn't notice him, the moment he arrived he could see a scene playing out.

The Tatar Tribe people were getting rounded up into the middle of their square. They were surrounded by a group of mean-looking cultivators from all sides, the auras of these people were far too strong for the Qi condensation tribesmen. For the moment he just listened in, wondering what those people plan was.

"Senior... we have gathered all of these lowly commoners."

The cultivator that looked to be in charge nodded after another person came over to give him a report. It was an old man that was wearing an eyepatch and looked slightly beaten up. The people were wearing black robes with a familiar symbol of a dark palmprint on their backs. They were obviously remnants from the destroyed sect that had somehow escaped into the lowest region.

"Well done, take their clothes, then kill them all. The old sect is gone and we must remain hidden from that upstart sect..."

Zhang Dong continued to listen as the man in charge gave his instructions. The plan was to take this village over, the Dark Palm remnants would use these tribesmen's clothes and live like them in this small village. They probably didn't think that anyone would find them all the way here were most respectable cultivators never showed up.

Which wasn't such a bad plan all things considered. They were from a hunted sect, they could either disperse and go about as rouge cultivators or set up a base of operations. Unless a nascent soul cultivator or at least a core formation elder appeared, they would probably go unnoticed while hiding their aura. While the order to kill and strip was given, one of the tribe youths shouted out.

"You won't get away with this, The mighty Lord Dong will eradicate you all!"

Matt wanted to cough after hearing his mighty tittle. He did a quick scan of the name of the person that just shouted out and was surprised that it was the silkypants youth that he had met before by the name of Yang Rong. Next to him was another youth that nodded with approval while yelling. His name was Cheng Yun and he was also someone that he knew from back in the day.

"That's right!"

"Lord Dong? Do you think Zhang Dong from that upstart sect will ever come to a shit hole like this?"

The senior from the group laughed and so did the people from the Dark Palm sect, no one expected a nascent soul elder to ever come to an area with a low amount of spiritual energy like this was. There was a reason why the tribe people were considered the weakest in all of the empire. Their location was in a place where cultivating was extra difficult.

"Now stop talking, this will be all over soon!"

The Tribe's people started shouting out, they were unwilling to die here. There were hundreds of people gathered here and they would be put to death so that these renegade cultivators could escape their death sentence. The tribe's people were being held back by the suppressive pressure of these superior cultivators and they couldn't move.

They could only sit together while trembling, indignity in their eyes. They looked at the various faces of the people that were pulling out swords and sabers. This looked like it was going to be it for them, the women and children weren't even going to be spared in this massacre.

But just as the sobbing started something unusual occurred. The pressure that that murderous group was giving out suddenly stopped while they themselves stopped in their tracks. The people from the Tatar Tribe were baffled by the display as the cultivators stopped mid-stride.

"What is this?"

They asked aloud while standing up, the Dark Palm remnants were clearly unable to move and alive. They could see them sweating and their brows were twitching.

"Hello there people of the Tatar Tribe, we meet again."

The villagers heard a voice coming from above, it was very familiar as it belonged to someone that had left an impression on everyone here. They all glanced up and saw a man in a white robe descending, his white hair was fluttering in the wind and he had his hands behind his back. He looked like a god descending from heaven, he even had some kind of unearthly glow about him that seemed to be golden.

"B-by the moons, it's the honorable Lord Dong!"

One of the tribe members finally managed to shout out while all the others were still slack-jawed. The answer to the unmoving evil cultivators was right before them. This man had come to aid them in their time of need and he did it once again just like two years ago.

"Its the Lord!"

"The Mighty Dong!"

"Yeah!"

Everyone cheered out while Matt was kind of contemplating if he could get some kind of pseudonym. It wasn't odd for powerful cultivators to change names, maybe he could find something more fitting and not be referred to as large genitals anymore.

He moved his hand up, instantly everyone quieted down while bowing in respect. Zhang Dong descended right to the ground and looked at the Dark Palm sect remnants that were being all held back by his nascent soul realm power.

"Quite a gathering of scumbags if I do have to say so myself, got anything to say for yourselves?"

He stopped some of his aura from seeping out allowing the Dark Palm cultivators to speak out. What he got in return was a lot of pleading shouts.

"No please honorable senior it was all Shi Tao's fault, we couldn't go against him!"

"You bastards, you want to pin all the blame on me now!"

"Yes venerable Daoist, it was all him we couldn't go against him, no one wished to harm these good people!"

The lower realm cultivators were quick to blame their leader for everything, he was the sole core formation expert in the group so he was an easy target to shift the blame to. Zhang Dong just shook his head side to side.

"I hope my sect doesn't become like you..."

"I should kill you all here right now, you wanted to murder all of these innocent people here, women and children included."

"Lucky for you, my sect is in need of 'free' labor at the moment, you will spend the rest of your life working in mines."

He had also found pockets that had some mineral deposits scattered here and there. The metals there weren't anything all that special at most usable for earth grade materials but it was still a source of revenue. He would cripple all of these evil cultivators and they would spend the rest of their life working as slaves.

"F-free labor senior?"

"Slaves, you will be slaves. Death would be too easy of a punishment for the likes of you. You will have a lot of time to repent."

The Dark Palm remnants trembled in indignation. Their plan had failed and now a future worse than death awaited them, slaving away god knows where while getting whipped and abused.

Zhang Dong brought out his communication jade and informed his sect members about the issue. They still had some flying ships so they could transport these people. After taking care of that issue he turned to the large group of trembling people. He waved his hand forward and they all started floating up into the air and towards each other.

They started shouting out, pleading for mercy but Matt wasn't going to be lenient with them. A giant share of electricity surrounded the group of cultivators, shocking them with golden lightning while destroying their foundation pillars.

The Tatar Tribe's people looked with shock and awe at the bright light show. They were astonished by the power this man possessed, to them he was getting closer to a godly being than to a man. They all dropped down to their knees and started bowing at the display of his might.

"These guys shouldn't be a problem for you anymore, so please tie them up until people from my sect arrive to pick them up."

He dropped the charred and twitching cultivators down to the ground, they were all passed out and their cultivation path was broken. A child at Qi condensation level was now stronger than them.

Chapter 199

Matt was feeling a bit uncomfortable right now. He was surrounded by people from all sides. His sect members would need at least a day to get here and he felt that just leaving without a word would be a tad rude.

“So… long time no see?”

To his question there was no reply, the people were bowing face down and with their butts raised into the air. They were probably afraid to meet the gaze of the man that almost single-handedly took out the Dark Palm sect.

Zhang Dong just wanted to facepalm but instead, he just nodded and gave a more compelling order. He knew from his experience how people like this operated.

“Rise up, that’s enough.”

The people slowly moved their heads up, their eyes were uncharacteristically sparkly. He could tell that he was getting revered by this group. From their standpoint, he was one of the most powerful experts in the whole empire, a nascent soul realm master. He had also aided them in this time of need and previously saved the Chief’s son from a powerful monster.

The first man to get up and walk up to him was the old Tribe Chief, he didn’t change all that much in these past two years, maybe a wrinkle or two here or there. He clasped his hands in respect once again before finally opening his mouth.

“Honorable Senior, you have aided us once again, how can this Tatar Tribe ever hope to repay you?”

While the chief was speaking the rest of the Tribe people started standing up. Yang Rong and Cheng Yun that he met before were side by side. They had apparently buried the hatchet and Yang Rong in particular had grown up to be a respectable young man that was on his way to be the next Tribe Chief.

“Ah, You don’t need to repay me, just live your life, as usual, it was just luck that I was close by while all of this was happening.”

Zhang Dong glanced at the charred Dark Palm members and was brought back to reality. He didn’t have time to exchange more pleasantries with these people. He had to map out the area and find a good spot for his sect to flourish.

“But I shouldn’t linger, I didn’t come here to play around.”

He wanted to leave but the Tribe’s people couldn’t let such a chance slip by. This was a powerful nascent realm master, they wouldn’t have a second chance like this in their lifetime. They needed to somehow lure him in and maybe accept one of the youths as a disciple.

"Please Honorable Senior Dong, we must hold a giant feast, why don’t you rest and let us show you some gratitude?”

The village chief glanced to the side at some of his people that were quick to pick up on his scheme. They sprung to action fast, they surrounded Zhang Dong even closer and started begging him to stay, they were a lot of young ladies even mixed in to appeal to the man’s male side.

“Please Grandmaster won’t you stay?”

“Won’t you stay to enjoy our tribe's best foods?”

“Please let me be your disciple, I’ll offer my kowtows of respect!”

“Do you need some servants for your travels, I’m sure the youths would be helpful, take as many as you want!”

“My daughter is a good cook and she can clean, she would be great as a maid for you my lord.”

Various people started clamoring for his attention. If they had even one of their family members work for this man their status would skyrocket.

Matt raised his eyebrow at the Tribe’s people. They were moments away from getting massacred by the evil cultivators. You’d think that no person would be able to make a quick 180 after a traumatic event like this but here they were.

He got reminded of how tough people in this world were. When they saw an opportunity to further their cause they went for it. He knew well what this was about but he needed to quench their enthusiasm. He had no time to stay here, he even remembered what happened last time. They sent him a group of young girls to his quarters as a bribe. He was in the middle of courting Feng Liena so he didn’t think this would be appropriate.

‘Wonder what she would do if she found something like that out…’

He was a bit curious if the woman would be jealous or envious. It wasn’t strange to have multiple wives in this society so would she care if he had any flings? He on the other hand was an old fashioned modern type of man, that would rather have one warm woman than ten lukewarm ones.

“Stop, let me speak.”

Everyone quieted down after the white-haired man raised his hand while speaking out.

“I don’t need any more servants and I don’t need any disciples.”

“I also really don’t have the time so I’ll be leaving.”

He started floating up to the people’s dismay. They knew that they couldn’t keep this person here but they just had to try. They kept their eyes on his magnificent form almost as if they were hoping to get a cultivation boost from it.

He then vanished from their sight, almost like a blur as he took off into the deeper parts of the forest. Everyone from the Tribe was saddened that they couldn’t real him in.

“What a shame… if he took one of our girls as a concubine no one could go against this village.”

“Or if he took one of our boys as a disciple, we would be the greatest tribe!”

The people chatted it up almost forgetting about the charred Dark Palm sect people. The same that were still out cold and they would probably take a few hours to get over their shocking experience. The only reasonable person was the Tribe Chief that immediately ordered his people to get some rope and tie up the evil cultivators. They might have been crippled but that didn’t mean that they couldn’t escape into the woods.

Zhang Dong had moved forward into the forest but he had seen something odd. While passing the village from the top he noticed his name being mentioned on some signs. After further investigation, he figured out what it was.

The bathhouse he previously used had his name added before it. There was something about it being a secret ground for cultivation. He could feel some residual Qi in the water that was probably left by him when he cultivated for the first time. He had caused lightning to descend from the clouds which was enough to make this a desired spot for cultivation for these Qi condensation tribe people.

“I should sue them for copyright infringement!”

He flew away but he didn’t realize how far his presence here had changed the place. The secret cultivation ground was just one thing. The Tribe even hosted sightseeing tours. They took people to where he fought the tentacle faced monster and told the tales of his gallant adventures. They also let people stay at the building he lived for those weeks at exorbitant prices.

His mind was preoccupied with the strange Tribe that was going crazy for him so he didn’t notice that he had arrived at the place that started it all. He came to a halt and saw the damaged tree stump from where the miniature version of cthulhu sprung from.

“Hey... this brings me back…”

He moved towards that leftover stump, it was in bad shape as the monster burst from under it, destroying most of the tree in the process. He was still wondering if this was some kind of tutorial area and if the monster was a pre-planned encounter. He could have also been unlucky arriving at a bad time.

“This thing sure pulled a fast one me…”

He remembered running away in fear even though he was much stronger than the creature. He was inexperienced and unable to use his techniques to their full extent. It took the Tribe’s people getting in trouble for him to finally man up and face the creature. In the end he just overpowered it with his powerful body and lightning.

While reminiscing about the past he realized that he had come far. He had managed to somehow bumble his way into a leader’s position. Going from a shut-in to a sect leader which was comparable to kings from his old world.

He snapped out of it, this was no time to remember the good old days. He still needed to find a good location for his sect to set up shop. He looked to his system map while disgruntled as he didn’t expect to find anything worthwhile in the lowest of the low regions that he was in now.

“Hm?”

His eyes went wide as he noticed something out of place. There was some kind of signature here and it was right below him. He was standing right next to the tree and the open field that he was transported to at the start of his journey. Could this have something to do with it, was his question.

This was quite a strange signature as it didn’t show up normally. It looked like a giant black spot and it was right below him. The blackness spread throughout his system map. It made it seem as if something was blocking out the signal from reaching there.

He had to investigate, it was a highly unusual sight and he had reasons to believe that it had something to do with his arrival here.

“This looks sketchy…”

He didn’t like this, the spot below him wasn’t that far underground but even he couldn’t feel anything there when he used his spirit sense. If he didn’t have this graphical interface he would probably never have spotted this anomaly.

He steeled his resolve and dived down into the rocks below. At his level of power, he could force his way down the hard ground but at a slow pace. He burrowed his way while lighting the path with his golden aura, eyes glued to the map.

Zhang Dong could see that there was a naturally formed cavern leading to one of the blacked-out parts. He descended into it and burst through the wall. He came out in a large cave, the area lit up the moment he came through from his shiny aura.

There was nothing out of place with this corridor so he followed it towards his destination. The splashing of water echoed through this place as it was some kind of naturally formed underwater passageway. The further he went in the closer he got to the black spot on his map.

Finally, he arrived at his destination, the black spot in the area revealed itself to him. It was an out of place obsidian wall. He moved closer to it, it was clearly nothing that had formed naturally as it was way too smooth.

“A wall?”

He placed his palm on it, it was really polished and the light he was exuding was bouncing right off of it. It looked man-made as if someone placed or carved it here. This strange wall was clearly made of a different material than the ones in the corridor. It looked like hard obsidian.

He knocked on it with his knuckles and noticed that this material was very resistant. Normally a simple knock on some rocks from someone with his strength would have caused some cracking.

He decided to form a fist for his next test. He inserted a small amount of spiritual energy and punched out. The hit landed on the black wall and the whole place shook, the wind pressure alone from his hit caused the normal corridor to quake and tremble.

The obsidian wall stood without a scratch though, he felt like a normal person punching an iron wall. His hand was even trembling and he didn’t even leave a dent on it.

“What is this made of…”

He wondered if he should put all of his power into another punch but before he could do that the wall started lighting up. Some strange symbols appeared which glowed blue and a light shot out that enveloped his whole body.

‘Scanning in progress, please remain still, intruders will be eliminated.’

He heard a strange robotic voice call out to him. A small orb appeared out of the wall and started scanning him from top to bottom. He had activated some kind of mechanism, it talked about elimination if he was deemed an intruder. He could only put up his defensive bubble and hope that it wasn’t powerful enough to cause him harm while he waited.

Chapter 200

The strange device that came from the wall performed a full body scan on Matt. He tried blocking it out with his cultivator aura along with his barrier bubble but to no avail. The scan seemed to go through all of his defenses and he was unable to do anything about it. Soon he heard the robotic voice again as it was finishing up.

“Error...Subject number 80082...error…deceased…”

The strange light started flickering on and off, it was red in hue while saying the part about the subject number but then it changed to green.

“Error...Overseer identification number 6893, identified.”

“Welcome, Overseer. Have a nice day. ”

The light flickered out and the sphere object that was scanning him absorbed itself back into the wall as if it was never there. The walls started rumbling and a human-sized door appeared before him.

“Subject number 80082?... Overseer?”

He had no idea what the robotic voice was talking about but he was really curious about what was inside. The walls were robust and he didn’t think that he would be able to force his way out of this place if he got stuck. This made him a bit concerned and halted his progress inside.

“I know this is incredibly stupid, but…”

He knew the risks but for some reason, he didn’t feel like there would be something dangerous inside. He felt that the status of Overseer that this machine gave him would keep him safe. Why it was calling him that way was still unknown to him.

He made a step towards the wall and then another until he vanished into the door. The door closed itself after him as if it was never there in the first place.

Matt felt a certain lack of ground under him and he quickly used his floating ability. The whole place quickly lit up and he was greeted with a large spherical room with not much in it.

He appeared out of a random spot in the wall, these doors could probably be formed in any location.

The whole place looked like an abandoned hangar, the walls were made from that black substance that he couldn’t budge with his current power level.

The most interesting thing was right in the center, it looked like a floating cube and it was similar to the one he saw back in the secret ground. The cube was spinning around by itself while radiating faint light, even from here he could tell that this thing wasn’t simple.

“T-that’s… that’s an immortal grade item!”

The moment he got in here he could feel the massive power radiating off that small thing. How could something like this evade everyone’s detection was his question.

“It must be these walls…”

He looked at the inner walls of this spheric space. There were many inscriptions etched into them that were clearly working. This place was a large array and it was hiding this floating cube from the other people in this world. The question on his mind was why was this cube being hidden and what did it do.

“How many spirit points can I get from this thing if I absorb it… a hundred million? a billion?”

He had no idea how an immortal treasure would be counted by this system. This cube was clearly storing a lot of energy inside of it and it seemed to be powering this whole place.

There was also another question on his mind, will the person that this thing belongs to notice if he just took it. Also, does this place have something to do with him being transported to this world?

He strained his eyes and looked at the intricate etchings on the walls. He had some knowledge about teleportation gates and arrays from the secret ground. Maybe if he could decipher this formation he could come to some kind of conclusion.

“As I thought… it has some similarities to some of the teleportation arrays in those books but it’s many times more complex…”

He tried placing his palm on the black walls with the arrays, but his system wasn’t willing to analyze this so he had to give up on that possibility.

He started trembling at his discovery, this meant a lot. He came to the realization that someone or something had yanked him from his original world and placed him here. This grand teleportation formation was directly over the spot he appeared here over two years ago, this was too much of a coincidence.

He tried theorizing about the point of this all. He had somehow placed the strangeness of being brought over to a xianxia world to the back of his head. He attributed it to being some kind of game and his Tranquil mind had made him not worry.

Now from this evidence, he believed that it wasn’t a game. He started thinking that his own world, his home was out there and he could perhaps go back. He thought to his family members that he left and to the time he had spent there.

‘Do they think I’m dead? What happened to my original body? What is this system anyway?’

He had a myriad of questions now, ones that couldn’t be easily answered. He felt like his original body might have remained in his old world. His soul might have been taken here and placed into this Zhang Dong that might have actually been a real person before. The possibility of this being a created world by some higher being was also out there.

He decided to move towards the cube that was floating around and radiating massive amounts of Qi. Maybe if he examined it with his system he could come up with something. He focused on it and looked for an answer, to his surprise his identification skill wasn’t able to identify this item. Even more, he was getting a jumbled mess of characters over this particular cube.

For some reason he felt drawn to it, he moved his hand towards it with his index finger outstretched. The moment his finger was one centimeter away from the floating object a tiny spark of energy flickered. His body came to a halt and he felt like he was deep under the ocean. His ears started ringing and he was close to passing out.

“Ugh…”

He couldn’t pull his finger away instead, his body jolted forward and grasped the whole floating cube which made it exude more energy. This energy was going directly into him, he was lighting up like a Christmas tree, glowing in bright white. Matt felt his bones rattling and his teeth gnashing as a massive amount of pure energy was pushed into him.

Just as his body felt like it would crumble under the pressure something occurred. The massive force was somehow redirected towards his dantian. Something in there started absorbing the enormous energy wave that the cube was trying to inject into his body as if trying to destroy him.

The whole place went dark and the floating cube that was giving out copious amounts of light shattered into many tiny pieces while being grasped by him. Matt himself fell down and landed on the cold hard ground which was composed of the obsidian material.

“Hey, you okay there, friend?”

Matt slowly opened up his eyes, he felt like he was run over by a truck. To his surprise someone was now talking to him, his vision was blurry but he could make out an outline of a figure.If it was a man or a woman he didn’t know, the voices also switched between low and high pitched.

“I don’t have much time, so listen well.”

“Don’t worry, the overseers won’t notice you just yet, I’ll be sure to block the signal.”

“I need your help.”

“You must gather more ……..c….s ...so...ble….to….bzzzzz”

Before his vision could focus the person talking to his fizzled out of existence. It felt like he was talking to him through a really bad microphone with a lot of static and he couldn’t make out the last part of the massage at all.

He slowly stood up, he didn’t know who that person was or where the energy that he was somehow absorbing went. His system wasn’t showing any more spirit points than he had. He looked all over the place but he was now in total darkness.

He infused some energy into his body to produce a light source. From what he could make out the cube had shattered into dust, there was nothing left. It was clearly the power source for this place but now it was gone, he feared that he would be stuck in here as he probably couldn’t break the walls.

“Damn what was that?... was that some kind of hologram?”

He had more unanswered questions now, why did he get drawn into grabbing that cube. The moment he got closer he felt like he should touch it. He didn’t even get the opportunity to put on some gloves.

Then there was the strange voice that called out to him, it sounded like a man but he wasn’t sure. He wanted him to get him something, but he wasn’t sure what. This all started after the secret ground encounter and after he absorbed the cube that was there.

'Does it have something to do with these cubes?’

He wasn’t sure if he could trust that person. Wherever that energy went it wasn’t him, there might be something stuck in his dantian getting nourished by it. His mind made him think about a certain movie about aliens, he really didn’t want to end up with someone bursting out of his dantian.

He tried scanning his body, looking into all of his parts even into his nascent soul but he couldn’t find anything. The only thing he had to go off of were these energy cubes.

‘Does that mean there are other people like me here? Or there might have come here before me…’

He racked his brain about the purpose of spiriting people away to xianxia styled worlds but he couldn’t think about anything worthwhile. The more important thing was getting out of here. He hovered over to the spot he came from and managed to find it thanks to his good memory.

He placed his palm on the hard surface and gave it a good few knocks to no avail. He then kicked it with all his might and to his surprise, there was some kind of reaction as the intricate array symbols started glowing.

He thought for a second and then placed his hand on the surface. He then started infusing the wall with his own spiritual energy. After a certain point, the door sprung open and he quickly jumped outside into the previous corridor. The whole thing was lacking a power source but was still in working condition. He had enough juice to at least make this part of the structure move and let him out.

‘I guess it still sees me as this overseer thing?’

He was now back outside. He had gone in with a lot of questions and came out with even more. This whole expedition had proved to be a big fat failure. He didn’t find a place for his sect to stay as and now he was having an existential crisis about being played with by some kind of higher being.

He was almost ready to take off and return home but then he felt something. He had to pull up his map once more to examine it. After the cube was gone the whole area became visible. Right below him was another surprise, there was a large spiritual vein buried deep underground and it was exuding copious amounts of spiritual energy.

He put two and two together and came to the conclusion that this device was probably hiding this source of spiritual energy. The cube might not have even been the source of energy, it was probably siphoning it from the spirit vein.

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh, he had decided to bring his sect over here. One of the reasons was this newly discovered vein the other was that he didn’t want others to discover this teleportation array. He needed to examine it further and with his sect on top of it, it would be a lot easier.

Chapter 201

The Spirit veins were something like natural spirit energy generators. It was something like natural geothermal energy that was produced by the planet they were in. These exposed veins could be used by the cultivators as fuel for their cultivation, the closer they were to them the more energy they could absorb into themselves and speed up their progress.

Just like Zhang Dong was able to use stormy weather to hasten his progress, so could others use these spirit veins. Just that these were far more universal and didn’t require any specialized techniques. The vein placed here wasn’t the largest, maybe the floating cube had sapped it of its energy for all these years it was buried here.

The good thing about these naturally occurring treasure areas was that they recharged themselves over time. This was actually something good as the sect could set up their spiritual formations now and block other sects from finding this place. If those three sects noticed that the United Element sect found a better location for cultivation then they had, they would surely come asking for trouble.

‘Yeah, I found something, bring more people we need some architects. I think I found the new location for our sect.’

Matt ended his communication with Zhang Kuo while outside of the hole. He knew that they could somehow hide this place from prying eyes but that didn’t mean that they would be suspicious of them. The whole act of placing your sect in the lowest of low areas was already really sketchy. He didn’t think that the other three sects would act before gathering more evidence though, they just needed to somehow falsify it.

If they managed to make it seem like there was a smaller pocket of spirit metals or spirit herbs here instead of a spirit vein then the other sect would probably leave them alone.

‘Hm, can I somehow redirect the spiritual energy from this spirit vein into the Dimensional Regalia, with its aura masking traits I should be able to hide everything.’

His first thought was to use the pocket dimension. On the outside, they would look like a small sect while on the inside they would prosper into a mighty hidden titan. He went back to his library to find the right array formations for the job. He flew up into the sky and was already mapping the whole area out, his map feature was quite handy in situations like this.

‘This planet is as huge as the sun but I remain in this little part of it… it’s kind of funny…’

He thought back to the life he was living. His life here wasn’t very adventurous, he had remained in the vicinity of a couple of cities he knew and never left. His clan kept him from moving, the only freedom he ever had was when he worked as his demon hunter persona and even then he didn’t really wander into the large sect territories.

He was even slowly wondering why he was even working this hard. Wouldn’t it be okay if he just built the sect anywhere and relaxed, he just needed to pay some spirit stones to the other sects from time to time. Not like they would come to murder him unless they found out that they all had immortal level skills. Then he thought to all of the people that were depending on him and smiled, he couldn’t just abandon them.

‘Well, might as well do a good job while I’m at it.’

He pumped himself up, he could create the best and strongest sect that this world had ever seen. He was already in the nascent soul realm so he had enough time to do it meticulously. He went back to examining the surroundings until some of his sect members arrived. It was Zhang Kuo and with him were a couple of unknown elders from the other sects that he didn’t have the opportunity to talk too. With them was also Zhang Zi piloting the large flying ship that was hovering above the tall trees.

“Sect leader we are here!”

They all bowed to him and jumped down to the ground. They looked around the forest area and noticed some of the weak beasts scattering out of the way to hide themselves. They were curious why the sect master wanted this to be the new location.

“Good, let me show you something.”

The people here were mostly in foundation establishment but all of them stuck through till the end so they could be trusted. He brought them down to the hole that he had dug up. The spirit vein was in a separate cave of its own, the walls were all crystallized and these crystals were close to spirit stones but not quite.

Everyone’s eyes opened wide with surprise, this was truly a magnificent spot to set-up their sec.

“As you can see, this is a spiritual vein, it’s a bit drained now but it should recover within a year.”

“We must secure it, set up formations to block out the spiritual energy from leaking out.”

Zhang Dong said what he thought about the situation. About how he wanted to hide this from the sects and how the Dimensional Regalia treasure would be used. He even wanted to design a separate teleportation gate and place it into his treasure. This way people wouldn’t have to constantly use the small medallion as an entrance. This would also hide its true form and whereabouts from any potential spies.

The whole sect became busy overnight, the most concerned people were the tribesmen. The small pickup for the Dark Palm sect turned into a large event as they started seeing more and more people from the United Elements sect coming to their village.
It didn’t take long for them to notice that they were building something in the forest. They were concerned at first but they had trust in Zhang Dong and that he wouldn’t hurt them. The days started passing and the word that this sect would be using their forest as their main base of operations was brought to light. The tribe members were ecstatic about this news, they were even allowed to stay here.

The whole building process would take a while but Matt was mostly concerned about keeping the spiritual vein hidden for now. Unless a spy appeared then it would be safe. This is also why he decided to stay in person, he would use his map feature to catch any people unrelated to his sect in the area. His spiritual sense filled the locations around the spot that the new sect was being built.

This was quite a boring task as he could only sit around and stare. His people were mostly finished with setting up the smaller formations that would block out the spiritual energy from seeping away. The buildings started to slowly take shape, the first thing going into place would be the walls around the center area.

He was going to place a giant castle right in the middle of the spirit vein. It would have an angular hip roof at the top with the Sects name written out on a flag. There would be six large pagodas all around it that would house some of the stronger elders from his side. He wasn’t sure what he wanted to place into the courtyard just yet, probably some gardens and maybe a place for people to train in.

This grand structure would be nothing but a distraction though, the real sect would be right in the immortal grade treasure that he had found so long ago. He didn’t think killing one demonic cultivator would let him discover such a useful treasure but he was apparently a lucky man.

This center castle would be the most important structure, but not like it would be the only one. There would be smaller yet similar buildings spread out throughout the forest area that would need to be cut down. They would be placed in strategic locations in a decagonal fashion around it. More walls would be placed between those Chinese styled buildings to complete this large defensive fortress.

On the inside, there would be more buildings like apothecaries, training areas, smithing shops that would aid the disciples on their journey into the future. Matt really wanted to place his sect on some large mountain peaks but there just weren’t any at this geographical location and he wasn’t quite powerful enough to raise giant mountains from the ground to carry them over here.

While he was overseeing the construction he noticed some people sneaking around. There have actually been a couple of spies that he had apprehended during the weeks of this construction. The three sects might have looked uninterested but they still sent cultivators over to snoop about. It started with foundation establishment cultivators trying to peek then evolved into core formation elders trying to glide through the forest on their flying blades.

He had promptly taken care of them, he knew well that the sects wouldn’t actually admit that these people were from their side. Such was the life of a spy if they got caught there would be no rescue party coming. Thanks to this he was free to relocate them into the ‘free labor’ initiative movement, maybe he would release them after his sect got powerful enough to not fear the three larger ones surrounding them. He still knew that they were just following orders; this wasn’t something he would want to punish people for.

This day was a bit different though as the people snooping were far too weak.

‘Qi condensation?’

He raised his eyebrow while continuing to hover above the construction site in a lotus position. He used his spiritual sense to gather more information. There were two people coming and they were still quite far away, if they moved too close then the United Element sect guards that were also placed around the area would find them out.

‘It’s those two kids?’

The ‘spies’ were actually just two youths from the Tatar Tribe. It was the silkypants that he had met over two years ago and the youth that he saved while flying towards civilization. The two were now moving in unison towards the construction. This location wasn’t that far away from their village so they could probably reach it within the day.

‘Did someone fall asleep on the job back at the village?’

He had told Zhang Kuo to make sure that the villagers wouldn’t go towards their sect's new location. Even if the possibility was low, they could be captured by the enemy sects and forced to cough up some intel if they wandered in too deep. He gave out a sigh and used his communication jade to call his retainer. He couldn’t really leave his spot and this wasn’t something a sect leader should be dealing with.

In a matter of minutes, there were two cultivators at their location. The youths were scared out of their wits and tried apologizing, from what he could tell the reason they wandered into the forest was to join the sect. They were promptly removed from the premises by the two sect members that consisted of one Feng Clan member and one Huo clan member.

‘They wanted to join the sect?’

He thought to himself. It was a bit too soon for that but in the future, he wanted to expand. He needed a batch of fresh recruits that were around the land. Some of the sects were strenuous with this process making the new disciples go through rigorous tests. Some used connections with rich families to procure favor while accepting their youths into their midst.

He didn’t really want people getting into his sect just by association, the three main clans were an exception as they were considered the founding members. He moved his gaze back to the people below as he went back to watching the progress. If you didn’t count the spies from the other sects the days went by peacefully. They were on the right path but as always he and his people needed time and he hoped that this time around they would have enough on their side.

Chapter 202

Matt was sitting in a new-made room. The whole sect was busy at work with constructing the new stronghold and he was stuck here with them. He had spent a couple of months hovering in the clouds and watching for any potential spies or people that could cause trouble. The life of the sect leader was proving to be somewhat boring.

His two friends weren’t here either. Huo Qiang was patrolling the borders and Feng Liena was moving between the lands and guarding their resource convoys. He, as the strongest of their cultivators, was defending the Dimensional Regalia along with the new location. There was nothing interesting to keep him busy though.

He couldn’t really cultivate as they needed him to keep watch. There was no radio, no TV, and the holograms that he made were back at the old Zhang headquarters. If they were here he could at least listen to some news and laugh at the stern presentation.

‘This sucks… how much longer will this take?’

They had managed to prepare a makeshift room for him. He had a quill in his hand and there was a large canvas on the wall. He was using it to redraw the area around them while using the system map as a reference.

He did find some mineral pockets deep underground along with some other resources. They could use them to bolster their depleted stock as after the war there wasn’t much left. Luckily the Feng Clan and Huo Clan weren’t hit that hard, they still had all of their stock.

After Huo Qiang’s father discovered that his son was using an immortal grade technique, he quickly changed his tune. He was all in from that point, Qiang even asked Zhang Dong if he would permit him to let his father use the same cultivation technique as him. He just shrugged and gave him the okay, he had given Qiang that as a present and he could do with it as he pleased.

The idea of drawing the map came to him as a means to end this boredom. He was also working on copying down some cultivation techniques for the future sect disciples. He had even decided on the color grading of the robes. With the help of some sect members that were not as color blind as he was.

At first, he wanted to separate everyone into a different element. Red for fire, blue for water, and so on. This would be a bit jarring as there were quite a few elements and it would just be too bothersome.

First, the disciples would start out in plain gray robes. These would be what every outer sect disciple would get. Then the inner sect disciples would get blue robes and the core disciples violet as it was apparently a color of nobility and royals. He and the other two grand elders were free to choose their own robes.

The elders would have the same color coding but they would have added symbols to their robes that would distinguish them. There would be other markings if the person was part of another inner group like their alchemist association that still needed to be made. Everyone would also have the character for their sect sewn into the back of the robe. This would let everyone else distinguish them from the masses.

They needed to house various types of learning halls to produce specialists in professions. They needed pill makers, weaponsmiths, beast tamers, and of course a martial hall to house the best fighters.

They had a long way to go as they were just setting up the basic scaffolding. It would probably take at least a year till this actually started to look like something. Luckily he didn’t have to lift a finger during all of this. His main purpose was to act as a deterrent against the other sects but this also meant that he needed to remain here.

‘And done…’

With the last stroke of his quill he had finished the large map of the area that he was responsible for. There were many large cities that housed millions of people in them. This world was truly gigantic, it was even bigger than his previous home planet.

It took about two days to make a round trip around his old planet. When he was at core formation his flight speed was comparable to a jet plane and he still needed a day to fly between some cities and sometimes longer.

He was now the proud owner of this land. There were many millions of people living here, most of them scared as a new force had taken over. To them there wouldn’t be much of a change, from one tyrant to another was their consensus. No one thought that the other large sects would be any different from the others. Overbearing and quick to anger if face was being tarnished was the way people lived in this world.

Matt was trying to defend himself against this way of thinking but even he saw that it was hard to make these people change. Even he knew that unless you had the biggest fist around, no one would listen to you. He didn’t want to rule with it though, he would rather have everyone work together in a more coherent way.

‘Living as one big happy family is all nice and fine, but…’

He still would need to use his fists. The sect was weak and they had many eyes looking at them. Looking for them to fail, ready to pounce at an opportunity. He would still need to act as a powerful and all-knowing leader. Maybe if he had ten more nascent soul elders on his side he would be able to relax. Though controlling so many powerful individuals might cause some internal disputes.

The finished map would be placed in the new meeting room. It would act as a good prop for further plans. He decided to take a stroll through the new area, outside he could see his sect members working together. All of the three main clans were here, everyone working diligently new relationships created day by day which made him happy.
He looked to the side as his senses picked something up. It was one of their large transports bringing over more building materials from the other clans. This one arrived from the Huo Clan. He perked up a bit as he felt a familiar person coming with this convoy, it was Feng Liena acting as the guard.

She would be free for a couple of days now as everything needed to be unpacked. With her around, he could probably take a bit of a breather as she also was a nascent soul master with a powerful spiritual sense.

He looked at his reflection in the mirror while slightly nervous. Previously he never did care about his outer appearance, now he was checking out if his white robe didn’t have any wrinkles in it. He even raised his armpit to see if he wasn’t sweaty. Luckily his body had evolved so much that there wasn’t really any foul odor produced by it.

“Hello, how have you been?”

“Eyyy, how you doin?”

“Junior Sister, you’re looking as lovely as ever…”

He practiced in front of the mirror, his face looked tense, and the way he smiled looked forced at best. It was really hard for an unsocial person like him to actually talk to women. There wasn’t really anyone that he could ask for advice and most of them would probably just say that he should propose.

Dating as a concept wasn’t really a thing in this world. People got together with the sole purpose of forming family ties or making kids. There were relationships with love involved but most of the time it was arranged by your elders. Unless your standing was high, the privilege of choosing a partner wasn’t your own.

He wanted to punch the mirror in front of him as he looked like an idiot. The amounts of cringe coming out of his mouth were over the charts. He finally decided to leave his temporary room. His destination was the large flying ship that had precious cargo on it.

He went out instead of flying as the ship that had already landed. He had a bit of stage fright but he had gone on some mini-dates with Feng Liena a couple of times before. They had some tea with each other while discussing the sect's current predicament.

When exiting his room he garnered some attention from the other sect members that gave him the usual salute. He just nodded at them and continued forward, the guards by his new room followed right after him as they were ordered to tend to his needs. This didn’t help with his predicament as it only meant that there were more eyes on him.

He continued forward, whenever someone saw him they stopped in their tracks to bow. Even if they were performing some difficult task they would take some time to show their respect. He even saw some people dropping a massive block made from solid rock just bow with appreciation.

He took his time, not really being in any hurry. The days felt slow as he had to be here guarding the construction site. Taking a little stroll through the new land was one of the things that could make time pass a bit faster.

The sect workers were busy with flattening the land and clearing out all the trees. This was also the main reason why this was taking so long. They had to remove their roots along with the trunks. The only good thing about this task, they were getting a lot of free construction materials. The trees here weren’t of such good quality so they would probably be mostly used as timber or for furniture. They could also be used for things like shacks that didn’t need to be too sturdy.

The rapid deforestation caused a lot of friction with the beasts living here. They were all lower-level beasts so they didn’t pose a threat. By his order, they were to be captured for future beast taming training.

He came out of the corner and finally saw their ship. It previously had the Feng Clan flag hanging from it but now it had changed to the United Element sects characters. He didn’t hide his presence at all so people probably noticed that he was already approaching.

Feng Liena wasn’t the only person coming. To his surprise, his two disciples were also here, with them was Liena’s younger sister Nuana. She was hanging around Zhang Liu’s arm like a tick while the youth looked uncomfortable. His sister Zhang Xue was walking while being accompanied by Huo Kong, Huo Qiang’s most prominent son.

There were also various other members from the other clans from the junior generation tagging along. They had become bored with staying at the Zhang Clan sanctuary and asked Feng Liena to take them along on her escort mission. It was a lot more interesting to fly on a large ship and visit other places than being cooped up in one place. They had quickly gathered together and most of these people were the youths that had gone to the Dao Festival together. Matt even saw one of the youths being surrounded by at least ten Gyarus , he looked like he would be having a similar fate to his grandpa.

This made things a bit more awkward but he didn’t falter while walking forward. He wanted to try smiling in front of the arrivals to greet them but he came out stone-faced as always. The moment the people saw his white-robed form coming their way they all stopped in their tracks. This was their sect leader that was coming to greet them, they all felt honored.

“Greeting sect leader!”

Before he could welcome them they called out, giving him the usual show of respect. He glanced at some of the people, some were being more respectful than the others. His two disciples seemed glad that he was here and he could tell that they wanted to chat with him. His gaze was glued to the person that was walking in the front, his so-called ‘girlfriend’ Feng Liena.

“Ah, greeting to you all and to you to junior sister.”

He made sure to single her out from the group a little smile appearing on his face.

Feng Liena nodded slightly while covering her face with a fan. The people that came with her looked between the two, they had noticed that something was going on. The person most interested in this exchange was the one hanging on by Zhang Liu’s arm.

Chapter 203

Feng Nuana was a peculiar person. She was still hung up about the ‘ancient texts’ of her clan. Her older sister had come back with a claim that they weren’t accurate and that the clan women should follow their own hearts. She on the other hand was a firm believer that this was untrue and the texts were holy scriptures.

This was also why she was clinging to Zhang Dong’s disciple so much. Through the texts, she had deemed him worthy of being her partner.

She was looking at her sister blushing slightly while covering the lower half of her face with a fan. She looked to the reason why she was doing this and saw Zhang Dong standing there. The man was quite handsome but she still preferred the more youthful looks of Zhang Liu’s.

She narrowed her eyes while looking at her sister moving over towards this white-haired man. That the two were growing their bond was an obvious thing, which would mean that this person in front of her would become her elder brother. Due to the secret texts not presenting any boundaries between others, she thought it would be natural to greet him. She would do it in quite the overblown way though.

Feng Nuana stopped clinging to Liu’s arm and skipped forward. She appeared next to her sister that was busy hiding her bashfulness. Zhang Dong had noticed her approach but not like he would stop the little sister of his love interest. He also just thought that she would do the usual bow of appreciation.

To his bafflement, the girl just quickly jumped out and gave him a big hug. He was on the taller side at 190 cm of height so she had her face planted in his abs. He was quite surprised by the sudden act of affection by the girl he only knew as ‘that girl that always clings to Zhang Liu’

“Elder brother, little Nuana is happy to see you~”

“Uh…”

He stared at the girl that was wiggling up against him and then looked to her older sister. He could see a vein appearing on her forehead while her eyebrows inclined.

The junior members that were standing behind the whole scene were dumbfounded by the act of affection. Was the sect leader already this close to the Feng Matriarch and her younger sister that they were okay with hugging each other?

No one knew what to do, was the girl going out of line and offending the new sect leader? Normally people in such high positions were quite pedantic about their face. What if he decided to punish her and the good relationship built with the Feng Clan would cease to exist.

The first one to break the silence was Feng Liena. The fan was used to block out her rage but she was quite angry about what her little sister did. Not because he was being rude towards the sect leader or that it could cause some misunderstandings. No, she was mad that her sibling had managed to hug the person she admired before she could. She was even rubbing her face all over his belly, this was something that she was supposed to do!

“Nuana, get away from Senior Brother Dong this instance! What do you think you are doing?”

“No, I don’t wanna! Save me elder brother, big sis is being a meany!”

What ensued was a scene of the nascent soul elder trying to peel away her younger sister from the sect leader. The smaller girl was clinging to him hard though, just as Zhang Liu had feared she did indeed have some dastardly clinging technique. Feng Liena even started pulling her by the legs which caused Nuana’s lower body to move up in the air. She continued clinging while her sister kept pulling, the other sect members just looked without doing anything as the sect leader was involved.

Zhang Dong didn’t know what to do either, it felt odd having one cute girl clinging to you, while another beautiful one was trying to pry her off you. Even if he liked the attention he knew that this couldn’t go on any further.

“You have quite the interesting little sister there, Junior Sister Liena…”

He finally spoke out and poked Nuana’s forehead with his index finger. The girl felt a strange force rushing through her body before going limp and losing all of her strength in her body. She was pulled backward by her older sister but the two were enveloped in a gentle golden aura. Feng Nuana was spun around and placed onto her feet, the moment of weakness subsided rapidly.

Zhang Dong moved over and gave the troublemaker a pat on the head before moving next to Feng Liena. She looked kind of angry at the whole predicament but he didn’t really want to cause a further scene. He also noticed that for some reason her Qi went into disarray when he gave the little sister a head pat. He could only think that she was mad that he dared to touch her little sister without consent.

“Ah, think we should head inside… the sect members are working diligently, I’ll be your guide.”

He laughed a bit to himself. The younger sister pouted a bit before moving back to clinging to Zhang Liu’s arm. The youth’s expression switched from confusion to defeat in a span of a few seconds as the small busty girl was back.

Everyone just nodded while Zhang Dong walked forward, they couldn’t decline the leader if he was going to show them around the new sect ground. Feng Liena remained half a step behind him while the rest followed in the back. Everyone was still thinking about their status so everyone lined up accordingly.

Zhang Dong peeked behind him, everyone was keeping their distance even Liena was lagging slightly behind. He noticed that she and Qiang kept doing this, they always remained half a step behind him. This was just a show of respect to their leader but he wanted to move past that. Have wished the two accept him as an equal and not like someone above them.

This prompted him to stop in his tracks while peeking behind himself. He made a little controlled maneuver and placed himself at the right next to the tanned beauty with the pink hair.

Feng Liena stopped momentarily as she found a certain white-haired man right next to her. He just smiled while nodding as he tried to indicate that it was okay to walk with him as an equal. The junior members in the back looked in with awe at the man before them as they knew what this kind of gesture meant.

Regretfully Matt wasn’t someone from this world so he didn’t realize what his little act caused. In this world allowing a woman to walk beside you was akin to declaring her as your lover. This was something he was slowly trying to go towards for but this was seen as quite the power move on his part.

The girls in the back were surprised by the boldness of this sect leader. The youths were just shocked by how nonchalantly he had done it, there was no hesitation, no fear. He just went for it and the lady next to him was looking quite glad.

‘Why is she blushing like a ripe tomato?’

‘Why is everyone looking at me like this?’

Matt was curious about the reactions of the people in the back. He just took a step back so that Feng Liena didn’t have to do this saving face nonsense and walk next to him. He didn’t make anything off it, it was just a simple gesture of good etiquette.

“Shall we?”

He asked, indicating that he wanted to move forward. Feng Liena’s heartbeat increased and he could hear it. The increased heartbeat caused him to think that she was having some kind of panic attack as it was highly irregular to behave this way. He stepped forward, he was a physician as well so he could probably give her a checkup if he just grasped her hand.

So he did. The people in the back and from all around opened their eyes widely. Her Sect master was so brazen, he just more or less asked for the woman to be his lover and now he was already moving ahead and asking her for marriage. To Matt, this gesture didn’t mean much, to the people here it meant that he was proposing. The people around them went wild, their eyes glued on the two as they hoped for a good reply.

‘The heart rate is a bit high but nothing out of the ordinary, think she is just nervous?’

‘Is she stressed out from having to guard the convoys?’

‘Maybe I should give her some time off?’

“I…”

He finally heard Feng Liena replying, she started stuttering at first but then she came to some kind of conclusion.

“I accept!”

“You accept?”

He replied.

“She accepted!”

Everyone shouted in the back with a lot of emotion that caught him off guard. Why were these people acting like weirdos again?

“Yes, I accept!”

She replied again while dropping her head down and turning to the side. He let go of her hand and they finally continued on with the tour of the base.

Unbeknownst to him, the people from his sect were on this like rabid dogs. Everyone sent out information with their jade tokens about the good news. The Zhang Clan Patriarch, now the United Element Sect leader, was going to wed Feng Liena, the Feng Clan Patriarch.

This was quite the scoop for their people and also a morale booster. This brought two powers together in a bond of unity and the Zhang side and the Feng side would be even closer than before.

This did bring the Huo Clan into a bit of a predicament as they didn’t have any bargaining chips from their side. Their biggest opportunity was in Huo Kong’s relationship with Zhang Dong’s female disciple. If they could get the two together, they could expand their influence in the Zhang Clan and get a better foothold.

When the news reached Zhang Jin that remained behind at the old Zhang Clan sanctuary he was ecstatic. He feared that something was wrong with his grandson as he was taking his time with courting. He himself would have already sealed the deal and a baby would be on its way.

He alerted his wives to the good news, they were to prepare a list of people to invite to the wedding. They could host it in a few months after more of the sect was set up as a large banquet. It would bolster the spirits of the people. Seeing two of their leaders as a couple could be used as a tool to further the sect agenda.

They could invite all of the scattered clans from all the other cities. Show off their power and also stabilize their position in their hearts. They could also send invitations to the three powerful sects that would probably send some envoys of goodwill.

Marriages like this were perfect for finding new business partners and allies. If all went well, they might bring someone from those three overbearing powers over to their side. There was also a chance of offending them in some way but they just needed to take the risk. They still had Zhang Dong’s master protecting them from the back.

“The sect leader is getting married? To senior Feng Liena?”

“We must prepare a big banquet!”

“A banquet? We should make a whole festival, invite everyone to show off our mighty sect!”

Zhang Jin’s wives started chuckling with each other while making plans. The festivities were going to be big, the problem was the lack of funds from their side. They were still a bit low on spirit stones due to the war and were in the recovering process.

“Don’t worry, just ask my grandson’s sworn brother for some aid, their clan should have the funds.”

Zhang Jin gave his advice. The Huo Clan section of the sect would probably be worried about not really being included in the whole wedding. But if they covered most of the expenses they would also gain some face.

Everything went in motion, the people were already picking out the venue and designing the best wedding dresses for Feng Liena to pick out from.

The man of the hour, Zhang Dong had no idea what he had started. He was just trying to be nice while slowly courting his target. He had never gone through this process so he wanted to slowly enjoy it while their emotions developed. Soon he would discover that today’s actions had brought something into motion that he couldn’t stop anymore.

Chapter 204

Matt felt that the gazes of his sect sisters and brothers were somehow different. Ever since the day he had received Feng Liena and her sister everyone was acting strangely. He had also received messages on his communication jade, people were congratulating him for something.

Whenever he passed by the female cultivators he could hear them whisper and when he left their eyesight they would start squealing like little kids. The male ones looked at him with some kind of devotion that wasn’t there before like he had accomplished something great. This felt different from the usual Patriarchal loyalty that he grew accustomed too, it felt a lot more crazed.

He just shrugged it off while thinking that they were just being goofy and that he just wasn’t accustomed to some of their hijinks.

There was also the problem with Feng Liena, she felt a lot more bashful than before. Then just one day after she came to the construction site one of her retainers stood in his way. She had informed him that going by tradition he wasn’t allowed to see her until the big day. What was this big day, or this tradition he had no idea? He just backed away thinking that it just might have been that day of the month and that it would be rude to ask about a detailed explanation.

He was a bit saddened by the lack of company so he had to take out his frustration in the best way possible. He would do this by beating up his disciples and their friends that had come begging for some pointers. There was nothing better than putting some snotty kids in place with a good whack.

“Your right side is wide open!”

‘THWACK’

Zhang Liu flew into the distance after he got tapped on the cheek by his master. Zhang Dong had lowered his cultivation base to fit his disciple’s but he was still someone at the nascent soul level. Just the fact that he had an evolved spiritual sense let him predict every attack that was thrown at him. He also had absorbed all the knowledge from that sacred ground. He was a master of hand to hand combat with both a high level of Qi and body refining.

“Don’t swing so wide!”

‘WHAP’

Zhang Xue tried attacking her master after he brother took a swan dive into some trees. Her master just leaned back while evading a lightning charged kick. The girl then got smacked on the back and tumbled into some bushes. The two were already at the foundation level so the impacts of their hardened bodies made small craters.

“Take this!”
Zhang Dong peeked to the side after defending himself against the two youths. A fist engulfed in fire was heading his way. He just lowered himself while redirecting his Qi into his forehead. The one punching was Huo Kong and the moment he delivered his punch was also the moment that he realised that he made a big mistake.

The youth flinched back while grasping his hand; it felt like he hit some kind of anvil made from precious metals.

“I took it, now what? Don’t only depend on the strength of your attacks, you’re leaving yourself wide open for a counter.”

He flicked the muscular youth’s forehead with his finger which caused him to fly away into the direction that Zhang Liu went. Both of them ended up on top of each other. More junior members were looking on from the sides, their eyes straining not to blink as they were worried that they would miss something in this lecture.

The only person left was Feng Liena’s little sister. The busty shrimp just went into a frenzy and started attacking Zhang Dong with all she had. She wasn’t weak for her age but he had realised that these youths weren’t that great at strategizing.

They mostly tried to overwhelm their opponents with superior techniques that quickly drained them of their Qi and stamina. You just needed to be good at evading and reading their movement patterns. After they tired themselves a bit you could move in for the kill.

Just like the rest she was sent flying into the distance. She landed with her posterior on Zhang Xue and the fight was over. Zhang Dong moved his hands behind his back and looked at the defeated youths, his head moving side to side as if he was disappointed.

“You all need to work on your basics.”

“What is the most important part of combat?”

“The power of your techniques? The sheer amount of Qi you can store in your body? Or maybe is it your cultivation realm?”

The defeated youths gathered up. His two disciples were a bit surprised that their Master was so chatty today. Most of the time he just implemented some knowledge into their brain and then went on his way. Somehow he felt more genuine today and more carrying.

The group of young cultivators looked at each other and started to think. They were mostly inclined to believe that power in general was the most important part. Having to battle someone of a higher realm was considered suicide by almost everyone. They all looked to the sect leader, ready to receive his wisdom, no one was even willing to make a prediction.

“Hah, I guess I’ll tell you then.”

“It’s your footwork.”

The youths were a bit surprised by the answer. There wasn’t even any footwork involved when nascent soul or core formation experts fought with each other in the air. So how could this answer be true?

“Footwork isn’t limited to the ground.”

“You can defeat your opponent just by feeling out how they move.”

He explained further. The place they were training in was on sand where their footprints were left behind.

“Look at the area I’m standing in and then take a look outside it”

The youths started examining it. The stretch of space that the sect leader was standing in wasn’t large but they could tell that he wasn’t moving in it all that much. Compared to that his opponents were flying all over the place, making big jumps and dangerous techniques that made them move around a lot.

“Make your opponents work against themselves, you can control the flow of the battle like so.”

Zhang Dong made it even more obvious by making his footprints glow in gold while the other ones had a blue hue. The youths could instantly see that his feet stayed in one general area while all the others were random and erratic without a sense to them.

“This does translate into aerial battle later, but it gets more difficult.”

“But we will take that step after you create your core. This shouldn’t be that hard for such promising youths.”

These juniors here were all the crème de la crème, they would be the future powerhouses of the sect. Reaching the core formation-level would probably be achievable in the coming years.

The group really perked up at the mention of a core being created. They were all from clans where a core formation expert was the pinnacle. So they felt quite good about themselves when the sect leader made a statement that it should be easy for them.

Matt laughed a bit after he saw their eyes go wide. These kids were still cultivators, the most important thing for them was to reach the next realm.

“Kong, Nuana, Liu, Xue and Tai, You five, in particular, show the most promise. The sect is expecting a lot from you but I also would like you not to rush with your cultivation. Building a good foundation is paramount, take your time and don’t rush it.”

“Yes, Sect Leader!”

“Yes, Master!”

“Little Nuana will make sure to make my elder brother proud!”

Everyone shifted their gaze to the short girl with the pink hair. She had continued calling the sect leader with ‘elder brother’ since the day she got here. They all knew that her older sister was getting married to Zhang Dong so she wasn’t doing anything wrong. Still, she was going a bit overboard and not really giving him face which caused his disciples to be a bit apprehensive about it.

“Ah yes… you don’t get discouraged. Everyone progresses at their own pace, when we are finished with building the sect ground you might have your opportunity.”

Zhang Dong turned away from his new ‘little sister’ and looked at the other junior members that were standing there. He gave them a little pep talk while hoping that they wouldn’t feel discouraged. He was clearly favoring his own disciples and the relatives of his friends that also were probably only stronger due to their wealthy upbringing.

He already knew that talent and potential could be measured by his system. This didn’t mean that someone’s progress was set in stone. This was only a number that would indicate natural progress. It didn’t really take into account how passionate and hard working the person was.

For instance, if you took a person with A grade potential and one with B grade potential. The one with the B could very well outperform the A grade if they were diligent in their work while the A grade was being lazy.

The rest of the kids just did the usual clasped fist bow while he nodded. If he was wearing one of those flowy robes he would probably turn around while swishing his sleeves. Alas, he was someone that was practical and he wore more form-fitting clothes.

“Well then, all of you line up and show me your punching form!”

“Yes, Sect Leader!”

“Yes, Master!”

“Little Nuana will do her best~”

He cringed a bit at the reply he got from his new little sis. She was acting similarly to how Feng Liena did the first time he met her. He knew the cause of it but at this point, he didn’t really want to argue about it. He still hadn’t seen those so-called ‘secret texts’ and he didn't really want to see them. He would have to somehow explain everything again which could make things worse.

The day continued while he tried giving the youths some pointers about fighting. He wasn’t sure if he was the greatest teacher but the kids seemed to like him. He even managed to drop his stone face and show a bit of a smile as he got more comfortable with being around people.

The day passed quickly, Matt had a lot of fun working on the kids and had to rethink his whole disciple situation. Maybe he could even give some lessons in the future martial hall when it got built.

‘Maybe I’m just that bored though…’

He shrugged and returned to his temporary quarters. He went back to sitting in the lotus position while scanning the area. He remembered reading about people in his position. They were rarely mentioned in the books. Always in the back and only appearing when the main protagonist needed saving. It was probably not very fun or interesting to read about some old man sitting in the room and scanning everything with his spiritual sense. Now he was this kind of expert, just sitting there and keeping watch.

His spiritual sense swept the whole area, no further spies had appeared since he took out the core formation ones. The other sects had probably given up after they got reports of him being here. He wasn’t worried about the secrets leaking out as even after months of being here there was no retaliation.

The calm days continued, Feng Liena finally flew away with the ship without telling her farewells. His disciples remained here along with their friends as he had started giving them pointers from time to time. The sect continued to grow and his workforce became more diligent with each day. This all culminated in one faithful day when his grandfather arrived.

He was awfully chipper as he arrived on a flying sword that he had previously made for him. The truth finally came out, the amounts of sweat forming on his forehead made it look as if he had just taken a bath after he got the ‘good news’

“Huh? I’m getting married?”

Chapter 205

Matt was minding his own business, just cultivating slightly while watching over the sect that he was responsible for. It looked like it was going to be another boring day as the rest as it continued. Most of the protective formations were already set up in place. They only needed to power them with the help of some treasures and then Zhang Dong could probably take a break.

While he was thinking about the coming days and what he would do when this whole grand defensive array was fully operational he spotted someone coming this way. It was a core formation expert that he knew. Surprisingly he was coming alone and he was on a flying sword and not on a flying ship.

‘You don’t see gramps moving much without some cute maids, was he in a rush or something?’

Matt already gave up on this man. He knew that his libido was unstoppable and he would probably die while being embraced by some kind of womanly figure. He only wished that his many relatives would stop sending him letters. They always tried to either offer him a concubine or someone as a disciple.

‘Is this how a lottery winner feels like?’

He wasn’t sure why his grandfather was coming here unannounced but he would at least say his greeting. He wouldn’t have to leave his room though as the old man was apparently flying right to him. He just waited for his arrival while scanning the area for anything suspicious.

It didn’t take long for Zhang Jin to come bursting through the entrance. The wooden doors almost flew out of their hinges after the old man made an entrance.

“There is my favorite Grandson!”

“Yeah, hi gramps. Try not to destroy the door, someone will have to repair them.”

He looked at Zhang Jin, the old man felt quite chipper. Did he perhaps get married again or something?

“This is truly a grand occasion Dong’er, you must make a toast with your Grandfather!”

Zhang Jin moved his hand out that had his spatial ring on it and produced a large bottle of spirit alcohol. It was an aged spirit from his personal stash that he only brought out on special occasions.

‘Huh? Is he really getting married?’

‘Instead of a harem protagonist, he is probably a hentai protagonist instead…’

He would oblige this old man. He didn’t care if he married another thousand women, if one of them stabbed him in the neck while he was sleeping it would be on him. Still, it would probably be best to ask about the joyous occasion, maybe someone else was getting married.

“What ‘grand occasion’ are you talking about here? Did one of your wives have triplets or something?”

He asked while Zhang Jin was pouring the alcohol into some drinking cups.

“Hah, Dong’er you sure like to joke around, I’m talking about your marriage.”

“You made your grandfather worry, you were taking so long.”

“But yes the first time is always the most difficult one, I remember my first proposal, my knees were all shaking and I was so young back then… that reminds me of the time when I...”

The old man started rambling about the good old days while Matt stood like a statue. Did he mishear, he was getting married? Did he miss a memo or something?

“Wait...Gramps hold on there… who is getting married?”

“Stop fooling around Dong’er, you of course, to Feng Liena, I came to congratulate you and decide on the guests.”

Zhang Dong received a strong smack to the shoulder that didn’t make him budge one bit as he was in a state of shock. He started thinking back to when this could have happened, when did he get married. Then it dawned on him, people started acting strangely the day he received Feng Liena that one day. He remembered touching her hand and moving to her side, he also remembered her blurring out that she accepted something.

‘Was it then?... Was that considered proposing?’

His whole face went white with horror. He was getting married and apparently the date of the wedding ceremony might already be set in stone. He only wanted to get to know Feng Liena a bit better and treat her like an equal and this was the result.

“Why are you being so quiet Dong’er? Here drink!”

He looked at the filled cup in his hand and took a swig. Due to his high cultivation alcohol like this didn’t really work and cause him to get drunk. Though he would really like to drink his woes away right now. He grabbed the whole bottle that Zhang Jin brought over and started chugging, soon enough there was nothing left and he still felt like his heart would pop out of his chest.

“Hey, leave some for your Grandfather! You’re lucky that I brought moreover!”

The two continued drinking but Matt didn’t feel like talking about the wedding ceremony and told Zhang Jin to take care of it.

After his grandfather left he flopped onto his back and started staring at the wooden ceiling of his temporary residence. He had somehow proposed and the woman said yes. Normally this would be a good thing as this confirmed the woman’s emotions as she was willing to marry him. He was still someone from modern earth though, he didn’t feel like he knew Feng Liena that well.

The most time that they had spent with each other was during the sacred ground. Even then he only got glimpses of her true character as she was acting with those secret texts in mind. Only in the end she started behaving like a normal person.

‘Should I break it off?’

This was one of the options. If he did this now though the relationship that he had built up with the Feng Clan would cease. The women from that clan would probably never forgive him if he did such a thing to their Matriarch. This could even split the whole sect into parts, maybe even the Huo Clan would follow suit and feel like he couldn’t be trusted.

Matt wasn’t someone that believed in love at first sight. He was more inclined to believe that love would blossom slowly after you got to know a person better. That’s why he felt that unless he lived with someone for a prolonged time he wouldn’t really know if they meshed together.

There was no such thing in this world though. It was straight to marriage and then you were supposed to pop out children. This also brought another thing out into the open, was he supposed to father children now?

He felt like packing up and fleeing into the deep mountains. He already had trouble interacting with teenagers like his disciples. How was he supposed to be a fatherly figure to a toddler? He didn’t feel like he would be a good dad. As a socially awkward person that grew up in the modern world, he didn’t even think something like this was an option.

Still, he couldn’t abandon his people. He felt like he had done enough fleeing from his problems in one lifetime. It wasn’t as if he disliked Feng Liena and couldn’t see himself marrying her in the future. This situation only hastened things a bit.

He was already past his thirties which even in his original world was considered old to form a family. He was getting a beautiful wife that liked him and not like he disliked her in any shape or form.

‘This might not be that bad…’

He rolled to his side while analyzing the situation. If he wanted to keep the good relations between his clan and the Feng clan he needed to go through this. The woman he was marrying was also a nice person that he didn’t mind being in the company of.

‘...’

He gulped while calming himself down. The thoughts of running away had left his mind and got replaced by something else. He started imagining himself with a child on his shoulder and Feng Liena walking next to him. Hand in hand, just walking through a grassy field.

‘I think I’m getting ahead of myself here…’

He rose up to his feet as he made a decision. He would go through with this, he had already taken a swan dive headfirst. He might as well make a nice splash at the end. Another problem arose though, he didn’t know how people operated in this world when it came to getting married. Asking his grandfather about it wouldn’t be appropriate so he needed another opinion.

He grabbed his communication jade and sent out a message to one of his retainers, his female one that was Zhang Ya.

“How may I be of service, Sect Leader?”

She bowed in while asking, she was rarely called in by Zhang Dong as he mostly used the more analytic Zhang Kuo. She understood soon after she heard the question which brought a tiny smile on her face.

“Uh, how do wedding ceremonies work?”

The woman covered her mouth a bit as the Sect’s leader's facial expression was kind of bashful. She kept it in as she went through the ceremony and what was required from the groom and the bride. Surprisingly the whole ceremony was really similar to western-style weddings.

The groom wasn’t allowed to see the bride until the day of the wedding. They needed to send out invitations to the people they wanted and the bride would wear an expensive dress. Instead of it being white though it was supposed to be red.

The whole banquet would be set up in a red theme, this color was associated with success, loyalty, honor, fertility, and love. You also could insert some gold colors for wealth, from what Zhang Ya was saying his wedding robe would probably mostly consist of that color scheme.

‘I need to make the wedding rings…’

The traditional wedding bands or rings came into play as well. The wedding night was also a staple of the tradition. This was something that he would be a bit stressed out about, luckily he was someone with some experience so he was even willing to be the lead in that regard.

“That’s everything my lord, the wedding needed to be pushed back. The elders want to host it after the main sect facilities are complete.”

This was a happy occasion but accidents could happen. The sect's protective formations that could go against nascent soul threats needed to be put in place. The main castle area and the side buildings where the large banquet would be held needed to be prepared as well.

The sect had even hired some outside help with these wedding preparations as there was just not enough time. They wanted to have everything done within the next three months. The sets building process had already lasted for half a year and quite a bit of the main structure was standing.

The formation that was going to siphon energy into the medallion was going through the testing phase. They could even hasten the building process by moving some smaller structures with the help of the flying ships towards the main sect area.

He let Zhang Ya go back to her previous assignments as she was also quite busy with all the wedding planning.

He took a peek into his storage ring, there were some materials that could be used for creating these wedding rings. He didn’t only want to make them beautiful he also wanted them to act as a protective accessory. With his current knowledge he could add some nice features to these two rings, even make them connect with each other.

‘Hm, red and gold huh? Think I’ll just make them gold… maybe into a dragon design?’

He was thinking about making the rings into the shape of a coiling dragon. He could add some features to them like teleportation, so if his wife was ever in trouble he could always transfer himself to her location to aid her.

He needed to wait a bit for the arrays to be activated before heading into his crafting abode. The wedding was getting closer and he needed to create some presents for his fiance.

Chapter 206

The months continued to pass and word had spread far and wide that the new upstart sect would be having a festival. Two of their senior members would be bonded in secret matrimony and become Daoist partners.

All of the prominent clans in the United Element sect area were invited to this event. This would be a chance for them to meet up with their new overlords. There were a lot of rumors about this Zhang Dong, mostly positive ones. He was supposedly a generous man that favored the weak while being an honorable warrior.

Every large city that was comparable in size to Spirit Spring City or Moonlight City had one of these clans. They mostly had to have a core formation elder in their mids to be eligible for an invitation.

Everyone was skeptical at first. The Dark Palm sect was gone but not due to the United Element sect. They were taken out by the three other large sects from the area and not by this new one. They feared that if they socialized too much with these upstarts that the other large powers could take their anger out on them.

They took a wait and see approach without taking any sides. Time continued to fly but for some reason, even after the Dark Palm sect’s demise, the other three sects didn’t seem interested in attacking the upstart. Then updated news arrived that Zhang Dong’s master was apparently someone that was to be feared. He was the sole reason that the three sects didn’t move in to seize the rest of the lands. There was also info that the three United Element sect elders outclassed regular nascent soul masters.

This was evidence enough for the weaker clans to seek an audience. Everyone knew that the quickest way to prominence was joining a powerful sect. Even though this one was only starting out and it was dangerous they still had nascent soul elders on their side. This wedding would be a good opportunity to make a good impression so they all needed to get some gifts ready.

Everyone used their spies to get information about the most prominent people in the sect. There were some discrepancies but everyone agreed that Zhang Dong was probably the strongest one from them all. The next in line was Huo Qiang followed by Feng Liena in tow, though her status might have been higher as she was the bride.

Then the fourth most influential person in the sect wasn’t even at the great circle of core formation. No, Zhang Jin was considered next up as he had the ear of the Sect leader and could affect his decisions. After that, it blurred as the sect was still new and the inner workings weren’t clear.

The clans were wary of the nascent soul masters so most of them decided to go for an easier target to bribe. This would be Zhang Jin and he was quite infamous in the land. He had stolen quite a few brides in his younger days and never ceased doing it to this day.

Concubines and alcohol would be on the people's agenda. Getting one of their sisters in bed with this old pervert was cruel but they saw this as an opportunity to prosper. Plus, they couldn’t really do that with Zhang Dong as his Daoist partner was also a nascent soul master. Trying to give away their daughters to him could bring ruin to them by Feng Liena’s hand.

There were also lower priority targets like Zhang Dong’s disciples. Also anyone from the inner circle that belonged to one of the three clans that established that sect. The probability of gaining their trust was low but they had to try as it was a golden ticket to prosperity.

While the clans with lesser power made their preparations the three sects were in a bind. Should they send envoys to the wedding, or should they ignore these newbies and show that they weren’t on their level by ignoring the invitations.

Each one of them had tried gathering more information during the period that they were building their base. They didn’t come up with any substantial evidence of the reason they were in the lower lands. From their standpoint, Zhang Dong had to be crazy to wish to build his sect at that location. There was just nothing of value hidden there.

The investigations brought nothing and all of the spies that wandered too close to the building site vanished. They then received word that their sect leader was seen patrolling the whole area and figured that they would need someone close to him in strength to get anywhere. This they weren’t willing to do as they still feared the man that was backing him.

In the end, they decided to send someone over that was expandable. They didn’t need to move their nascent soul masters yet but could at least show some good faith. This was also an opportunity for them to see how this new sect operated. It had been about a year since they started rebuilding and they were close to completion.

While everyone was finalizing their schemes of either getting on the good side of the new sect or spying on them, a nervous Zhang Dong was pacing back and forth in his room. He had managed to prepare the wedding rings and was now getting cold feet.

While busy with his work he could relax and not think about the commitment he would be making towards the Feng Matriarch. He had made two identical golden rings, they were of a dragon and phoenix that were entangling each other. He got the idea from Liena’s and his soul beasts that were a dragon and a phoenix.

Just as he wanted he had added a teleportation function to both of them. He could either teleport to her or have her teleport to him in times of need. There was also a tracking function connected to his system. This would show him his wife's last location if ever something blocked out his teleportation or if the rings got damaged.

There wasn’t enough space to fit too many enchantments into the items. So he had to settle for the teleportation function and a barrier that would appear as a large bubble and shield her from harm. It could also be later recharged if she used up this protective measure.
He had been able to relax after the protective arrays had been set up. He inspected them by himself and even tested out their power. They were able to even take hits from him that were equal to a nascent soul expert at the late stage. Thanks to the spirit vein he didn’t need to use his system points to power the cubes that acted as batteries.

The siphoning array that was the most important one was also completed and now all of that natural spiritual energy was being funneled into the Dimensional Regalia treasure. The longer this continued the larger the floating island got. There was now enough space to fit large structures for their core disciples and core elders.

Building them would have to wait till they started with their recruitment drive. They were finished with the main structure and the walls surrounding it but still had to prepare the side buildings that would be used by the outer sect disciples. They also needed to organize the food and prepare some occupations for their new disciples.

They wouldn’t just allow strangers into their minds without making them work for it. That’s why they were going to set up a merit-based system. They would also have something akin to a notice board with job listings.

The elders would place jobs that the disciples could perform for them. Like helping with pill forging, procuring herbs, or even going out of the sect to hunt beasts to bring back cores or food. Everything was moving forward fast and it seemed that the sect would be taking flight soon.

The sect wasn’t the thing on Matt’s mind though, no. He was the groom and he hadn’t been able to see his bride for a couple of months now. The closer to the date of the wedding the more nervous he became. He had gone through the whole thing in his head a couple of times but he was still anxious. What if he says something stupid? What if they don’t get along with each other? What if that sister of hers tries doing something silly again?

There was a myriad of questions flying around in his head. The tranquil mind technique seemed to be working a bit less since he got to the nascent soul level, probably because he got it while he was still at the core formation level. While he was looking over the wedding rings, checking if they weren’t chipped in any place a small group of female cultivators walked in, Zhang Ya at the front.

“Sect Leader we have brought the designs for your wedding robe”

There were five women of various ages here, even one that could be his grandmother. They started bringing out robe after robe and hung them out for him to see. A giant mirror was also brought out and placed to the side so he could see how they fit him.

They were mostly in red and golden color, some of them purple or violet as that was also considered the color of nobility. He would rather use his white clothes but apparently white was attributed to mourning and bad luck. Which didn’t really fit the joyous occasion that was the wedding.

The women that Zhang Ya, her included looked quite eager to make their sect leader try on all of these robes. He had to get this over with so he let them use him as a dress-up doll. They continued to squeal with joy each time he came out in a brand new robe. He even was coerced into putting on a silly hat and a black and gold fan with a dragon pattern.

In the end, he was forced to decide on a long flowy red robe. It was all in crimson with dragon patterns running all over it. He was also wearing some kind of rectangular hat with twelve strings of beads hanging out in the front of his forehead. From what he knew these kinds of hats were worn by men of power. The wiggly beads on the strings were there to remind him that he shouldn’t make any sudden movements to make them wobble. They were to remain unmoving while he kept a straight posture.

The group of ladies finally let him have his rest and the date of the wedding approached closer. He didn’t know what kind of wedding dress Feng Liena was going to wear but considering it was the Gyaru clan we were talking about. She might appear in something closer looking to a western wedding dress. Though he had convinced her to lose those traditions so she might appear in something to match his red and gold appearance.

Soon the day of the wedding came. The banquet would be held inside the new large sect castle building in a giant hall. There were numerous round tables with golden tablecloths. Everything was on red and gold, the chairs and decorations included. There were beautiful fountains with golden dragon and phoenix heads spitting out spiritual water that glowed in a blue hue.

Murals depicted some of the struggles that their Sect leader had to go through. The soul-beasts of Huo Qiang, Feng Liena, and Zhang Dong were all depicted on the walls looking quite ferocious after one of the more artistically inclined sect brothers witnessed their battle.

This space was quite empty at the moment as the guests from the sects were only just arriving. The large numbers of ships and cultivators on swords were slowly flying this way. If you didn’t know better you’d think it was some kind of invasion. In reality, there wasn’t even a single person that was at the nascent soul level that was coming this way. Most of the people gathered here were from the clans that were even weaker than the Huo Clan was before they rose to more prominence with the United Element sect.

While the guests were coming a pale looking Zhang Dong was looking at himself in the mirror. He was all dressed up in his groom's robe and had to now go out to greet the guests. His wife was going to arrive soon and he was getting cold feet.

He gave himself a double smack to the face with his palms. His cheeks went slightly red as he finally mustered the courage to walk out of the room. He put on his poker face while pushing the large door wide open, his retainers already waiting outside.

‘Let’s get married!’

Chapter 207

Outside the main United Element sect’s newly built palace was a giant courtyard. There was one main path lined out with cherry blossoms. To the sides were chairs in the usual gold and red coloring.

Some people might think that all this extravagant gold coloring scheme was extremely costly but they would be wrong. Gold wasn’t really a metal that cultivators appreciated that much. You even stopped really trading in golden coins after reaching the foundation establishment level and then switched over to spirit stones.

This wide path would be the one that Feng Liena would walk through. Zhang Dong was supposed to receive her by the entrance of the castle. After which the two would walk in and be wed by a marriage officiant, there were no religious priests here so this would be done by Zhang Jin. In most cases this would be done by an elder that was of a high ranking, such an honor would fall on Huo Qiang but he refused and Zhang Jin was chosen instead.

After this was done everyone would be led into the banquet hall for a party. This part was less extravagant than the weddings from back on earth. There wouldn’t be any dancing and the couple of the hour were going to just greet the people and accept some gifts. This would probably be quite boring and take a while as there were quite a lot of people coming to this event.

At the moment Zhang Dong was looking at the inside of the castle structure. He was standing at the large gate-like doors through which he would be guiding Feng Liena inside. On the inside was a large hall that was decorated in red and gold yet again. He could even see the podium on which they were supposed to repeat their vows.

‘Uh… this is really happening…’

If his body was normal he would probably be drenched in sweat. The little hat with the green jade beads was wiggling around each time he made a step. If he concentrated a bit he could move without it wobbling around but he was a bit too nervous to focus now.

“Sect Leader, the guests are arriving as we speak, you should get ready.”

Zhang Ya’s voice sounded from the side which made Zhang Dong’s flinch a bit. Even she could tell that her Patriarch was a bit out of it, which made her hold her hand to her mouth and chuckle. She was glad that she saw some humanity under that emotionless face from time to time. Due to Zhang Dong keeping up his facade most people considered him to be the perfect stone-faced no-nonsense cultivator. In reality, he still wasn’t quite sure if what he was doing was something that a leader would do.

‘Ah yes, when the door opens I’ll just step out and greet the bride just as we rehearsed…’

He nodded towards Zhang Ya that moved away to accept some of the guests. He could hear people talking and chairs moving which indicated that the crowds were getting seated. There weren't quite enough chairs to fit all of the people so the junior members were expected to stand. They would also remain outside the wedding hall and mingle with each other as only the more prominent figures were allowed to witness the whole marriage and then the banquet.

Matt moved his hands up, the robe he was wearing was quite long. His sleeves were super baggy and when he moved his hands around they would just swish and shake. He wondered how people could actually consider fighting in robes like these as he faced some cultivators that wore similar ones to battle.

Suddenly the doors started opening this made his heart jump. He quickly straightened himself out, he couldn’t let this annoying flowy bead-hat jiggle. It would be considered bad luck and also a hit to his face if he didn’t move as a proper kingly figure. Though he could probably force the beads to stop from moving with his spiritual force. This would be noticed by the other cultivators which would be quite shameful.

He gave out one last sigh before stepping forward. His posture impeccable and even when he stepped forward his ceremonial hat didn’t move at all. He was greeted by bright lights and the shining sun that momentarily stunned his vision.

After his eyes adjusted he was stupefied even more. On the other side of the long pathway that was lined up by cherry blossoms stood his bride. She was wearing a red dress with golden patterns that looked like phoenixes.

Parts of the wedding dress were very form-fitting as he could see her thin waistline and pronounced chest. On the other hand, her sleeves were uncharacteristically long. They would reach all the way to the ground if she stretched out her arms to the side.

The lower long skirt was also quite a thing to look at. Besides all the intricate pattern designs it was being held up by small green birds. The birds were probably some tamed beasts and they were holding up the long skirt from the back as it stretched for at least five meters.

He couldn’t see Liena’s face yet as it was under a veil, but he could kind of see her eyes under that semi-transparent cloth. She took a step forward and her high heels clicked on the smooth polished marble floor. All of the guests stood up as the bride approached, some were crying some were smiling while some remained untouched by the occasion.

Zhang Dong gulped a bit that made his hat almost move. He was astonished after seeing Feng Liena’s curvaceous figure. He wasn’t sure if she was just blessed or if it was due to the body refining technique that she was using. He straightened out while people were focused on the bride, finally, she began to move.

Some kind of eastern tune started playing, there were a couple of people playing on the zithers while the bride moved forward. To his surprise, one of them was Zhang Xue that was also wearing a slightly less extravagant red and golden robe.

The closer his wife got the more nervous he became but she continued. Her strides were short but resolute, he wasn’t sure if she liked him that much but she didn’t seem as on the fence as he was. This was a reassuring thought which made Matt a bit less nervous.

The cherry blossoms danced around behind her as she continued with her slow walk. Behind her, you could see some of her family members. They were all dressed up and most of their faces were unknown to him.

The only two people that he recognized was her younger sister and the baked potato granny that was bawling her eyes out. She was loudly sobbing while voicing out her appreciation that her little granddaughter was getting married.

He also was a bit scared that that little sister of hers would try to pull something during this wedding. There were works of fiction where someone interrupted the wedding while the pair was taking their vows. What if she tried to grab him from the altar while he and Liena are repeating their vows?

He shifted his gaze back to the bride and tried to calm himself down again. The strange image of Feng Nuana knocking on some glass while shouting his name came to his mind and made him chuckle. This silly image was enough to cheer him up as the bride had arrived. The music stopped with the bride and everyone waited for Zhang Dong to follow up.

He had to strain himself immensely to keep his head steady. He reached out towards his wife and presented his palm towards her. The woman responded with grace and grasped it with hers. His hand was a lot larger than hers and he could feel the warmth coming from it after they held hands.

He turned to the door that they were supposed to walk through. Side to side they continued with the people just looking on. He was on the right while she was on the left akin to a traditional earthly wedding. They stepped through the entrance to the wedding hall and soon the people behind them followed suit.

While walking forward Zhang Dong continued to focus on not making his hat jiggle. The sensation of holding a woman’s delicate hand was quite distracting though. The two remained silent to each other, Matt was feeling shy and didn’t really know what to say while Feng Liena remained courteous as it was rude to speak out before the husband did.

When they finally arrived at the altar, Zhang Jin was there in a black robe with more gold in it. He was also wearing a really tall hat with a Taoistic symbol on it. Everyone from the senior generation was here as well as some junior members that were close relatives. The others had to wait outside and had their own outside banquet to mingle in.

“Zhang Dong and Feng Liena. Today you enter as individuals, but you will leave here as husband and wife, blending your lives, expanding your family ties, and embarking upon the grandest adventure of unity.”

“All those present have come to witness and celebrate your love and commitment this day.”

The people cheered a bit from the back, quite a bit of the ladies were already tearing up as Zhang Jin continued to speak.

“Today, as you join yourselves in marriage, there is a vast and unknown future stretching out before you.”

“Through your commitment to each other, may you grow and nurture a love that makes both of you better people, a love that will last throughout generations to come.”

“Now, repeat after me!”

Zhang Jin looked to Zhang Dong with a smile on his face, he could feel how nervous he was even though his facial expression wasn’t changing.

“Zhang Dong, are you willing to marry Feng Liena as your wife, in sacred marriage together for life?”

“Whether she has sickness or health, poverty or wealth, beauty or is plain, in good times and in bad, are you willing to love her, to comfort her, to respect her, and protect her?”

“And willing to be forever loyal to her?”

The bride was still covering her face by the veil but she could see her eyes through it. After a slight pause, he mustered the courage to reply.

“I am!”

Zhang Jin smiled a bit and then continued, making Feng Liena repeat the exact same vows that Zhang Dong just said. It didn’t take long before she also replied with a resounding…

“I am willing!”

Zhang Jin nodded again and looked to the side. Zhang Liu approached with the golden wedding rings placed upon a red pillow. He looked quite proud that he could do this for his master on this occasion.

“Zhang Dong, take this ring and place it on Feng Liena‘s finger. Repeat after me…”

“Feng Liena, I give you this ring as a symbol of the promise I made to you today.”

Zhang Dong repeated the short sentence and placed the ring that he had made on Liena’s finger on her left hand as it was the closest hand to the heart.

As before Feng Liena repeated after Zhang Jin and slid the wedding ring on Zhang Dong’s finger.

“May the blessings of life, the joy of love, the peace of truth, and the wisdom and strength of Spirit, be your constant companion, now and always, as husband and wife.”

“You may seal this union with a kiss.”

Zhang Dong moved his hands towards that veil and moved it out of the way. He finally witnessed his wife in all of her glory. She was just stunning, her large blue eyes were focused on him but they soon closed, her pink lips puckering up. He gulped momentarily before leaning down. He placed one of his hands against her neck and cheek, finally, he leaned in, their lips meeting in a kiss.

A lot of people started cheering, hands going into the air while some flower petals started to fly around the room. The wedding was finally complete and now the banquet remained.

Chapter 208

Matt was sitting down by a giant table, hand in hand with his wife that was sitting next to him. He was feeling a bit dazed after the first proper kiss that the two had had at the wedding ceremony. He needed to keep a cool head though, this was the part of the ceremony where they were going to be accepting gifts from the other clans and sects.

There was an old friend from two years ago looking at him. He was bald and looked like a monk and his name was Bankei. He had met him and Feng Liena during the forced expedition to the sacred ground. They received a bunch of talismans and evil repelling treasures as also an oath of recognition from him and his sect. They didn’t reach out in their time of need though so Matt didn’t feel like he owed them anything.

The boring exchange of bows and presents continued on, all various clan names were being thrown about but he didn’t remember any of them. He even felt like some of the last names started repeating themselves. This made him realize that he was sitting on even more power and land now, it was as if he was an emperor on his own planet, at least surface wise.

He tried recalling what the next part of the ceremony would be. He would have to go through the whole sect on a decorated flying platform and wave at everyone there. He had already made his greeting speech and was just waiting till all of this was over.

The thing that he was anxiously awaiting was the ending of this wedding, namely the wedding night. He was equally eager and equally afraid of not fulfilling his wife’s womanly needs. The only thing he had to go back to was the one night stand almost three years ago and knowledge from internet movies from back in his earthen days.

“Now from the Dragon Gate Sect…”

His nervous contemplations were brought to an end after he noticed the name of one of the three great sects being mentioned. He went a bit on alert and also could feel Feng Liena gripping his hand a bit tighter. If he liked it or not these were people he had to contend with and offending them would never be anything good. Still, a line had to be drawn and there were certain things that they wouldn’t be able to turn a blind eye to.

The person that appeared was an older man, his cultivation wasn’t high or anything and he conducted himself with grace. The gift wasn’t anything grand but it made Zhang Dong feel like this sect was being respectful. He just nodded and thanked the man and that was it.

Next came the Demon Subduing Sect, this time it was a lady close to his age. She looked a bit haughty but she also managed to deliver the present of goodwill without making much of a scene. The trouble only started with the third and last guest that was from the Limitless Sword Society.

The person was your typical young master as always. Matt wasn’t sure why there were so many of those types in this world but they seemed to always cause trouble. He arrived late and even held up the ceremony process. It would be seen as a disgrace if they changed the order now.
The first red flag was that he was carrying his sword on his hip. Apparently the Limitless Sword Sect’s cultivators treasured their weapons and would rarely allow them to be taken away. Still, this young man wasn’t at a position where he would be allowed to do that in front of a nascent soul master like Zhang Dong. He was clearly disrespecting them, not afraid as he had his sect to back him up.

Matt just gave out a sigh as he watched the man that looked to be in his late twenties strut in. He wasn’t sure how old he was but he could very well be over fifty even if he looked like this. His core formation cultivation gave him quite the longevity up to 500 years of age. A nascent soul elder in contrast mostly lived between a thousand and two thousand years.

“Greetings from the Limitless Sword Society~”

The man had a couple of people behind them. They didn’t bow or even clasp their hands while approaching Zhang Dong and Feng Liena. Liena grasped Dong’s hand even tighter than before and he could feel like she could have some kind of a rage outburst soon.

‘Hell hath no fury like a woman scorned…’

Matt wasn’t all that mad, he had already kind of gotten used to those haughty young master types. He already went through battles and knew that nothing good came from aggravating them. This showed after the Dark Palm sect debacle which was caused by one of their junior members. He even started blaming the parents more than the young masters for how they acted. If their elders showed them how to present themselves and not see everyone as a little bug to squish they would probably be normal people.

He was just a bit afraid that his wife could do something emotional as this was her wedding and women tended to take it a bit more seriously than others. He did a small side glance to his wife, he could see her eyebrows twitching furiously at the display of disrespect.

“We came bearing gifts for you honorable lord and your beautiful wife, hope you cherish this treasure.”

The man from the sect clapped his hands together and two of his retainers brought out his gift. It was in a polished bronze container which they placed on the offering table. They opened it up while everyone looked with curiosity, inside were low-quality pills that made more brows furrow.

The people started whispering with each other. This was a blatant show of disrespect, those pills that were getting presented looked to not even be above mortal grade in rarity, probably at the lower end of it.

The people from the United Element sect were appalled by this behavior. They were sure that the young man was just throwing his weight around. He had some backing as his granduncle was indeed a nascent soul master from that sword sect.

Still, the United Element’s sect leader managed to last through the battle with the Dark Palm sect’s Yang Guanyu and even took on five cultivators at once. This young man was probably unaffected by this fact and probably thought it was just baseless rumors.

“Oh, quite the high-quality earth grade pills you have brought with you there…”

After a moment of silence, Zhang Dong’s calm voice resounded through the banquet hall. Everyone looked to the sect leader and wondered what their leader was on about. The pills that those people brought in were clearly low-grade mortal ones.

Before anyone could ask about what Zhang Dong was talking about, one of the pills moved upwards. It flew towards the United Element sect’s leader and stopped in front of his face. He moved his free hand over to the pill and tapped it with his index finger.

The people weren’t sure what he was doing but soon realized that it wasn’t anything they could fathom. After the little tap, the pill started changing, it spun around and exuded a large amount of spiritual energy. The ugly brownish color started to change into a golden one as the pill increased in quality shooting all the way to the pinnacle of earth grade in a matter of moments.

This was one of the upgrades that his crafting abode. He didn’t need to be in it for some of its functions to work as he could affect the items outside. What the haughty young master had brought over were simple Qi replenishing pills, they could be easily upgraded as they didn’t really require any more ingredients, just some pure spiritual Qi.

The shameful present was turned into something more bearable. No one really offered anything at the heaven grade which was not something many were willing to do. By doing it like this Zhang Dong was trying not to start a fight while also showing off his power.

The young master in question looked surprised, by turning the trash pills he brought over to something valuable Zhang Dong had delivered a blow to his face. Before he could speak out about it though he felt a strong presence washing over him.

“Listen here you little shit, I’m not sure what you were trying to achieve with this, but those trinkets that you are wearing won’t be able to protect you from me.”

Zhang Dong was the one speaking while concealing his voice so that only this person from the Limitless Sword Society could hear him. The young master was stunned, the protective treasures should be able to block out any nascent soul master’s spiritual power and even teleport him back home if he got into trouble. For some reason, they weren’t activating and he couldn’t move a muscle or even speak.

“I will ignore this only once if you dare disrespect me or my wife again…”

“Your elders won’t even find traces of your soul behind. Now just smile, apologize to my wife and move on with your pathetic excuse of a life.”

The man felt the strong power vanishing and he could breathe again. He quickly scanned his treasures and to his surprise, they were all unresponsive. They were all heavenly grade but somehow they all stopped working, he couldn’t even teleport out of here to save himself.

He realized that he could very well die now if he continued with this charade. He just did what he was told too, bowing down while his face went pale.

“Excuse me, honorable elders… I’m not feeling too well... “

He stumbled back and almost fell over the people with him surprised at the reaction of their young master. They rarely saw him this way, he looked meek and afraid. Zhang Dong was good enough in masking his aura so that most of the people in the room didn’t know what he did.

Two people did though, Feng Liena was one and Huo Qiang was the other one. The latter burst out in laughter and even pointed at the Limitless Sword Sect cultivators that were leaving.

“Look at them run with their tails between their legs.”

The two people that came before him were a bit surprised but it didn’t take much knowledge to figure out about what transpired here. None of them could tell what the United Sect Patriarch did but it had to have left an impression of the young haughty man. They were surprised that his protective treasures didn’t activate, this prompted them to be extra careful.

This was Zhang Dong’s home turf. He had designed all of the formations and with the help of the spiritual vein, they also boosted his power. The youth’s treasures were all heaven grade but at the lowest spectrum so deactivating them while he was under his grand formation was easy to accomplish.

The gift-giving continued for some more time and finally, the day was coming to an end. The street lights that were spread out through the entire sect lit up as the sun went down. The whole sect has a more modern look to it as those lights also had lightbulbs in them instead of candles.

Feng Liena and Zhang Dong were now making their rounds on the decorative flying platform. Waving at their new sect members, the two didn’t talk that much. Whenever Zhang Dong tried doing some small talk the woman started blushing, he didn’t think she would be this bashful right before the big night.

The two finally flew out into the sunset and glided towards a secluded villa. A separate protective formation churned and engulfed them in a thick barrier that didn’t allow anyone to peek in.

The other people continued mingling with each other and Zhang Jin found himself surrounded by beautiful women from all sides. In the future, there would be tales of the big female cultivator brawl that happened after the famous Zhang Dong’s wedding that would be recounted in history books for generations.

The woman and man of the hour awkwardly went in through the door of the villa their sect members had prepared for them. Apparently it was lifted from somewhere and brought over by a flying ship instead of being built. Now they were supposed to consummate their marriage. Zhang Dong looked at his blushing wife and nodded to himself.

‘The final battle has just begun...”

Chapter 209

A mostly naked Zhang Dong looked up to the ceiling. He had woken up after an evening filled with passion. The wedding night had lasted all up till the next day as the two lovers showed stamina worthy of nascent soul masters. Unbeknownst to him, a legend had been started this way, it would be later named the ‘Passionate Earthquake’ that kept everyone from the sect up for the entire night.

Feng Liena laid bare under the red bed sheets. Her wedding dress was tossed to the side along with Zhang Dong’s bead hat. He smiled a bit as he descended without making any noise. He used his nascent soul powers to cover his sleeping wife with the rest of the bed cloth before heading outside.

The villa that the two were now resting in was quite large and it even had a nice room with a fireplace. He sat down with a towel wrapped around his nether regions, his chest exposed. He started spacing out, the memories of the previous night still fresh in his mind.

‘Well, that was something, she is surprisingly flexible...’

He found himself comparing this night to his first time. That was a long time ago, reaching three years now. It felt a bit different and somehow better, but he wasn’t sure if it was only due to him not having done the deed in a while. This cultivator body worked differently than his old one as he didn’t feel like he needed to perform the usual tasks.

‘We didn’t use any protection either, but she is my wife so that shouldn’t matter.’

He recalled that he might have gotten a bit overzealous but what was done was done. He would face the consequences later. He stayed seated there without doing much, there were no servants or anyone to bother them here either. Soon enough he heard the door opening up and the figure of Feng Liena appeared.

“Husband?”

His mouth quivered a bit after he heard the way she referred to him. He was certainly not used to that one as the woman used to refer to him as senior brother not long ago.

“W-wife? Wifey? I’m down here.”

He felt a bit awkward, the two might have known each other for years now but their interactions were limited to mostly business.

Feng Liena had woken up a bit after Zhang Dong left the room. She was a bit out of it at first and then confused as she didn’t find her husband next to her. She recalled the previous night and how forceful her hubby had been which caused her to blush furiously. She then left the room in search of him, worried that he might have left somewhere. She didn’t need to go far as he was sitting just there on the floor below with only some cloth covering his lower parts.

Zhang Dong looked at his wife. She had appeared wearing some kind of nightgown robe hybrid that he wasn’t accustomed to. The moment she saw him sitting there she started blushing yet again which kind of made him want to tease her. The two had already seen themselves naked so from his standpoint there was no reason to be shy.

“Are you hungry, the sect had prepared a feast in the other room and even set up a formation to keep everything fresh.”

He stood up from his seat while looking up, Feng Liena covered her face a bit but followed the movements of her hubby while looking between her fingers.

“No need to be shy after what we did yesterday…”

He had gotten over his nervousness during the deed, his wife on the other hand was still acting a bit reserved. He flew up to her and lifted her up into his arms before heading out into the room with the food. Liena was skittish at first wiggling in his arms while trying not to show too much skin. She would probably need a bit more time to get used to this type of treatment.

The two continued their lovey-dovey honeymoon for a couple of days before heading back to the sect. They still had a lot of things to do and even if they wanted they couldn’t just remain there.

They were greeted back by their family members. Zhang Jin and Huo Qiang had smirks on their faces, Zhang Dong was unsure why but soon he would discover the earthquake he caused.

“Welcome back Patriarch and Matriarch…”

The people clasped their hands while acting awkwardly, even though their two nascent soul masters were behind a defensive formation, the tremors reached up to the main castle structure. Luckily they had reinforced all of the furniture in that villa beforehand.

“Anything happen while we were gone?”

Zhang Dong asked while floating down, hand to hand with his wife.

“The guests have already left, the people from those three sects left on the first day…”

He recalled the young man that tried to insult him and the other two. He managed to resolve the situation somehow but wasn’t happy that they still weren’t getting taken seriously.

“Good, how are the formations? We should be able to proceed with the plans”

“Yes, the crafting masters would like a word with you, they want you to approve the teleportation gate design.”

“So we are close to the finish line…”

He continued talking with Zhang Jin. The moment they connected the Dimensional regalia with the outside was the moment they could start setting up the true sect. This was an immortal grade treasure and it was repairing itself the more energy they fed it. There was no danger of it getting destroyed by a cultivator, the only thing that could cause damage to it was another item at that grade.

The medallion was hidden in a closed location at the sect. He deliberated hiding it in the place that he found the floating cube. But he was afraid that someone or something could appear there and snatch the treasure with his people in it.

Feng Liena and Zhang Dong finally parted with each other. Huo Qiang and her would leave the sect for now and patrol the rest of their lands. There was still danger of other nascent soul masters trying to sneak in.

The Patriarch would remain and help set up the core area for their most trusted people. There was much work to be done and now that the defensive arrays were fully operational Matt didn’t need to remain so passive. He could start crafting weapons, creating pills and combining techniques to form new superior ones. If this continued they could finally become a proper sect and even open their doors to new disciples.

He also had the option of traveling through the lands. There were a couple of undiscovered places that reached into the lower areas of the empire. Most people didn’t bother with those as spiritual energy was faint there, unsuited for cultivation. He was able to find some treasures in that type of location. There was a spirit vein hidden here as well as the obsidian material that he couldn’t even budge with his full power.

He wasn’t in a hurry, the sects wouldn’t be going against them for quite some time. Everyone adopted a wait and see approach as they weren’t willing to offend his so-called master. Their new sect was also flying under the radar of the true behemoths of the empire. The other powers also had others to contend with, just as the fallen Dark Palm sect if they showed any sign of weakness they would be eradicated.

‘Think I can design that testing course for new disciples now…’

He thought back to the words of fiction that he used to read. They were weirdly similar to how this world operated. He remembered the sects setting up various tests that the prospects could go through.

He already approved one idea, it would be a corridor with some wooden puppet soldiers. Similar to the test that his disciples went through at the dao festival. They would need to reach the end to qualify further.

There would also be a Qi measuring device but it wouldn’t require a person to perform any punches. He had his system to help him out, he could imbue some devices with some nice measuring features.

He wanted to create a machine to measure all-around aptitude, current strength level as also their deposition. His system could tell a person’s alignment, if they had an evil heart or were someone just. The system showed it to him in a D&D alignment system, raging from lawful good to chaotic evil.

These alignments weren’t set in stone though, they could even shift in the middle of battle. For instance, the Dark Palm sect leader’s alignment was Lawful Evil before they started the fight. When he turned himself into that monster it shifted to Chaotic Evil in a matter of seconds.

Still, this would save him from accepting anyone sketchy into his sect, he was still on the fence if he should accept Chaotic Neutral people, they were a bit random to work with. You never knew what they would do, they could very well abandon their sect brothers in a time of need.

‘Would be probably better to cap it at true neutral, just to be safe.’

While Zhang Dong was thinking about the improvement of his sect another scene was playing out somewhere deeper in the empire.

There was a certain gathering of old men and women taking place. Only two from them were talking with each other, the rest remained in place without moving a muscle.

“Hey, old Wang, that grandson of yours has been causing quite a ruckus in the sect.”

“He even crippled old Jing’s grandson and stole his fiance.”

One old man asked another one while laughing. Everyone in here was a nascent soul cultivator and a pillar of this behemoth of a sect.

“He won the duel fair and square, if that bastard even dares to lay a finger on my grandson he knows what will happen.”

“Is he taking after you? So ruthless!”

The two laughed while sipping on some spirit alcohol. The other people in the room didn’t respond, one of them seemed a bit dejected by what was being said here but he held his mouth shut.

“He sure has been progressing at a fast pace since two years ago, quite the late bloomer.”

The person called Wang nodded at the remark while sipping on some more alcohol.
“As long as he progresses..., wish he didn’t develop that little hobby of his, that girl probably won’t last long either...”

The moment the nascent soul elder mentioned his grandson’s ‘hobby’ the other people in the room started coughing and looking to the sides.

“Well, geniuses are like that as long as the sect prospers I don’t think we should worry about that. Not something we can’t fix with some spirit stones.”

The other man laughed out loud while the others looked even more uncomfortable after hearing him talk. The man named Wang just gave out a sigh and nodded.

“Enough about my grandson.”

“Anything of note in the empire? It would be nice if we got some good news for once. Maybe that bastard of an Azure Emperor died?”

“If only old Wang, if only.”

“Nothing much besides one of the middle-sized sects going under, what was their name again? Dark Foot? Dark Fist? Well never mind, they weren't important, think the other little sects already had their fill of their lands.”

“They colluded with each other to ransack their remains, not like they pose a threat to our Soaring Dragon Sect.”

Old Wang just snorted.

“That’s a given, there is only one reason we aren’t at the top of this empire.”

The other man that Wang was talking too also gave out a snort of disdain. They talked some more while the other people in the room remained silent, not uttering a word unless they got asked. The two elders delved into the country's politics some more, rumbling on for quite a bit till everyone left and it was already dark outside. The old man stood up from his seat and walked outside.

“Junior greets the Sect Leader.”

The man didn’t look back as he continued going, his eyes started glowing with a blue light before he disappeared into the ether. He appeared moments later above the large sect ground that he was the master of. He just glanced at the massive structures that were on even larger mountain peaks.

“Soon my sect will reign supreme over this land, we will crush everyone in our path and even the Azure Emperor will stand no chance.”

He smirked slightly before disappearing once again, this time towards an unknown destination.

Chapter 210 Vol 3. Start

“Take care Rong’er, you must succeed, the future of this tribe depends on it.”

A large burly man was giving his son a pat on the back, this man was the Tatar Tribe’s Chief and he was talking to his son Yang Rong.

“Don’t worry father I’ll be sure to get in, the sect is really close so I’ll come to visit often!”

The youth laughed out loud while smacking his chest that had gotten quite wide within the years. He wasn’t alone here, there were many other youths at the Qi condensation level gathered. People from the village were seeing them off as finally, the honorable sect that they owed their lives too was opening up their doors.

Cheng Yun was also there, the boy was one of the first people that Matt had come across in this world. The two youths and some of their tribe members were packed up and ready to make the walk towards the United Element Sect’s location.

The sect had set up their main headquarters in the nearby forest. This caused some trouble with the beasts that fled in all directions, but the sect was nice enough to reimburse the tribes for the loss of food.

After some years they had finally announced that they would be accepting new disciples. They were divided into age groups depending on the realm someone was in. For instance, they didn’t accept anyone above the age of 25 that was still a Qi condensation practitioner. This left most of the people in these lower lands without any hope. Only the youngsters would be allowed to participate in the Sect trials.

Cultivators of the foundation establishment level were also tested, they would receive higher positions also depending on their age. There was also a cap there that ended at fifty. It was obvious from these limits that the new sect was looking for youthful cultivators. There were a couple of theories out there why it was like this. The most feasible one being that they didn’t want talentless old cultivators in their midst.

The trials would be taking place in a week. The Tatar Tribe was located a day away from the United Elements sect. The tribe people were going there a bit early as they just couldn’t wait any longer. They knew the woods like the back of their hand and would probably arrive even sooner.

“Take care.”

“Make us proud!”

“For the tribe!”

People were waving and hugging the youths that were below the age of 25. There were no tribesmen that were at the foundation establishment level. There was quite a bit at stake here, the future of this tribe was on the line here and the youths knew this.
The Tatar Tribe wasn’t the only one around here. There were many similar tribes in villages scattered all over this massive forest. Everyone knew that if even one person gets accepted in as an outer sect disciple it would be enough to protect them.

This was how things worked in this world. If the other tribes managed to land a spot in the new powerful sect they would be able to toss their weight around. There were long-lasting grudges between some of the tribes. They also battled with each other for resources and food on a regular basis.

Cheng Yun and Yang Rong that was in no way related to the Dark Palm Sect leader finally left the village. They had about twenty people in their group all trained and previously tested by their village elders. The sect didn’t really specify anything besides the age limit but no one was willing to let untrained kids participate in the trials. The sect might take offense if they send juniors of low cultivation bases and low skill.

“Brother Rong, do you think we will succeed?”

Cheng Yun asked while the group moved through the woods. The two didn’t use to see eye to eye all those years ago but they have gotten past it. The reason the two were so close now and considered themselves brothers, was Zhang Dong. He had saved both of them and the two bonded over it.

“Of course we will succeed, the mighty senior even blessed us with his presence twice already!”

Rong was pumped and believed that there wouldn’t be any problems. He had been training for all those years, even hogging most of the bathhouse that Zhang Dong cultivated in to get faster breakthroughs.

“You are right… he might favor our tribe! I wonder what the inside of that sect looks like, we never got far enough to see anything…”

The two were caught by some United Element elders sometime ago when they tried seeking it to ask Zhang Dong to accept them as disciples. They were punished harshly by the tribe elders after returning home. It was seen as quite the disgrace at the time, their parents were even worried that the tribe might be annihilated if they offended someone from that overpowered sect. Luckily nothing like that occurred, the sect apparently was quite honorable and didn’t act out in anger against weaker factions like this tribe.

“I bet everything inside is covered with white and green jade! You can hear calm zither music and beautiful elder sisters fly on their swords every day, their long hair just dancing in the wind!”

The two blushed and drooled a bit. They were still young men and were hoping to find a partner in the sect. Cultivators that practiced body refining techniques tended to be more beautiful than your regular people. They got a glimpse of some beautiful elder sisters when they came to pick up the remnants of the Dark Palm sect.

“What if we manage to catch the eye of Fairy Xue?”

“Huh? Do you think Fairy Xue will look twice at an ugly bastard like you? She will be mine!”

Rong replied to Yun while laughing, the two started pushing each other in good faith. The other one just smirked as he retaliated. Zhang Dong’s disciples were quite famous among the younger generation. Liu was considered to be the epitome of a young man while Xue was of a woman, they were seen as perfect disciples both in looks and cultivation. Everyone wanted to meet them and call them senior brother and senior sister.

“I wondered why it stunk so much, it were some smelly brats from the Tatar Tribe.”

Rong’s and Yun’s wrestling was interrupted by some voices. They looked to the voices and spotted some people wearing pelts.

“Scum from the Black Scar Tribe!”

“Who are you calling scum? You trash!”

The two groups faced each other. Both sides had a similar number of people. This was one of the tribes that were in opposition to the Tatar tribe. They lived close to each other and always competed for game or other resources, sometimes there were even bloody battles.

“Brother Rong, we shouldn’t if we battle them here, we might not make it for the sect trial…”

Cheng Yun positioned himself behind Yang Rong and tried pulling him back. On the other side, the Black Scar tribe was acting in a similar way. Their two leaders were at their throats but the others knew that it would be better to conserve their strength for the tests.

“You are lucky that we are close to the esteemed sect grounds! After I secure my spot as an inner disciple I will make your tiny tribe pay for all its done!”

The groups started barking insults at each other but luckily no one was willing to fight just yet. They weren’t willing to lose their chance of getting into the powerful sect. A small injury could very well cause them to fail one of the tests. It was unknown when the next trials would take place, they could be too old to participate if they don’t make it in now.

“You an inner disciple? Hah. You won’t even qualify as a servant!”

“We will see, you should pray to not meet me at the trial!”

The two leaders of the tribes glared at each other before moving away. There was still some more walking to be done but with the other tribe now with them, Yang Rong decided to increase the pace.

A little competition took place as the Black Scar tribesmen realized that the people from the Tatar tribe were trying to get to the renowned sect first. They started off slow by speed walking but soon enough it turned to running. Everyone was giving it all as they sped towards the sect grounds at full throttle.

With the speed increase, it didn’t take them that long to get there. They realized that they were someplace new the moment they got there. The forest vanished and they could see flatland and grass that stretched out for kilometers.

The United Element sect workers cleared a lot of the forest around the area that Zhang Dong designated as the center. The trees were uprooted and the ground was covered with green spirit grass. Through the grass a brick road path was going through, in the distance, the youths could see massive walls stretching far. There was even a moat before that wall and a drawbridge at the entrance.

“We are here, it’s ‘New Spirit Spring City.’”

Cheng Yun said while panting, tired from all the sprinting he was doing for some hours.

“Yes, the sect is past the city and further in!”

The sect was established first, the whole area was sealed off with a grand formation and walls. Still, there were many residents from the old Spirit Spring City remaining. Zhang Dong gave the people two options.

The Zhang Clan would be relocating which was a given. They would welcome them to establish the city here if they wished or move back to the old one. The previous one was destroyed during the quick war that took place. Some of the costs would be covered by the sect and the people could rebuild.

A staggering majority wished to remain with the new sect. The people felt that the sect leader was an honorable man which was proven during the battle that took place. They let all the residents evacuate and were even willing to pay for their losses. Who else than the United Element sect would do such a thing? No one!

They would be lucky if some other overbearing sect would even let them live in one of their towns if they paid them for it. This one would be letting them stay with fewer strings attached. They still would need to pay taxes but they would be given enough time to set up their shops and businesses for that.

The youths looked at the giant walls, they were at least fifteen meters tall and there were even larger guard towers connected to them. They also noticed that they weren’t the first people to arrive. There was already a big line to the large main gate and it was moving very slowly. Above them flying ships and cultivators were whizzing past them and they could even see some of the robes that the United Elements sect wore.

“Hey look there! That person is flying on a big jade sword! He is wearing a blue robe, it must be an inner sect disciple!”

The youths came informed. They even knew about the types of robes that the disciples were wearing, a blue one represented an inner sect disciple which was quite an honor. After getting past the trials they didn’t expect to get anything but a gray robe of an outer sect disciple.

This wasn’t a problem as they knew that you could rise in ranks. How did they know all of this? The sect released some information before the recruitment drive, some of their disciples traveled the lands in hopes of attracting promising young students and maybe some older masters that were looking for a new home.

“Brother Rong, we should get in line before those bastards from the Black Scar tribe get there before us!”

“You are right Brother Yun, we must be there before them, brothers and sisters run for it!”

Everyone ran towards the long line with smiles on their faces. The only thing on their mind was successfully entering the big glorious sect.

Chapter 211

“How does it look?”

“Think this is going to take a while, didn’t expect so many people to show up…”

Two people in United Element sect robes were talking with each other. They were blue with a sort of emblem attached to the shoulder part. This was something that indicated that they were elders and not disciples. There was also the violet color which was above this, it was reserved for core elders and disciples that were even above them in prestige.

One was a large fellow, quite rotund yet muscular. The robe he was wearing had to be custom made to fit around all of that mass. His name was Zhang Hong and he had a moderate amount of fame in the sect from the old days when the Zhang Clan was still going solo.

The other person was a lot more ordinary. His face was plain and his height might have been a bit short. He was also a person that lasted through the old times and his name was Zhang Bao.

The two young men were in one of the guard towers. They were looking down at the space in front of the large gate entrance to the New Spirit Spring City that was considered United Element sect territory. It was the first time the sect would be accepting new disciples into their midst.

Zhang Hong was holding a bag with some pastries and eating while squinting. What he saw was making him worry. Outside the city gates, there were hundreds of thousands, maybe even a million of people. Tents and impromptu made shelters had been set up even a month before the sect trials could take place. The latecomers were continuing to pour in and some of them even camped out in the forest that hadn’t been cut down.

Zhang Bao just gave out a sigh. He had managed to gain an elder’s position and was even an inner sect elder but this honor came with added responsibilities. Their first task would be to get the prospects through the trials and they had to screen everyone, there were no exceptions.

They weren’t the only blue robe elders tending to this. The more potential disciples appeared the more people the sect had to assign. They had to make sure that everything went smoothly. This wasn’t the only gate that was letting people come through, there were three others.

“Luckily the seniors designed that device, it will make this process more bearable…”

Bao nodded while looking at the swarm of people that were getting ready to be accepted through their gate.

“Yes, thank god we have the divine artifact department. We’ll be able to root out the unfit before they can enter the city.”

Hong nodded while munching on some sweets as the two people headed out of the tower, some other people in gray elder robes followed behind them.

After going down they were now at the large gate. It looked more like a medieval castle gate, it also had a draw bridge and iron bars that slammed down shut if they had too. It was also quite thick on the inside, you had to even go through another gate there that acted as a buffer and a checkpoint.

At the middle point there stood a strange looking machine. Similar looking treasure devices were placed at all the other gates. It was cylindrical in shape and there was an entrance from one side. It was connected by some thick wires to a console in a closed section. The people could see someone operating those consoles through a small window that was covered by glass. There were more than one of those devices here and the sect members were performing the last inspection before opening them up.

“Remember the training, move every potential disciple into the scanner artifact. The result will appear on the console and depending on it we will grant them entrance or have them leave. Only the ones chosen by this artifact will be allowed to participate in the rest of the trials.”

Zhang Bao delivered his short speech while moving to the side. He and his brother Hong were responsible for this gate, they would need to stay here and make sure that nothing went wrong. They had permission from the elders in higher positions to use force if anyone got out of line. They didn’t think that anyone would be stupid enough to do this, but there could be a spy among the people and this device apparently could tell this as well.

“Let them in, everyone form a line towards each divine artifact scanner, the faster we finish the sooner you all can go home!”

The people behind the gate started shouting as the metal bars were lifted up into the air. No one dared to move in quite yet though. They waited for a person in a gray robe and with the united element sect’s emblem to go out. He did a short speech explaining what would be happening.

“Please follow the instructions in an orderly fashion. If any fights break out, you will be removed forcefully…”

People just wanted to run through the gate and be done with everything. The people that were at the front had waited for a whole month, just sitting there and meditating. The first person moved forward and was instructed to go into some strange looking artifact. The doors slid open and he found himself in a well-lit space.

‘Please place your hand on the measuring orb.’

The man flinched after hearing a woman’s voice call out to him. He looked around wondering if someone from outside was calling out to him but before he could ask an orb the size of a bowling ball popped out from some kind of hidden slot. It looked to be made from glass or some kind of crystal. The man didn’t react and kept wondering what this was about, the woman’s voice repeated the massage again before he finally reached out to touch the sphere.

The moment he touched it a jolt of electricity ran through his body and he felt weak. He wasn’t able to move a muscle or utter a word. A ray of light appeared above his head in a horizontal line and it started moving downwards. It moved through his entire body, scanning it and feeding that data to the console outside.

A woman from the sect looked at the console. It showed her various biometric data, height, weight, bone structure, and age. Every small detail was revealed thanks to this machine. The woman looked at the numbers and her eyebrows furrowed slightly. There were a few red indicators that didn’t spell anything good for this potential disciple.

“Age 27… Qi Condensation 5th stage… Potential: low… Disposition: Orange…”

She did what she was trained to do and pressed a red button. The large capsule-like device where the man was in opened up. It had a little monitor above it that showed a ‘Failed’ message all in red.

“What, I failed? T-this is impossible!”

The man trembled in utter shock, he wasn’t even able to take any kind of test of might or knowledge. He hadn’t heard of any other sects doing things like this one, most of the time there would at least be some practical trials for the potential disciples to take. At most, they only tested your realm before allowing you to take a trial.

One member from the United Element sect stepped out to the man that started shouting and demanding to be let into the artifact again. He thought that he must have failed when he couldn’t free himself from the scanner in time.

“You lied about your age, this is enough to disqualify you. Leave, or you will be forcefully removed.”

The man from the sect activated his spiritual energy and suppressed the Qi condensation cultivator with his foundation establishment aura. The man that failed the test shrunk back and promptly left, other people looked at him with fear. This sect was using some kind of strange treasure that could even tell your age.

Before the next person could move forward Zhang Hong appeared in front of the gate. He activated his cultivation and shouted out.

“If you are above the age of 25 and still at Qi condensation, don’t even bother. If you are discovered, you will be lashed ten times! Don’t waste mine and the sects time!”

Some people flinched, the sect already announced the age restriction. But some people that were a year or two above 25 still tried coming here. They didn’t think the sect would be that strenuous and if they made it through the tests they would probably forgive them. This was apparently not the case and they would be lashed in front of the crowd. They looked to the crafty looking sect members, they all looked tough and radiated power, getting lashed by them could be deadly.

“Continue with the screening. Next!”

The warning seemed to have worked as some of the people that were standing in the line moved back. Not all of them got discouraged though as after half an hour another person that was past the maximum age popped up. Zhang Hong gave the order and the man was pulled out to the front of the gate. He was lashed ten times, his back was now bruised and bloodied and he was tossed outside. They couldn’t stop people from trying to sneak in but they had to be resolute with their rules.

The scanning continued and quite a bit of people were getting sent home. No one knew what the criteria of making it through were. There were a lot of people to go through and even though most of them were denied some made it in.

‘Passed’

A beautiful woman walked out of the scanner. Every man in the vicinity craned their necks to get a good look at this beauty. She was quite curvaceous and her choice of clothes made the men gulp. Zhang Bao and Hong couldn’t keep their eyes off the female either, besides her beauty there was also something else.

“Foundation establishment… late stage? Potential… high!”

The woman that was reading the scanner looked at the results. The woman here had better stats than a lot of the current sect members. She clearly was suited for an elder’s position and not for a disciple and she wasn’t even that old.

The woman was given the okay to go through, her shapely hips swayed side to side and you could see a whip-like weapon attached to her hip. There was a small gathering of people that made it through the strange artifact inside the city. Other sect members were greeting these people and showing them the way towards the next area.

This woman wouldn’t need to attend that though. People that were of high enough caliber could skip the trials altogether. She only needed to register with the sect and receive her robe. She would then go through a trial period while learning her duties as a senior.

She looked at an emblem that she was given, it had some kind of long number on it which was apparently something that identified her as a member of this sect. She could use this emblem to gather sect merit which she could trade in for various resources and even spirit stones.

“Interesting… He really made it big. Shouldn’t have let him escape that time…”

The woman gave out a sigh while mumbling to herself. She had managed to make it inside this sect, her new life was finally starting and she would be making the best of it. Her frowning face changed into a smirk as she tossed the emblem that looked like a small shield up into the air. She caught it right back before placing it on her shoulder just as the other people in the sect did.

“Time to start a new life!”

She was promised her own cultivation residence, she wasn’t sure if it would be a cave or a building quite yet. While she left other people were still getting analyzed. The lines moved forward slowly and more people were failing than passing. The testing would continue for multiple days as there were just too many people outside the city. The next part would be the practical trials that would force even more people to prematurely retire.

Chapter 212

“You can do it, senior brother!”

The leader from the Black Scar tribe that was previously at odds with Yang Rong walked into the scanner tube. The other members from his clan looked at him with anticipation. Rong wasn't far behind as he also was the first one to get into another measuring device that was standing to the side.

The machines took some time to process the information and the two stepped out into the open. A ‘Passed’ in green letters appeared over each of the cylindrical treasures as the two went out. Each one of them wanted to laugh at their enemy when they failed but both passed at the same time.

“Please move, there are other people waiting to take the test.”

One of the members from the sect had to move in as Yang Rong kept glaring at the person from the Black Scar tribe. Both of them made it in so they headed inside the city, they stopped right outside the entrance and they waited for more of their tribe members to appear.

“I bet more of my brothers will pass than yours!”

“As if!”

Yang Rong replied while crossing his arms over one another and glancing back into the gate corridor. He had made it through the first test but he was still worried about his tribe members.

“Brother Rong I made it through”

Cheng Yun strutted out right after Yang Rong which caused the person from the Black Scar tribe to frown. They weren’t the only three that made it through, each side ended up with 10 people passing which halved their numbers.

“This isn’t the only trial, we will see who remains till the end you trash!”

The two enemy tribes slung some profanities at each other before walking away. They all finally looked into the city, it was a lot different from their old fashioned village. The houses here were mostly made from stone and bricks which was the biggest difference. The villages used wood for their houses and straw for the roofs.

The people that passed the initial scanning test weren’t left to their own devices on the inside. Everyone was guided to the city square that was quite spacious. When Yun and Rong arrived they spotted something that they recognized.

“Isn’t that?”

“Yes it is!”

It was a statue of the renowned Zhang Dong. He was standing gallantly in his tight robe while looking out into the distance. The statue was located in the middle of the city square and was in the middle of a large fountain. There were two other people standing next to him both on the sides while he was in the middle.

“I think that’s the Senior’s wife Elder Feng Liena.”

“Yes and that man over there must be Huo Qiang, the three Elemental Lords!”

These three were considered the founding members of this sect. This came with some titles that they or the closest people to them thought of. Zhang Dong had garnered some titles like ‘The Lord of Lightning.’ Huo Qiang was the ‘Tyrannical Inferno Fist’ and Feng Liena was the ‘Mistress of the Winds’.

Zhang Dong was sometimes also referred to as the ‘Lightning Emperor’ but that name was a bit problematic due to the Azure Emperor’s existence. At most they could call him the ‘Lightning King’ otherwise they might offend people in that camp as they couldn’t be two emperors in an empire.

The two youths looked around, there were many people here close to their age. They were standing or sitting while just waiting. The person who guided them here told them that they needed to stay here for now. They would be provided food but no shelter for the night.

“This is probably another test, we need to be resolute!”

They all nodded and sat down in their lotus positions. They would use this time to relax and wait. There were still many people waiting to get tested and it would probably take days until everyone was processed.

Everyone took their time to examine the surroundings they were in. This was the new Spirit Spring City that was built after the short war with the Dark Palm sect took place.

The buildings all looked sturdy and had an oriental feel to them. They mostly had hip roofs or xie shan roofs. The area they were waiting in had some parks with flowing water and small bridges outside the square. They could also see some larger pagoda-like structures in the distance sprinkled here and there. They were akin to modern-day skyscrapers and probably could house thousands of people in them.

This city was owned by the sect, but it wasn’t populated by the sect members. They lived inside the sect compound that was further in. Even from here, they could see another wall that was twice as tall as the one outside the city. This was where the real sect resided and where they would be taking the trials.

Night came and everything became well lit. There were many soldiers patrolling the area that were mostly in Qi condensation but there were some others that were above it. These people had different uniforms, they were dark blue but not like the inner sect disciples.

“I think they are part of that ‘police’ unit.”

One of the people from the Tatar Tribe spoke up, after the sect rebuilt the police force was reestablished. The only change being that it was now mostly populated by the people from the city. The top bras were made of outer sect disciples and the police chief was at least a core formation expert.

These people in those strange uniforms were all spread throughout the city. There was quite a bit of them out as they were worried that some of the trainees were going to cause some trouble. They were there to break up fights that might occur between the participants. One such fight was taking place right about now but it was swiftly resolved. The rowdy cultivators that couldn’t follow the rules were promptly kicked out. This was enough to keep everyone else silent as they still wanted to make the cut.

It took another two days for all of the participants to get examined at the city gates. The moment everyone was at the square the fountain sculptures started rumbling. The eyes of the Sect Patriarch started glowing and his head started turning.

“Welcome potential brothers and sisters, we welcome you to this Trial!”

A beam of light shot out from the statue and produced a hologram of a beautiful woman. This wasn’t one of the inferior holograms that the Zhang Clan made all those years ago. This one looked very lifelike. The person was a young woman in a violet robe and snow-like hair. Her characteristic hair color gave her away as most people knew that it was the fabled Zhang Xue.

“Fairy Xue!”

“Such beauty!”

“Is she really here?”

“H-how could this be?”

Everyone’s mouth went agape after they saw the hologram projection of the beauty. She floated above and looked like a giant which made everyone realize that this wasn’t probably her real body.

“Everyone here will have the chance of being accepted into our sect. The trials inside might be harsh on your body and soul, if you aren’t willing to suffer through them you are free to leave.”

Everyone nodded and was unwilling to go back now, there was far too much at stake. A sect that could create such a treasure must have been quite powerful and resourceful. Everyone felt invigorated as they continued to listen to the beauty.

“Good, listen well. Our sect members will escort you to the trial area, please follow their instructions at all costs…”

The introduction continued for a while as Zhang Xue listed out some rules. The participants were to listen to the seniors and do whatever they demanded of them. They could quit at any time, they just needed to voice it out and then they would be removed outside. There wouldn’t just be your regular strength-based tests. There would be other various ways you’d be allowed to get in, even with a lower realm than on average.

“That is all, please follow the instructions.”

The hologram fizzled out and turned into multiple colorful lights. Zhang Dong statue’s eyes stopped glowing and they went back into looking into the distance.

“This is it, brothers, let us depart!”

“Yes!”

Everyone shouted in unison. The participants here were all hopeful, they had made it through the initial screening so there shouldn’t be any problems on the inside. At least that is what they all thought.

They soon arrived at the large gate that would take them into the sect grounds. It was made out of white jade and it was absolutely massive. There were some intricate carvings on it depicting strange monsters like dragons, phoenixes, and qilins. The moment they arrived those doors started to part. As they parted everyone noticed that there was a single person right in the middle.

He had similar snow-white hair as the beauty that they had seen in the square. He was quite handsome and was even standing on a large green crystal sword. He flew forward while everyone watched, his ability of flight gave away his cultivation level to the people here. Everyone did the natural thing and clasped their hands while greeting this senior.

“I welcome you to the sect, please follow me inside.”

He did a quick turn and moved inside. He was standing like a grand pillar with his hands behind his back and a stoic expression on his face. The crowd of people didn’t ask any questions and quickly moved inside. Even they knew who this man was and it would spell death if they offended him in any shape or form.

From the one million people remained about one fifth. The screening process was quite brutal on these participants. This was still far too many people, the sect could at most accept up to a hundred thousand. This was their first recruitment drive so they would be a bit more lenient with their first new batch.

“Listen up!”

“This is the United Element Sect! We do not accept people without talent that can’t offer the sect anything in return. We expect you to work and work hard! These tests will prepare you for your future life as a disciple, if you show us your worth, you will be rewarded!”

Zhang Liu performed a little introduction speech, listing a couple of things that Zhang Xue might have left out. He then pointed the participants in a direction, what they saw there shocked them quite a bit.

Past the gate was another wide-open space, walls were closing off the view of most of the buildings and there were many people in sect robes standing. This wasn’t the most interesting part though, there were many circular looking contraptions lined out. It didn’t take them long to figure out what they were for as one activated.

“I-is that a teleportation gate?”

“My lord, this sect is really a grand sect!”

The people became abuzz with chatter. Teleportation technology was something that wasn’t available to the regular clans spread throughout the land. Only powerful sects like the old Dark Palm sect were able to gather enough resources to build one. This cemented the United Elements sect’s position in their hearts and made them crave their knowledge and strength even more.

“As you might have heard, combat trials aren’t the only way of proving yourself. Alchemy, blacksmithing, healing, herb gathering, and many more. Each gate will take you to a different trial…”

Liu continued explaining, there were multiple trials and the participants had a limited time to pass them. They could abandon trials they were failing at and for instance, try pill creation instead of battling combat puppets. There were many ways of passing the tests and they needed to prove their worth by getting merit points.

“Each trial has a set number of merit points assigned to them if you manage to gather 100 points you will pass!”

The potential disciples looked at the teleportation gates that started activating one after another. Soon the blue light filled the entire area, the strange sound of those gates brought goosebumps of anticipation.

“The trial will commence now, I wish you luck, and may we see each other in the future!”

Zhang Liu nodded before taking off, the trial would have a time limit of a week and would probably bring down the number of participants to one-tenth of what it was before, maybe even lower.

Chapter 213

“Good day Patriarch.”

“Glory to the United Element sect!!”

Zhang Dong was walking through one of the corridors in the main sect sanctuary building. He nodded at the people that greeted him and continued forward. The sect recruitment trials were taking place at this very moment and he wanted to check upon them.

Five years had passed since this sect had been created. Everything had been built to completion before they decided on opening their doors. It took a bit longer than expected but he was also busy with his own personal business.

He was a married man and didn’t want to waste away only cultivating for the rest of his life. He made sure to have a good relationship with Feng Liena and the two were seen walking hand in hand quite often. The culmination of their relationship finally resulted in an offspring, the same one he was now carrying in his arms.

The one-year-old was looking around, her eyes sparkling and green like emeralds. Her hair was similarly pink like her mother’s but a lot lighter, this probably due to her father’s hair being snow white. The Sect leader was known to bring his child out and the sect members never missed a beat to compliment him on his cute little daughter.

“Greetings Patriarch! I see little Xiu is looking as precious as ever!”

A couple of female cultivators were walking past and spotted their sect leader walking around. They instantly surrounded him, the small child being the talking point. With the years the people from the three clans managed to figure out Zhang Dong’s true nature. Which was quite stoic and docile, he never got mad at anyone and didn’t think much about face. He cared more about his family members than himself and would come to their defense more than towards his own.

He was also known as a doting father and as a good husband. Zhang Dong looked at the group of ladies and then to his cute daughter that was looking up to him with a smile. His face started twitching as he couldn’t help but smile back, this didn’t go unnoticed by the people from the sect.

“Yes! Isn’t she the cutest!”

He gave the little girl a couple of gentle head pats but didn’t offer her up to the group of women. He remembered his daughter crying a bit when someone pinched one of her cheeks. The sect member in question then tried to appease this fault by slitting his belly with a sword. To not have a similar encounter he decided to just not let other people touch his child. This only made everyone think that he was being overprotective.

‘She is getting sleepy, I should go back. Better not have her sleeping outdoors.’

He took off with his daughter in his arms, the little child’s head started wobbling around but he stabilized it with his aura. They slowly flew through the air while taking in the sights. The 10 million large city that used to be Spirit Spring City was moved here along with all of its residents.

He always took in the wondrous sights of this world. The city was five times as big now and still growing, they were ever-expanding. The first sect trials were taking place and after they got more members they could finally start operating like a normal sect.

“Bwo bwaaa…”

The girl said while pointing at something in the distance. Zhang Dong just placed his hand on those pink locks and ruffled them up a bit. The girl protested and squirmed but nothing could save her from those head pats of fatherly love.

He descended towards his own residence that was floating right above the large castle structure. He didn’t want to stand out at first but he managed to recreate the technology that would allow their structures to float. His advisors said that it would be best if he set up his own residence above everyone else, it would show that he is there protecting everyone from above.

He finally relented and had his sect build him a pure white castle that was fit for a shogun. They planted cherry blossoms all over the place as his wife was quite fond of them. She also favored the more Japanese looking kimonos than what you would see the other people wearing. This was probably due to the secret texts of her clan having those types of esthetics.

He did finally get to see her secret stash after they got married as everything from the Feng Clan was put up into their sects mega vault. It housed quite a bit of their treasures and spirit stones. If a sect member had enough merit points he could head over to the treasury department and get a pass for an item.

The text as he had thought was drawn mangas. He didn’t recognize them or the art style. He came to the conclusion that they were drawn by someone that just as he came here from another world. The plotlines in those were your usual rom-com scenes with ecchi parts included. They were heavily focused on the tanned gyarus and ganguro girls for some reason. Each story had one as the main heroine and the male lead always went for them in the end.

He was sure that he wasn’t the only person that came from earth here so this wasn’t much of a shock anymore. The massage that the person he heard after he touched the cube was still fresh on his mind. He wasn’t able to find any more of those places after going through the lands again. He didn’t venture outside his sect yet as he was afraid to leave his wife that was in labor.

“Good morning~”

He heard a sweet womanly voice from afar and looked down. There she was, his beautiful wife. She looked a bit rounder than usual and there was a reason for it, there was another little person growing in her belly. He already knew that it would be a boy this time around, even Feng Liena could scan herself with her spiritual sense to tell the gender.

This was quite the joyous moment for the whole sect as they had a legitimate heir to it. Zhang Dong was considered to be the king, little Xiu was the princess and this boy would be the crown prince. The people were quite surprised by both the children as it was quite rare for nascent soul cultivators to ever have children. One reason was that most of them were far too old for such things and the other one that birth was a lot harder on the woman’s and the baby's body.

“Bwaba~”

The little girl called out and stretched her hands out towards her mom. Feng Liena just smiled and moved closer taking the child into her hands and giving her a big smooch on the cheek.

“Yes, it’s your mommy.”

Zhang Dong smiled slightly as he saw his wife rub her nose with his cute little daughter. He moved closer and placed his hand on her protruding belly. The time of the birth was close and it would probably put a strain on his wife.

“How are you feeling? Are you hungry? Are you sure you should be out here? You might catch a col...”

Before he could finish his sentence a finger was placed against his mouth. Feng Liena looked up to him with a smile on her face while chuckling.

“I’m fine, this child will be fine as well, I know my husband won’t let anything bad happen to the both of us~”

Zhang Dong nodded while rubbing his neck. He was concerned about his family, finally he could relate to the adults who were responsible for their own children. Luckily with his healing abilities, he could help out during the childbirth, he had done it during the first one successfully and was planning on repeating this procedure.

“Now let us eat, the maids made dumplings and they roasted a spirit duck for my little glutton.”

Feng Liena pinched the side of Zhang Dong’s belly which made him flinch to the side. He wanted to return the favor but couldn’t due to the baby in belly situation.

“Oh, you…”

The two-headed into the house and started chatting. He gave his sleeping potato of a daughter to one of the maids that helped her into her baby bed. He still needed to check up on the sect test so after giving his wifey a smooch he flew outside. His destination, the command center, or at least that’s what he liked to call it.

Without the child in hand, he was a lot faster, no one even spotted him whizzing by in silence. He appeared unannounced and opened the door and gave the people inside quite the scare as always.

“D-Donger please stop doing that, you’ll make your grandfather suffer from cultivation backlash.”

“Hah, like you’ll die from something like that, heard your wife count increased again, maybe giving you that cultivation technique was a bad idea…”

Zhang Dong narrowed his eyes, he was looking at his grandfather that should be over 200 years old. The problem was that he looked like a 25-year-old man. After the library building was set up for the disciples he had put every technique that he knew in there, this along with his disguising technique that was now even improved into heavenly grade.

His old casanova of a grandfather had come across it and used it to sire even more children. Now no one could even prove that it was him sleeping around, his old wives were at an uproar. He had also progressed into the great circle of core formation with the help of his grandson and would probably make it into the nascent soul level soon. Zhang Dong was afraid to prolong this man’s life as another thousand years could bring a million kids out of wedlock.

‘Maybe when he dies half of the world's population will be related to him?’

He shook his head and went back to business. He looked at one of the screens that was in his command center of his. He had gone with a very futuristic look for it that made it look like some kind of command ship from old sci-fi shows.

On the monitor, he could see some people sitting in front of pill furnaces. They were sweating while creating pills as part of the trial. He watched as one pill furnace exploded and the explosion had to be contained by one of the judges. The person that had failed could continue but some of his merit points would be deducted each time they failed.

On another screen, he could see the puppet corridor where a person was trying to squeeze through it. The many puppet soldiers were keeping the youth away from reaching the destination but somehow he made it till the end. His body looked all bruised and battered but he looked to be satisfied with himself.

‘Hm, not bad, that’s a good expression he has.’

On another, there was a large pit of lava. This trial was also designed by him, he got the idea from the platformer games that he used to play. Some of the platforms were moving around it and you had to time your jumps correctly so you could get to the end. You could also show overwhelming physical ability and make it through some other way. The lava on the ground looked more dangerous than it was and the contestants wouldn’t die if they fell.

He continued walking through the room while looking at the various tests. There was even a scoreboard showing the current contestants and how well they were doing. He didn’t recognize the names of the people there but he would have to give the top three medals for good placements.

“Oh and this one is?”

He asked while one of the people answered.

“This is the waiting room for the people that passed on the merit of having a high cultivation.”

Apparently the people here had good results from the scanner he designed. It scanned for potential, age, their alignment, and calculated if they would be a good fit for his honorable sect. There weren’t that many people there, only twenty but they could be trained up if they decided to invest.

‘Wait… what is she doing here…’

He raised his brow as he recognized someone, it was a woman he would probably never forget for the rest of his life. Her curves could give his wife a run for her money. His face twitched for a second she had already made it inside the sect, would his wife get mad if she knew this?

Chapter 214

Zhang Dong was looking at someone that he knew, someone that he had been intimate with. She was only a one night stand but it was an experience that he remembered all to this day. The woman’s name was Lan Fei and she was a merchant that he saved the first time he arrived at Moonlight City.

She was apparently a candidate for an elder. This role became available after you reached the late stage of foundation establishment. In the lesser clans, this was already enough to be its leader. Here at most you would be allowed to be the lowest ranking senior. In the future core formation practitioners and up would only be allowed as elders. They still didn’t have enough people for that jump.

He could see that Lan Fei took his advice to heart and was now using a whip weapon. She did have talent in that as well as high potential. This wasn’t that important though, there were other thoughts going through his head.

‘Uh… will Liena be angry if she meets a girl that I’ve been with before?’

He was a married man and already had kids. Normally having an ex-girlfriend wasn’t a big deal but he wasn’t sure how his lovely wife would react to this news. He didn’t want to lie to her but he also didn’t want to bring this information out into the open either.

“Oh interested in that one, Dong’er?”

Zhang Jin called out while glancing at the monitor that had the elder candidates in it. He had a somewhat similar face to Zhang Dong in his younger form but was slightly shorter.

“Gramps… keep it in the pants… you can’t be doing this with our sect members. Think about your position...”

Zhang Dong wanted to give his grandfather a smack to the face. Ever since he got his hands on this transformation technique rumors started spreading. Some people even confused the old fart with him which got him in hot water with his wife. Luckily he only had to pull the old pervert over for an explanation and it ended at that. His wife trusted him enough and didn’t make a fuss.

‘Think I’m worrying too much…’

He thought to his child and to his wife. They had grown more fond of each other through the years and even started calling each other cute names. He was the hubby and she was the wifey.

“What, want her all for yourself?”

Zhang Dong narrowed his eyes and moved his fist up into the air. Zhang Jin just started laughing as he ran away acting as if he was a teenager.

“Anyway… Is everything proceeding as planned? Were there any issues with the artifacts?”

He asked while turning to the other sect members in the room. Everyone here was already used to how the sect leader and his grandfather interacted and were relaxed around the two. One of the people moved forward with some papers and started giving a report.

“Everything is proceeding as we prepared Patriarch, we will be concluding the trials with your speech as we agreed upon. The inauguration ceremony and the pledge is going to be held a day after we are finished with the trials.”

Zhang Dong nodded at the report, the sect member even mentioned a couple of people by name that were quite promising. He was only interested in the ceremony that was going to be held after they gathered the disciples as he had to make a speech. He had kind of grown accustomed to things like this by now but that didn’t mean that he liked to do it.

The way this sect was handled was a bit unconventional. First, every disciple was required to take classes on things like reading and ethics. They had created large buildings that were similar to how schools back in his old world looked. The schools were separated and named differently to somehow produce an atmosphere of competition. There would also be regular competitions hosted between the schools, the ones that came out on top would be rewarded accordingly to their achievements.

He was slightly worried that some of the created schools would fall back behind the others. This was something unfortunate but it had to happen to give others motivation not to fail and to work harder.

There would be a four-year curriculum and then they would graduate becoming true disciples. The recruitment drive would then resume to get new students while the old ones started their work at the sect facilities. He deliberated on having a yearly infusion of new students to produce some upper and lower classmates. This would strain their budget too much as handling so many people each year was too much on this growing sect.

He remained in the command center and looked through the monitors some more. He could see people failing and succeeding. It was hard to watch the ones that didn’t make it, the expressions of disappointment and sadness were plastered on their faces. Some were even breaking down into tears after getting removed from the trials.

He didn’t like this part of his work. If he could he would accept everyone into his sect and form one big happy family. This wasn’t feasible, his sect might have been a large faction but they still had limited resources. If they started sharing it with just anyone then they would just spread themselves too thin. He still needed to contend with the other powerful sects but he was slowly building up to a point where they wouldn’t need to.

After going through the screens he decided to go check how things were going in the ‘true’ sect. Zhang Dong needed to perform a small task there. He was going find this task in his ‘Dimensional Regalia’ immortal treasure that had gone through a slight change.

He was the item’s master so as long as he was within a ten-kilometer radius of it he could just teleport in. He didn’t use that feature though as he wasn’t in a rush, he just used what the other sect members did, a teleportation gate. These handy artifacts were now widely spread throughout the sect.

They had connected all the cities that were owned by them. Moonlight City, Red Lotus City, Qingliang City, and others. In reality, all of those large megalopolises that were situated in their land belonged to them. The sect didn’t invest in all of them though and only set up smaller outer sect bases in the ones at strategic locations.

The original Dark Palm sect area shrunk down and they only needed to contend with two other parties at the borders and not with three. This was not due to one of them having perished, no the Dragon gate sect just took more of the treasures instead of the land while the other two split it between them. The United Element sect also didn’t have anyone bordering them from behind as that was where the forest area where spiritual energy was low.

He used one of the teleportation gates that were available to the elders. They all could be accessed and operated thanks to the shield like emblem that he had designed. It was similar to the ones that the new disciples would receive, each one acted as sort of a smart key. The higher your rank the more access to the sect's resources you would have. You could also spend merit points to gain temporary access for a limited time to some of the facilities. This was made so that the new disciples actually worked for their progress and not have everything handed to them on a silver platter.

The gate churned with spiritual energy and he disappeared into it. On the inside, there were already people there to greet him.

“Junior greets the Patriarch!”

There were guards placed on each teleportation station and just as any other job in the sect you would get merit points for performing this task. Zhang Dong went a bit capitalistic with his sect but it was working as the sect members were happy to work in exchange for resources. These being cultivation techniques as well as pills and combat weapons.

“At ease.”

He nodded while going in. The gate that he walked through was located at a steep hill that overlooked the pocket dimension in the dimensional regalia. He was looking at the spot where the old dorm building stood before. The old building was renovated into a huge pagoda that was several stories high.

The air around here felt different, it was due to the siphoning formation that was absorbing most of the spiritual energy from the spirit vein. The Qi here was more comparable to what the largest sects at the very top were used to. The Dark Palm sect and the three other factions in the area could only dream of something like this.

The small floating island that was only a couple kilometers in diameter when he first found it had changed into a giant landmass. It was similar to the size of a continent from his old world and it was still growing. By his calculations, the treasure would become complete when this landmass fully formed and it would probably be the size of a regular planet. This was the true power of an immortal treasure, something on the scale of a small world!

There were no enemies here so the sect didn’t need to build any defensive structures. Most of them were built to help the core disciples to train. They also kept most of their spirit herbs in here as the high concentration of Qi let them have bountiful harvests. The more energy the treasure absorbed the more lively it got.

Even without their help, trees, grass and all sorts of plants were beginning to grow. It was as if this small world was healing itself, gently regrowing what it had once lost. There were even some spirit beasts appearing here and there that could be used as food and wielded quite potent meat. They were friendly as well, they reacted to the orders of the one that was the master of this treasure, Zhang Dong’s thoughts. He could even order them to attack the people here as if he was the master of this whole small world.

He wasn’t here to watch the spirit herbs growing though, no he was here to spend some spirit points. The time had come to help one of his more trusted sect members to make the jump. He moved towards one of the larger hills in the distance, there he spotted four people waiting for him.

“Hey Senior Brother, you’re finally here!”

Huo Qiang called out while waving at Zhang Dong. Next to him was another muscular man, his father Huo Gang. The man that butted heads with Zhang Dong looked a lot stronger than before and he was also radiating the aura of a nascent soul master. The two had long buried the hatchet.

The third person was a woman that looked to be about forty but her true age was a lot higher. Her name was Feng Suyin, she was the strongest senior beside his wife from the Feng Clan side and she was also at the nascent soul level. Her skin was light brown and she had the usual gyaru features along with the curves that they all had. Her hair was platinum-blond and the makeup was strange to look at.

He wasn’t here for those three though, no he was here for the third person. A man that had stayed loyal to the Zhang Clan for quite some time, his name was Zhang Zhi. He had finally reached the pinnacle of core formation and was ready to take the next step towards the nascent soul level. He would be the first one besides him that had reached that level from the Zhang Clan, which for him was quite the honor.

“Greetings Patriarch!”

Zhang Zhi cupped his fists with vigor. He was sitting down in a lotus position with his chest bare. Before he would be allowed the step into the nascent soul he needed to get cleansed. Yes, Matt still used his system points to clear the impurities of the people that were close to going past the core formation level. This was one of the better uses he could spend all those passive points he was getting from his large territory.

“Well then, are you ready? This might feel a bit funny…”

The other three nascent soul elders chuckled to themselves as they all had gone through this cleansing. It was something that would be hard to forget, Zhang Zhi nodded, and soon Zhang Dong’s hand was placed on the sitting man’s back. Soon the inner core disciples that were training close to this spot could hear a man’s sensual moans...

Chapter 215

“Ohhh...t-that f-feels…”

“Ahhh…P-patriarch...”

The strange stuttering sounds of a grown man were heard from atop of the mountain peak. Matt didn’t like this part of the process of cleansing his sect members from impurities. If he performed it fast they would feel an excruciating amount of pain. If he did it slow it wouldn’t be bad, it was actually the reverse, it felt good.

He did it the first time with Feng Liena and thought that she might have exaggerated her reaction. After he went through Huo Qiang’s father and the second member from the Feng Clan he noticed that she might have underperformed her reaction. This was why Zhang Zhi here was moaning out like a little girl while he had to pretend that he was doing something. The process of cleansing the impurities happened via his system window but he had to pretend that he was doing it himself.

“Sect L-leader n-no more, I can’t…”

‘It would be nice if you stopped shouting out my title while you are moaning dude…’

He thought to himself while Zhang Zhi’s toes continued to curl up. The black ooze that he discharged had a really bad smell to it and he had to be in touching distance of it. Huo Gang and the lady from the Feng clan were looking at the moaning man with mixed expressions while remembering their own procedure. The only curious look was on Huo Qiang as his process was less than stellar and mostly painful.

Luckily this didn’t take so long and he had learned from the time with his wifey that he should stand behind the targets. Having them sit down on the ground was also something he came up with so that they wouldn’t lean on him.

“There, now go clean yourself up.”

Zhang Dong pulled his palm back, it felt sticky and some black goop was on it. Zhang Zhi almost face planted to the ground during the procedure. Now he was just panting while blushing. Zhang Dong used a moist towelette to wipe his hands and then moved down from the peak. While Zhang Zhi was cultivating Huo Gang and Feng Suyin would act as dharma protectors. They would keep anyone away while their junior took that large step forward. This was a delicate process and if he got interrupted he could suffer cultivation regression or even die.

“With junior brother Zhi that will put us on even grounds with the other sects, don’t you think so, senior brother Dong?”

Huo Qiang floated next to Zhang Dong and proclaimed while grinding wide. The man was a battle junky so if it was possible he would like to cause some trouble with the other sects and fight some of their nascent soul elders.

“With him we only have six nascent soul elders, if we go by what the Dark Palm sect had…We still fall short by four regular elders, that’s not counting the hidden masters that they had.”

Zhang Dong calculated that most of the sects had about ten official nascent soul seniors in their midst. These were only the ones that were active, each sect also had hidden monsters that could be stronger than the current sect master.

“That is true, but with our immortal cultivation manuals we won’t have trouble trashing those old farts even two on one!”

Huo Qiang performed a smack to his chest as always. This was actually a good point, even though they had lower numbers their nascent soul elders were far stronger than a regular cultivator at the early stage of the nascent soul realm. They were more in line with a middle stage cultivator that practiced a regular heavenly grade cultivation method. They also didn’t need to spend long to cultivate their soul-beasts either.

About five years had passed since the war with the Dark Palm sect. He had since made some progress and reached the middle stage a couple of months ago. Now even without his powered-up form, he could battle a regular late stage cultivator. If he fully let loose then he could contend with someone in the great circle.

Huo Qiang and Feng Liena had progressed further as well but both weren’t quite there. Liena was about halfway into the middle stage while Qiang had progressed by about 70%. He could clearly see the numbers on his system screen so they had to be true. He attributed Liena’s slower progress due to the pregnancies. He also gave her a little boost here and there and she was still behind Qiang.

“You might be right there brother Qiang but it would be better to not show them our fangs just yet. Appear weak when you are strong, and strong when you are weak. Always better to catch your enemy off guard otherwise, they might prepare some contingencies against us. We might suffer the same fate as those Dark Palm lunatics if we don’t prepare well.”

Matt was somewhat convinced that they should be able to at least tie if they went against one of those three sects. They had also increased the number of their core formation elders by improving all of their cultivation manuals all the way up to heaven grade. This was of course only for the ones that were core disciples and for some of the inner ones.

They just had to train them up as they were just falling behind the others far too much. This brought some trouble with corruption which they would have to clear up with time. Some of the new core formation experts were a bit drunk with power and sometimes caused trouble to other people outside the sect. Matt even had to create a special sect division of internal affairs to root out any corruption.

He gave the position of the chief there to the person that was most loyal to him, Zhang Zhi. His promotion would become official after he broke through to the nascent soul realm. Just as all the rest of the grand elders he possesses an immortal grade cultivation technique. The soul beast that would be formed from it would look like an evolved version of a water serpent. Similar to the one his clan used as a formation.

He had to spend some points he had gained to upgrade. Luckily the land that he was considered the owner of was a lot larger now. It encompassed millions of people now and brought in quite a lot of spirit points. The increase in cultivation level of his people also made his points jump up.

“If you say so, Senior brother…”

Huo Qiang slumped his shoulders forward, he was itching for a fight. Ever since he reached the nascent soul level he didn’t have a chance to have a good fight. He was stuck patrolling the border regions and giving the opposing sects the stink eye.

“If you ever change your mind be sure to get me first! You can even activate one of these treasures!”

Qiang flicked the earring from his left ear lobe. It was another treasure that Matt had made, the teleportation feature was just far too good to not use. His elder members could be teleported into battle whenever he needed them. There were even waypoints in their territory that they could instantly appear in.

The other sects would probably be really surprised if they try sneaking in to only find themselves against every single nascent soul elder from the United Element sect. These treasures came in various shapes and sizes but they had a limit to them and needed time to recharge. He could activate them to bring his allies to him, or they could send out a signal when they were in distress to alert everyone. Then the others could just teleport to them.

“I’ll be sure to do that.”

Zhang Dong laughed at his overzealous friend. The only thing he was good at was fighting but he felt reassured that he had him on his side. Matt was planning to stop paying the tributes to the other sects soon as they were slowly becoming self-sufficient. A show of force might be required when the time came but he wanted to wait some more till they were done with the new recruits.

Zhang Dong inspected the rest of the Dimensional Regalia while Huo Qiang went back to training. Thanks to this place being so large he could let loose, his training ground had long turned into a desert riddled with holes and molten lava. Matt also had his own section to train in and cultivate, the lightning energies in that spot were quite volatile.

These pockets were rich in elemental energies which could even be used by the future disciples. Zhang Xue and Liu would be allowed to absorb the golden lighting that appeared there from time to time. Both of them were in the early stage of core formation now and their hair was fully white just like their master’s.

‘Nothing out of the ordinary here, I should get back home.’

There wasn’t much for him to do besides cultivating and making artifacts for the sect. His crafting system was able to copy weapons which just made him have less to do. Thanks to this he could flood the market with affordable goods but he made sure not to sell his wares to his enemies. Most of the weapons and armor that he created would be used by his sect disciples and the seniors.

Before he left he could see a cleaned Zhang Zhi sitting on a mountain peak. He was already back at it and cultivating. He vanished through the gate that he came through and flew right back home. His lovely wife and cute daughter were both waiting for him. The child was getting spoon-fed some baby food by one of their housemaids.

Her mother would probably like to perform this task but she was out of commission due to having quite a large bloated belly. When he arrived he was greeted by smiles, the worries of the day seemed to disappear the moment he saw the mother and daughter duo. Time flew by fast and it soon was nighttime. He watched his wife and child fall asleep before going out to get some fresh air.

He went out onto the balcony and looked off into the distance. The recruits were giving their all even now as there weren’t any breaks even for sleep.

‘I hope nothing goes wrong…’

He was holding onto a parchment. It had a golden seal on it and the symbol of the Dragon Gate sect. This sect was the friendliest one from the three, with the Limitless Sword Society one always acting rudely towards him and his sect.

The piece of paper was an invitation. He was to go into their territory and take part in a sort of banquet. It was something of a get together for the more powerful sects. Besides the three sects that he knew there would be others from all around. This was a good opportunity to gain allies but also to gain enemies. He knew how these people operated and just as there was a fool trying to start a fight with him at his wedding, someone could appear there.

He was in no position to show weakness now. He knew how strong he was and he was certain that he could beat any of those three Patriarchs in a one on one fight. He still wanted to avoid any animosity if it was possible but he couldn’t show that his sect was weak. This part of this society didn’t change, the strong got stronger and the weak got weaker. If push came to shove he might have to show some of his hand.

‘Being the one making the big decisions is hard…’

“Hubby?”

He heard Feng Liena calling out to him. He turned his face and saw her concerned expression.

“Is something wrong?”

He moved over and gave the woman a smooch on the cheek before answering.

“Everything is fine, just don’t want to leave the sect grounds while you are still in this condition.”

He placed his hand on her belly which made Liena chuckle. He needed to leave for a few days but the protective formations along with the multiple nascent soul masters should be able to protect his pregnant wife.

“Everything will be fine, a certain worrying husband has created many defensive treasures for this wife of his.”

She showed off a couple more rings and earrings that Zhang Dong had fashioned for her during these years and chuckled. The two smiled at each other and went back to bed, the two moons lit up the dark night. While they slept the disciple candidates continued to fight for their spot in the sect soon a new chapter in their life would be starting.

Chapter 216

Cheng Yun and Yang Rong were sprawled out on the hard rocky ground. They were panting, sweat was running down their foreheads and their robes were all ripped up. The continuous panting was only drowned out by the sound of the teleportation gates. The artifacts were active and produced a sort of humming noise.

The two youths weren’t the only ones here. The tired bodies of other disciple candidates were similarly unmoving on the cold ground. The test had finally ended and now the only thing that was left was to count the merit points. Most of the people knew if they had already passed or not as there was a certain scanning device that would show you the number you had. The contestant just needed to go over to it and have it scan their emblem to show the number of merits.

The two weren’t quite sure, they were ejected from the last trial they were taking. They were frantically trying to pass and didn’t use the scanner to tell how many merit points they had. The two had to settle on the combat and physical trials. There were various other ways of passing even with no fighting ability whatsoever.

There were trials where you could show your knowledge about formations. There were even ones that required you to read and write as that was a skill that wasn’t that common in this world. The sect wasn’t only looking for powerful fighters, they also needed intelligent prospects that were good at management. Strength with no reason behind it wasn’t something this sect wanted.

A large gong sounded which indicated the end of the sect trials. The gates started to forcefully eject the participants that were still on the inside. Those areas where the tests were being held were specially built with an ejection feature. This was mostly for safety reasons as the people inside would be brought outside if their life signals dropped too low. If such a thing happened the contestants would be taken away into one of the clinics for a checkup. Matt didn’t really want people to be dying when trying out for his sect.

After a long week of trials and tribulations, the potential disciples that had passed would finally become part of the sect. They would not become true disciples though, they would first have to go through a trial period in the sect academy. They would be given the title of trial disciples and could always fail during the years the school was active. They could at most be held back by a year there, if they didn’t manage to progress they would be kicked out.

Zhang Liu came out once more on his flying sword. The sect could remotely tell who had passed and who had failed. The last thing that these youths had to do was just walk through another gate.

“Congratulations brothers and sisters, you have shown us the determination and worth of a United Element sect member! Now, anyone with at least a 100 merit points is allowed to walk through this door.”

Zhang Liu pointed to another gate, it was similar to the first jade one but looked slightly bigger.

“The sect emblems that you have been given will allow you to access some parts of the sect. If you have enough then follow me inside, if you don’t then please leave the sect premises.”

Zhang Liu performed another short speech before moving before the last gate and demonstrating how everything worked. He just stood in front of the gate and a similar scanner like ray hit the emblem on his shoulder. The gate then slid open, it was apparently a giant jade sliding door and would open each time someone from the sect stepped forward.

After Zhang Liu vanished inside the tired people started walking up slowly. The first person that stepped forward was a handsome young man. His robe looked tidy and neat if you compared it to the ones the two youths were wearing from the Tatar tribe. The moment he arrived the gate slid open and he just walked in without stopping.

This handsome young man was the person with the highest number of merit points from this batch. He was soon followed by a ravishing beauty, the woman caught every man’s eye as she also headed inside. She was second on the merit list and was followed by a large burly youth with a bare chest that finished at the third spot. The others just looked on flabbergasted by the looks of these people, everyone could tell that their cultivation was quite high for their age.

“Everyone please line up in an orderly fashion.”

A person from the sect finally walked up and started organizing everything. The youths had stopped before the last hurdle and not everyone was willing to step forward. Everything moved slowly and some of the trial takers weren’t allowed in as the door remained shut before them. They were excused to the side with a pat on the back, maybe they could try again in a couple of years if they weren’t too old.

Cheng Yun and Yang Rong were the only two people to successfully make it through the door from the Tatar tribe. To their dismay the other clan they were feuding with had three people make it over to the other side. The only good part about this was that it was forbidden for sect disciples to fight with each other outside the sect.

It took some time for everyone to get past that gate, the logistics of moving all of these people inside and outside the sect were tremendous. The way they performed the trials might have to be evaluated in the future as most of it was just people waiting in lines.

On the other side the new trial disciples were greeted with quite the sight. There were various massive buildings standing everywhere but the most eye-catching was the giant castle right in the middle and then a smaller one floating right above it, radiating power. Before anything could happen further Zhang Dong had to do his speech.

The youths that had gone through the week-long trials were all tired so he wanted to do this fast. He was looking at the statistics, close to fifty thousand people had made it through the trials. This might have sounded like a large number but there were over a million candidates at the start. Huge sects tended to have millions of members spread throughout the lands that they owned, so when they added fifty thousand they still were much smaller than the other superpowers.

Those fifty thousand were all now in the square while being surrounded by some official sect members. Before they could ask what was happening everyone felt a massive spike in spiritual energy in the area. The Qi in the air started vibrating as if something big was coming. Everyone here started getting goosebumps before they looked into the air and there they finally saw him.

Zhang Dong was floating in the air and looking down at them. He was wearing a long gold and violet ceremonial robe. His sleeves were long and they along with the bottom of his robe gently floated in the wind. Not everyone recognized this man as the sect leader but some noticed that he had a striking resemblance to the statue that was in the city.

“Greeting to my United Element’s Sect, you have managed to take your first step towards greatness. Keep this in mind though, this isn’t the end of your struggles, it’s just the beginning.”

The man smirked a bit after completing that sentence, the potential disciples flinched as they didn’t like the sound of that. Most of them barely scraped by to get those merit points and supposedly this wasn’t the end.

“For now rest, you did well.”

Something strange happened as the floating person reached out forward with his hand. The space around became distorted and he started shining. The whole square where the young cultivators were standing in became bathed in rays of golden light. They were surprised, what was this powerful master doing? Soon they realized as the fatigue and wounds that they had suffered during the trials faded away.

Somehow this elder used his power to heal so many of them at once. For a powerful nascent soul cultivator restoring Qi to lower Qi condensation cultivators wasn’t that difficult. Still, there were fifty thousand people here so he had to get the aid of the sect formations in the area to boost his power.

“You three did well !”

Zhang Dong waved his hand and three disciples that were the top of this class floated up. It was the handsome youths along with the icy beauty and the macho. The three that looked composed earlier were amazed by the display of power. They were all young masters from their own clans but they could do nothing about this powerful senior.

They found themselves up in the air about two hundred meters above everyone else. The white-haired man was directly in front of them. They all dropped their heads down as they bowed, directly looking into a powerful master’s eyes was considered rood.

“Raise your heads, you did well young ones.”

“Fang Shu, 546 merit points you did well.”

The handsome youth with long black hair moved his head up. He saw the white-haired master wave his hand around and some kind of necklace appeared around his neck. It was golden and had the characters for the sect’s name on it.

“Take this small gift, it will protect you from harm in the future.”

He noticed instantly that what he got was a mortal treasure of the highest quality. He dropped his head down and clasped his hands while thanking.

“Fang Shu thanks the honorable master for this gift.”

Zhang Dong just nodded and looked to the other two. The girl and muscular man had anticipation in their eyes after seeing what the person next to them got.

“Zhao Zhiruo 498 points…”

“Wen Xiufeng, 486 points…”

The two received silver pendants instead of a golden one that were of slightly lesser quality than what Fang Shu got. Matt at first wanted to make a bronze one but then decided to have two silver medals and a golden one instead. He gave the trio a little pep talk before sending them back to the ground. He started concluding everything, his speech was coming to an end.

“Follow the instructions of the elders, you will be guided to your new homes. Study hard young ones, show me that you are worthy of the resources the sect provides. If you are diligent our paths may intertwine again. For now, farewell my disciples. Live long, prosper, and may the Qi be with you.”

Zhang Dong finished up with his speech while the young disciples kept their eyes on him. Some were even unwilling to blink, this was the first time they laid their eyes on someone as mighty as this master. Everyone interpreted his words differently but a lot felt that the intertwining part meant that he might accept them as disciples if they proved themselves.

This gave everyone here another boost in confidence. They knew how ferocious this sect leader was, he even managed to go against five nascent soul cultivators at once and came out on top. The United Element sect members were sure to brag about their ‘Lightning Emperor’ whenever they had the chance.

Zhang Dong vanished from the spot he was standing and his aura that was giving everyone here goosebumps was also gone. The Qi condensation cultivators weren’t able to follow his movements at all as he just sped away back to his home. His pregnant wife was waiting for him and he left the busywork to his sect members. In times like these, they were the ones to shine.

He picked up the pace and even a sonic boom was heard in the distance as he left a couple of after images. His part in all of this had ended for the moment. He was still listed as the new school's special teacher. If the students gathered enough points they could even receive some pointers from him. The number required was quite staggering though. The leftover youths were left waiting but soon their new life as trial disciples was going to start, a bright future ahead of them.

Chapter 217

The people left in the square started looking at each other while murmuring. Most of them were still stunned after getting healed by the nascent soul cultivator who was the sect leader. Their chatting got interrupted by a loud voice and the appearance of more people. These people were all wearing gray robes and were wearing emblems fit for the elder generation.

“Quiet down! You are all trial disciples now, you are not yet fit to be considered true disciples of the sect! You will now follow us to the dorms, this is where you will spend the next four years of your life.”

The man was an old-looking cultivator with an eyepatch that wasn’t able to cover the giant scar on his face. There were other members from the seniors with him and they were mostly composed of the three clan’s side family members. Those occupied the spots of the outer sect members while the main family branch was all composed of the inner sect members.
Of course, everyone from them could be promoted to an inner sect elder if they worked hard. The reverse would also be possible and everyone could be demoted.

“Listen up, we don’t have the whole day. Your emblems are the most important item you could have in this sect. It stores all the information about you, your merit points, and also allows you to freely move through select parts of the sect…”

The man explained how the emblem they were carrying work as a sort of key. It stored their data that was then saved in the sects database. The trial disciples had free access to some training facilities as well as the new dorms where they lived.

“Remember the 100 merit points you needed to pass the trials? Those points can be spent on cultivation resources.”

He gave them an explanation about the merit point system. The points weren’t just for show, everyone was going to keep those 100 merit points. They would be able to spend them on various things as it was considered money around the sect. They would be provided basic living and food but if they wanted more they would need to use them.

There were various ways of earning merit points. The easiest one was attending classes and passing the tasks that were given by the teachers. Rising your cultivation level gave you points, getting through challenges or performing tasks for the current sect members was another one.

The biggest reason for gathering more points was pointed out here. If your points dropped to 0 you would be thrown out of the sect. If they ever fell so low you had a month's time to gather more in any way possible. You could even battle other disciples and get their merit points. This was the easiest way of getting them and the sect allowed friendly competition. This was also the best way to take care of the disputes between disciples.

The explanation was cut short as the elders needed to segregate the people into five schools. Each camp would start out with trial disciples of similar strengths all calculated through the scanners and the tests the participants went through. All of the academies would be mixed as their Patriarch didn’t feel like splitting the male and female population of the sect would be a good idea. This was in opposition to the Feng side of the sect that liked keeping their Matriarchal ways.

“Listen well, the emblem you have received has a number on it.”

The elder said while people looked to the emblems that they were previously assigned. He also explained that they were required to never lose them. They all already knew that this little treasure would allow them to walk around the sect.

“You will be assigned to an academy by your number, look here.”

The man said while pointing to the side. The moment he did a large flat contraption started rising out from the ground. The youths had never seen anything like this before so they were quite curious.

It was about twenty meters wide and fifteen meters high and attached to some thick columns. Soon they figured out what this was for as the treasure flickered on with light and showed many numbers.

This was a giant screen that Zhang Dong had based on his old world's flat-screen TVs. It had brackets that split into five academies, each one had a name.

“Find your number on the list and then follow the path to your academy, the seniors there will guide you to the dorms. You will be spending at least four years there. You have two days to look through the academy before the lessons start.”

The introduction soon ended and the new disciples moved forward, curious what this ‘academy’ that they would be living was. The two youths from the Tatar tribe pushed forward to look as well, luck was on their side as they ended up in the same academy.

“The Primal Dragon academy? What a ferocious name, it must be the very best one!”

Yang Rong proclaimed while Cheng Yun nodded, the two youths were very excited. They were just itching to get their hands on the sects cultivation techniques. Their moment of happiness was interrupted by the three tribe members from the enemy village.

“Heh, Primal Dragon academy? My Regal Phoenix academy will crush your smelly Dragon academy!”

Enemies were already forming as these five people glared at each other. Fighting was forbidden for now though so they would have to wait. Slowly people started clearing the square and moving towards the academy grounds. These ‘academies’ were more akin to small cities as each one of them had to contain at least ten thousand disciples along with the teachers and other staff.

The two youths were guided into the dorm district of the academy. These buildings were quite plain to look at and were just built with simplicity in mind. They were rectangular in shape and were many stories high. Each floor could fit hundreds of disciples in small rooms meant for two people.

At the reception area, the new trial disciples had the choice of finding their own roommate or having the sect choose a random one for them. The sect leader was all for mixing people up but even he knew that it was better to keep the girl's dorms and boy dorm rooms separate. He knew how the youths were and it would probably cause less of a headache if they didn’t live so close to each other.

The two Tatar tribe members decided to live together. The new room they received was quite small. There were two beds on each side with two dressers and two desks by a window through which they could see outside.

They were used to straw and wooden huts, so this building that was made from stone and bricks was already an upgrade. The beds that they received were also a lot softer. Both of them felt tired after all of those trials. The moment they sat down on their new beds to test them out, they both fell asleep instantly.

The announcement that the new sect’s recruitment drive had ended reached outside. From the million or so people only about fifty thousand remained. This wasn’t actually such a lower number as some other sects accepted far fewer disciples. This was due to them already having millions of disciples and thousands of elders in their camp.

Some of the people thought that the new powerhouse would accept more people under their umbrella. They clearly needed more people below the nascent soul level. Apparently, this sect was going for both quantity and quality.

While the youths were resting the sect leader was back at his home. His beautiful wife and his child were both fast asleep so he had time to ponder the next big event. This was him leaving the sect to attend some kind of gathering of the more powerful sects.

He already knew the structure of this empire by this point. Even though sects like the Dragon Gate Sect seemed like real powerhouses, they weren’t. They were only considered middle-sized sects when pitted against the real titans.

There weren’t really that many that were considered ‘large’ though. You could divide them into three camps. The first one was the Long Clan with the Azure Emperor at the helm of it. It might have been a clan and not a sect but they were gigantic with many branching side families. They were considered the strongest power in this empire.

Next were the two giant sects that kept them in line, the first one was called the Soaring Dragon Sect and the other the Blood Sabre sect. These factions were similar in power to each other and slightly lagging behind the Long Clan.

This trinity of giants were keeping each other in check. None of them could act against the other in fear of getting wiped out. If one of them was seen to be weak the other two factions would swiftly finish them off.

The trust between the three was paper-thin. Neither of the three powers was willing to risk making a deal with the others. They knew that they could get backstabbed in the middle of the fight. They were all greedy and wanted to be the sole ruler of the whole empire but had to divide it between each other. The Azure Emperor was deemed the strongest cultivator but even he didn’t have control over the whole empire.

There was also another reason why these three weren’t willing to fight. This wasn’t the only country on this giant planet. There were other kingdoms and similar empires bordering with them. If one of the giants was slain and their cultivators vanished then the other superpowers could try their luck and invade.

So a shaky period of peace was now in place. Everyone could be attacked at any moment and no one knew when war would break out. The battles mostly happened at the core formation level with the nascent soul powerhouses rarely making an appearance. At least not the ones that were part of the big three.

Battles between the middle-sized sects were still ongoing but unless you were someone at the very top of the nascent soul, you weren’t a problem in those giants' eyes. Matt didn’t know if there existed anyone at the immortal realm of power.

His own cultivation method would bring him to the very top, but there were no upgrades before he reached the great circle. He felt like it was a bit odd that no one had gotten to this level yet. If he managed to do it, then he would probably be considered this king of this giant planet but that was something quite distant.

He had also studied some of the texts that Feng Liena gave him. The ancestor that lived in that clan had long left this place and there were some records. He believed that they had ascended to that fabled immortal realm. The problem was that there wasn’t any information about that, it was as if they just vanished.

This made him think about them moving on to another realm like in some of the works of fiction that he read. If he reached the immortal realm, would he also get ejected from this world and forced to live in another one?

This was something he feared, he didn’t really want to leave his place. He had his sect here as well as his wife and kids. He wasn’t a person born here and he didn’t really care about being the strongest person in the world. He also didn’t mind staying here while not reaching the pinnacle of cultivation like most of the other cultivators that lived here. He already had a hard time believing the fact that he would live for a thousand years with his current cultivation level.

‘I should stop worrying about those things. I need to look at the current problem first. Who should I bring together with me...’

Zhang Dong thought about the gathering that he would be supposed to attend to. He needed to take some people with him as he couldn’t just show up alone. This was an event where sects were supposed to show off their power. Normally he would go there with his most powerful members and disciples. This was something he was afraid of.

‘I’ll need to change the scenario a bit here…’

He smiled a bit as he was going to try not to stand out, he knew how gatherings like those always ended. Someone always got offended and fights broke out, he just needed to take the right people with him so that they didn’t stand out too much...

Chapter 218

Zhang Kuo looked into the communication jade. The sect leader had sent him an order to gather up people for the next event. They were to go to the sect gathering with the largest battleship that they had. This was the normal part, the odd one was the characteristics of the members that he should gather for it.

There was a list of the attributes that these people from the sect should have. One was that they were supposed to be old, the Patriarch even added that if they were ugly it would be a big boon. None of his disciples were to come with him or from the junior generation. They were all supposed to be composed of the senior generation elders. Even the people doing chores were supposed to all be old and not good on the eye.

Zhang Jin was banned from going and Feng Liena’s grandmother would be coming with him instead. There were actually a lot of elders from the Feng Clan, Zhang Dong even mentioned that it would be best if they had a lot of makeup on and really dark skin. He even added that the people coming should be good at etiquette and not standing out.

Zhang Kuo scratched his head and just shrugged. He was already used to his sect leader’s quirky ways so he wouldn’t even ask about an explanation. He was already a core formation senior as well so he knew that if he continued working hard that maybe he would make it into the next realm. There were already other people that did it before him, so this wasn’t just a pipe dream.

While Kuo was working hard on his future, Zhang Dong was sitting in his own room and cultivating. He was thinking about the sect get together and how he could evade it going wrong. He already knew that things tended to go astray where they could.

‘Okay, what else… I eliminated all the good looking people from the equation so I shouldn’t run into any horny young masters…’

The first thing he did was forbid people like Zhang Xue to even set foot in the flying ship. He knew that her beauty would get the young lords all riled up. They would probably start fighting over her hand in marriage almost instantly.

He also couldn’t bring her brother along, that fool had a knack for getting in trouble as well. He would jump to defend anyone he could, if he saw someone in distress he would try to protect them. Fights were sure to break out with other disciples due to this. He would also be the first one to defend his master, Matt feared that if his name was tarnished there Liu would want to face the opposition with a sword in hand.

His plan of action was to bring only old farts that were nice and docile. They would be the types that would drop their head and apologize if there was a chance of avoiding a fight. They would be far too old and crafty to engage in combat with another sect. He needed people experienced in diplomacy instead of warriors even though this would make his sect seem weaker.

‘Well, they are only there to accompany me, the whole thing should only take a couple of days anyway.’

He certainly couldn’t take his wife or daughter with him. Feng Liena was the biggest problem, when she would be giving birth was a big unknown. Pregnancies at the nascent soul level mostly took longer than regular births. His daughter only came out after a full year and he had to support both of them with his golden healing aura during the whole process.

If he didn’t have to go he would stay but he was afraid to send Huo Qiang or any of the other masters instead. He could tell that they were all itching for a fight after achieving a breakthrough. This was something he needed to do on his own as he at least wanted to keep this fake peace until his son was born.

The city was well protected and with the spirit vein as a power source, it would last for quite some time against a middle sized sect. The number of defensive cannons was also increased as well as a whole legion of beasts and beast tamers to aid. He didn’t need to fear about his city falling unless the sects made another pact and attacked altogether.

‘Maybe I can strike a deal with that Dragon Gate sect master, he seemed a bit more sensible than the other two.’

He paced through his room, he had gotten a bit older and was even past his mid-thirties. The first few years were the most hectic but after establishing the sect everything had somehow settled down.

Thanks to his system he was able to identify any spies that tried sneaking in here, even through these five years the sects had never really given up. There were even several people from their camp during the trials. They were promptly apprehended and sent down to the mines along with the others. He would not refuse free labor if it was offered, maybe in the future, they could be set free.

The time of the departure was in a couple of days and his people were already packing up. He was a guest at that banquet but he was still required to bring a gift or two. He didn’t want to reach far into his pockets but he still needed to bring something with him. This something would mostly be pills that aided cultivation. He also had some other goodies packed if he felt that it was worthwhile to share them.

He gave out a sigh after finishing up with all the plans. He was worried, this life as a leader and a family man wasn’t the easiest. Still, he couldn’t grab his wife and kids and fly away or give the sect over to another person. This whole enterprise was his creation, without the system backing it up it might crumble into dust within a couple of years.

He soon went to bed while worrying. Time flew by fast as the sect members got the large flying ship ready. This was something that took over a year to build and was the sect's crown achievement.

It wasn’t made from wood as all the other ships, no it was entirely made of spirit metals. It also didn’t have the usual galleon design as the old Zhang Clan ships that Zhang Dong had used before. This one looked more like a modern capital ship, an aircraft carrier in particular.

Zhang dong had designed it while having a certain mobile command center in mind. It didn’t have any sails to pick up wind but it had two giant engines on each side, enclosed in more metal. It looked like a giant flying drone with many cannons plastered on top of its flight deck.

There were even some flying artifacts that could be operated by the crew inside that had the power of core formation masters. The whole giant mobile fortress was a heaven graded treasure and could even go against multiple nascent soul cultivators at once. It even possessed a hidden giant cannon that, if charged, could even harm a cultivator at the great circle level.

Matt decided on bringing this oversized flying fortress with him into enemy territory. He mostly did it as a backup plan if something went wrong. When he was in the captain's chair he could infuse his own spiritual energy into it and improve on its power. He could even dump his system points into it to repair some of the parts like the engines as they were made in his crafting abode and worked on the system’s rules.

The only downside of bringing it with him was that the other sects would see some of his true strength. That could also be a good opportunity to show of though, he didn’t want to start any conflicts but he wasn’t afraid. If they came asking for trouble he would be sure to act accordingly. He hoped that masking the ship as a low heaven grade treasure would be enough for the other sects to only see it as a large toy instead of a risk.

The day of departure finally arrived and Zhang Dong had to kiss his daughter and wife goodbye. Just as he had planned beside the trained ship crewmembers the rest of the delegation was composed of grandpas and grandmas that weren’t very pleasing to the eye.

Zhang Dong nodded at Zhang Kuo who did a great job in picking these ugly cultivators, some of them were even overweight. There was also another reason he wanted them to be old. He wouldn’t feel as bad if one of them offended a powerful sect member and got smacked. If it was one of his disciples he would need to defend them but if it was some random old guy that he didn’t know, he could just let him bow a couple of times instead. The loss to face if he didn’t intervene would be much lower then.

‘Didn’t think I’d be thinking about ‘face’ this much…’

His point of view had slightly shifted to fit the people in this world. Still, he mostly felt like his core values were there. He wouldn’t actually let any of these old fogies get hurt too much and he believed that they were all smart enough to not get into trouble. He sure hoped that a weirdo like that guy from the Dark Palm sect wouldn’t appear this time around. He really didn’t want to defend Feng Maling from soul hungry demonic cultivators again.

“Greetings Patriarch, it’s an honor to make this journey with you.”

“Granny Ling, you can just call me by my name.”

Zhang Dong waved his hand as the old woman was still very formal around him. He had married her granddaughter and now treated her as his own grandmother. She on the other hand didn’t want to drop the act only doing it when his wife or his daughter was close.
“I mustn't sect leader, what will the other sect members think!”

She looked at the other old men and women that were coming along. They were mostly here for their linguistic skills as all were crafty with politics. Their job was to try to weasel in some connections, maybe get a good deal on some crafting resources. The sect was in a spot with a lot of spiritual energy but they didn’t really have many resources. They had to mostly plant their own spirit herbs which took time and space. Opening trade routes with the middle-sized sects would be profitable for all people involved.

“Well, the trip shouldn’t take that long but we will have to go slower once we are in their territory to keep up appearance.”

Feng Maling nodded as she knew what Zhang Dong meant. This ship was massive but it was also very fast, a lot faster than what a low grade heavenly artifact should be. To keep appearances they needed to slow down while in enemy territory.

“Okay everyone, get to your stations and move out!”

Zhang Dong gave the order for departure after everything was in place. The trip to the border wouldn’t take more than a day but after that, he wasn’t sure. They were supposed to meet someone there that would escort them to the meeting place. Even if they were ambushed with the firepower this ship had they should be able to make an escape. He could also summon his grand elders to aid him if the need arose.

While the sect leader was leaving for the banquet the new trial disciples were getting ready to take their first lessons. They had switched to gray robes and were now all in the same color scheme. Their life would consist of attending theoretical lessons as well as practical lessons. Depending on their skills they could sign up for more classes like alchemy or crafting. Everything was slowly moving forward as the sect continued to grow but would things remain peaceful now one knew.

Chapter 220

A gong resounded throughout the area signaling that it was 7 am. The sun was slowly rising and some spirit beasts howled out along with the loud gong sound. From two beds two people rose up to attention, they were two youths just in their underwear.

The two looked at each other with quivering eyes. They had been unable to sleep during the night as it was finally happening. The time to begin their new life as United Element Sect’s trial disciples.

The loud sound that sounded like a huge gong was there to help the youths wake up in the morning. They still had an hour to get ready so there was supposedly enough time. The two rolled out of their beds and landed on the floor and shook themselves awake.

“Brother Rong… it’s finally time!”

“Yes brother Yun, we will finally become elite cultivators!”

The two had sparkles in their eyes. They were already seeing themselves flying on large swords just like the one their senior brother Zhang Liu had. They quickly put on their gray robes and made sure that their emblems were in place. The robes had the name of the sect written down in a larger circle on their backs.

To the side of it, there was a smaller circle with a drawing of a dragon which indicated the academy they were from. There were five of them and these two belonged to the Primal Dragon academy. Each one had about ten thousand disciples in it, which made things a bit hectic.

After inspecting their clothes they charged out of their dorm room to go outside. They weren’t the only people going out as the moment they left their room they could see many people in the halls. Due to the sheer number of them, they even had to wait before they could squeeze out through one of the exit doors.

“Next time we should go out of the window…”

Cheng Yun commented after he saw some other disciples using that method instead. Everyone was rushing to the first assembly. This would be their first lesson as new disciples and no one wanted to be late. Even though it was only a couple minutes after 7 am the young people swarmed the meeting place.

There were far too many people to teach in small classrooms here. Zhang Dong decided to go with the open-air option and place a large stage in one area of the academy ground. The teacher would do his lectures there with the aid of some large screens and a sound system. The disciples would have to either stand or sit while listening.

This was a free lecture, everyone was able to participate here at no cost. If the youths wanted more help from a senior member they would have to use their merit points. This wasn’t limited to the teachers, even disciples could teach other disciples while trading merit points. There were just some basic lessons that everyone had to get through.

The two youths from the Tatar tribe arrived with everyone else and they were somewhere in the middle of the crowd. There was enough space for everyone to stand and not have to be shoulder to shoulder. The two looked around and Yang Rong gave Cheng Yun a nudge with his elbow to get his attention.

“What is it, brother?”

“There look, isn’t that the senior sister that was second?”

Cheng Yun narrowed his eyes and looked in the direction that Yang Rong was pointing at. There she was, an icy beauty with jade-like skin and long black hair. The two didn’t see her that well as everyone was bowing as the sect leader was doing his speech.

“Such beauty... “

The two just continued to stare. The girls in their village weren’t ugly or anything but compared to this young woman they were like frogs. They were smitten by Zhang Xue’s hologram already but after seeing a real jade beauty from close up they were even more excited.

“She has to be my Daoist partner, I have decided!”

Yang Rong drooled slightly before mustering up some courage to walk forward. Cheng Yun was flabbergasted by his brother's attitude. How could he just approach such a beauty, did this man know no fear?

He saw him in a new light and just watched as he strutted over with big strides. There was a small problem though, before he could approach her someone moved to block his path. Cheng Yun noticed something, the beauty seemed to be standing alone but that wasn’t really the case. She was surrounded by many other people that were forming a shield and keeping everyone away.

Cheng Yun continued watching and just saw his brother shouting at one of the youths that blocked his way. In no time two more appeared to block his approach, Yang Rong seemed resolute as he tried forcing his way through. To his surprise, the group of people were all above his realm and easily pushed him back.

Fighting was forbidden by the sect and this was probably the only reason why the group of bodyguards didn’t give Yang Rong a good thrashing. After a few well-chosen words he returned to where Cheng Yun was standing. The youth just chuckled while Yang Rong’s whole face scrunched up.

“Did you make her your Daoist partner, brother Rong?”

Cheng Yun sniggered while some other people did the same. The young woman was an eye-pleaser so quite a bit of the other disciples saw the whole exchange.

“What do you mean! This is just a small setback, this Yang Rong will never give up!”

The young man smacked his chest with a lot of force before announcing his convictions. The other people who heard this didn’t know if they should cheer or laugh. The woman he was after looked like a lot of trouble. She was clearly some young missy from a stronger clan, the youth that was from a low tribe had no chance with someone like that.

At least that was what the smirking onlookers were thinking, the young tribe member was pumped up. Love was never easy, he just needed to impress the lady enough to catch her attention and then her adoration!

While the people were looking at the silly encounter another loud gong echoed through the whole area. Everyone looked to the stage and they soon saw a person walking out. The man was wearing a blue robe which indicated that he was an inner sect elder.

The person was really big, at least two meters tall with arms thick as tree trunks. He was even wider than the youth that was third place and could give the Huo Patriarch a run for biggest macho. The trial disciples stopped chatting and looked with wide-open eyes as they waited for the first lesson to start.

The large man moved to the front but he didn’t speak. Soon another person walked forward, it was a woman. In comparison to the large strong-looking man, this woman was quite curvaceous and alluring. Yang Rong was even reevaluating if he should go for this older sister instead of the other one he just swore his love towards.

“My name is Zhang Peng and this is Sister Ai, you will refer to us as Elder Peng and Elder Ai from now on.”

After the two took the center stage they started talking. They welcomed the disciples and gave a little talk about how much of an honor it is to be in this sect. They didn’t take long to finally get to the point, which was body refinement.

“I see that your bodies are unrefined and weak, we will be focusing on that for the first few months. All of you will be picking one of the basic body refining techniques from the library and practicing it. Only with a strong body, you may start cultivating Qi once more!”

The man continued to talk while walking around the stage. Finally, the lovely lady had time to chime in. She walked forward causing the younger men in the area to gulp hard.

“This is one of the rules of this sect, we are all practicing dual cultivation. Only people that can both cultivate their body and spirit will be allowed in as a true disciple.”

The youths gasped and started murmuring amongst each other. This was something unprecedented, most sects didn’t operate like this. You’d find them focusing on one or the other. Only elite individuals could hope to advance in both Qi cultivation and body refining. They were now worried that they wouldn’t make it as training in both was considered spreading yourself too thin. Their worries would be soon dispelled by this female teacher.

“Are you doubting yourself or are you doubting the sect?”

She asked while smirking.

“Dual cultivation in normal circumstances is very difficult but only when the techniques you are practicing are of low quality. Don’t worry my juniors, the sect will provide the right resources for you, I assure you that if you practice diligently you will achieve progress!”

The woman smiled while the trial disciples eyes shone. They didn’t think that these people were lying to them. They knew that if they got a really good technique and maybe some resources that anything was possible. They had all made it through the rigorous trials so they were in good spirits. This library that the seniors mentioned also piqued their interest.

“You will be given your first body refining manual and Qi refining manual free of charge. You will need to spend merit points for improved tomes and new techniques ....”

The large man and woman continued to talk. They gave the kids some advice on spending their merit points and which manuals were the best ones for newbies like them. They also explained that the school year was divided into two semesters and there would be a test each semester.

There would be mandatory lessons and some basic techniques that everyone would need to learn. They would be then tested by teachers and they would be graded on their mastery and progress in the future.

For now, they needed to go to the library to pick their body refining technique. There were some people that already had somebody refining techniques of their own. They were assured by the teachers that the sects manuals were superior to their own techniques.

The lecture took some time and more teachers came over to introduce themselves. Most of them were wearing gray robes and not the blue ones that the first two had. The blue-robed elders were the heads of their own departments while the gray robes were the assistants. They also would give pointers if you spent merit points on the lessons. The gray-robed teachers were cheaper and some even gave lessons for free.

The assembly ended and everyone was allowed to go to the library. The youths had already visited most of the places they were allowed in during the first few days. There were a couple like the large cafeteria that served them basic spirit rice for free. If they wanted something more nutritious they needed to use up merit points.

There was a gym where the disciples could lift weights and train their muscles. It had other facilities that you also could spend merit points on. One of those was the gravity room, that increased the gravity and was good for full-body exercises. There were various other specialized chambers that aided in growth as well.

The most popular one was the library though. It was closed before this announcement but now the trial disciples would be allowed to visit the first floor. In it, they would be able to pick out their first technique which would be used to refine their body. This along with a basic Qi refining manual would form the basis of their cultivation for the coming months and maybe even years.

Thanks to the in-depth tests that every one of the disciples went through. The sect knew which techniques would fit each individual and would limit the choices accordingly. This would lower the chances of the youths picking an unfitting manual and in term ruin their future prospects. The time of learning had finally arrived and everyone was eager to start.

Chapter 221

Zhang Dong’s travels continued. They went through the old Dark Palm Sect area that was now occupied by the other middle sized sects. The further they traveled the thicker the residual Qi in the air became. It was no wonder why people fought over these lands. As they wanted to move towards the giant spirit vein that was in the middle of the Empire.

The two largest sects along with the Long clan were surrounding that spot from all sides. It was rumored that the three powers built giant walls that reached up into the heavens. These walls were reinforced with some special materials and couldn’t be damaged by anyone. Not even the top experts. The sects split the most sought after resource between themselves and the walls were there so that fights wouldn’t break out between the factions.

The spiritual energy that was rising did a lot for plant life. The trees were thicker and larger. Even the regular herbs had more Qi in them than the high quality ones in the lower regions. The whole ecosystem looked more lively and lush, Matt could only imagine how the scenery would look like in the middle of the empire.

Zhang Dong wasn’t flying next to his ship anymore, he had moved down to his private cabin and was now looking at a large screen. The screen split into many smaller ones and he could see the scenery around the ship from its many cameras. He had successfully brought this technology to this world. He hoped that some talented people would soon pick up on it and make some interesting movies or TV shows that he could enjoy later in his free time.

He tried introducing another marvel of technology which was the internet not too long ago. This didn’t go through that well as the cultivators didn’t see a purpose for something like that. They already had communication jades to send information, why would they need an archaic system like the internet for a similar task.

They also didn’t really understand the whole graphical aspect of the whole thing. Maybe if the new TV system went through well, they would open up to the other one. At least that was what Matt was hoping for but he didn’t think he could get a carbon copy of the internet he had back on his homeworld.

There were no computer games for one and he didn’t think that the cultivator nuts here would spend their precious time playing Tetris. This was unless there was some cultivation aspect that the games could provide. He didn’t know how to do such a thing, it would be nice if he could design a machine that increases your strength while playing games. Doing it might not be impossible but the cost would probably outweigh the gain.

While looking through the live feeds on his screen he could see the other sect watching them. They had many soldiers looking at their ship constantly, he could even zoom in and see the greed in their eyes. He clearly knew that if they weren’t afraid they would try ransacking his flying fortress.

‘Damn greedy bastards, will they never understand that strength and power isn’t all that is to this vast world?’

Matt lamented in his thoughts. He wanted to change the mindset of these people but he really didn’t see how. The only way he could think of is world domination and having the biggest fist around. But if he forced everyone to see it his way, would he be any better than the rest? An empire like that would probably crumble the moment he died or someone stronger than him appeared.

The only other possible way was slowly changing the thought process of the people living here. Generation by generation, maybe he could soften their views and get them to see the bigger picture. Even that approach required a massive amount of prestige and strength. This was something he was still somewhat lacking.

He felt that it wasn’t out of the realm of possibilities though, with his immortal grade techniques he was convinced that he could take on the world. That is if the other sects weren’t hiding similar assets. He wasn’t foolish enough to believe that strong cultivation would always come out on the top. He almost was done in by a well placed trap formation even though he was strong.

This was also why his sect was important, he needed help from others. Luckily he wasn’t alone, he already had some good friends and a loving family. This also gave him the motivation to move forward.

He smiled a bit after thinking back to his little cinnamon roll of a daughter. While deeply in thoughts he got interrupted by a little red blinking light. This was an indicator that showed that the ship’s captain wanted to talk to him. He received the call while lazily sitting down on his overly soft couch.

“Glory to the Patriarch!”

Was the first thing that he heard, he rolled his eyes instantly. He knew that he would never get used to this, something deep inside his very soul was not allowing him to feel superior to others. He was just a random guy that was wished away here and got an overpowered body and a system. He felt closer to common people than young or old masters and this would probably stay with him till he died.

“You may speak.”

He had to prompt the captain to have him speak as the last time he didn’t reply the man kept quiet for over a minute.

“We will be arriving at our destination soon. The ship will dock outside of the city as the other sects have instructed and we will be waiting for your return. The banquet is scheduled to start after two days of our arrival.”

Matt sighed out, he needed to wait for even more before the whole thing started. This get together would last for more than one day and he would need to attend it all. His introverted personality had never gone away and he hated forced parties like this. Back in his own sect, he could leave at any time without explaining himself. Here on the other hand he needed to keep up appearances. He couldn’t just leave during a boring conversation, he needed to remain and keep nodding his head.

“Inform the other elders, we will be leaving as soon as we arrive.”

He heard a clicking sound as the captain disconnected. Matt rose from his seat while looking at the monitors. The scenery was flying by fast and he couldn’t see the city they would be arriving just yet.

He decided to move outside. The deck was under a protective formation so even if a regular person was standing on it they wouldn’t feel a breeze. He hovered upwards leaving this protective barrier while putting up his own that made him glow in a golden hue.

He inserted some of his Qi into his own eyes. They flickered with golden electricity before he saw the effect. His vision was enhanced and he could see a massive city in the distance. Even from here, he could tell that it was highly populated.

This city’s size was vastly larger than any other one that he had been in. Even his New Spirit Spring City wasn’t this big. There were probably tens or even hundreds of millions of people living in it. There were multiple checkpoints along the way that surrounded the land by massive walls.

He could even see some flying ships floating in the air with the Yinglong company’s rain dragon flag. They were expected to arrive so they were let through without a problem. Though he noticed that people were quite interested in his large ship that was dwarfing everything that they had seen.

The closer they got the more of the large city he could see. The architecture was similar to every other metropolitan he had seen before. Large pagodas and buildings with traditional slanted roofs were everywhere.

The structures at the front were smaller but everything rose up the further you looked. Right in the middle was a giant pagoda tower which was probably the main palace. It reached up into the sky and you could see some magical beasts flying around it along with some sword cultivators.

‘That banquet is going to take place there. I’m supposed to meet Xu Qing the Dragon Gate’s Patriarch tomorrow.’

Xu Qing was the name of the man that brought him over here. Most people would see this as an honor or a privilege. He on the other hand felt like it was a hassle. Still, what needed to be done had to be done. He floated back into the warmer climate of his ship and went back inside after checking out the surroundings.

He met up with Feng Maling with the rest of the old man group. When he entered the large meeting room everyone gave him the usual bow.

He didn’t really know most of these people Zhang Kuo had gathered. Some of them were even his relatives from his side family. There was a small group of old women that looked like baked potatoes similar to Feng Mailing. He didn’t think that any of the old masters or the younger ones would be interested in starting a feud over them.

The old men weren’t lookers either and he could already tell from the way they were repeatedly bowing that they knew how to kiss ass. He was glad that he picked an oldie squad like this, with them around they shouldn’t be offending other people.

They might lose some face due to only bringing over old men and women. With him around, he hoped that they wouldn’t try to start fights. There was a certain threshold that he wouldn’t cross until he would act. He hoped that this gathering of the middle-sized sects would go smoothly.

There were even sects that were in a weaker position than he was. He at least was considered to be equal or stronger to some of the sect leaders due to his fight against Yang Guanyu all those years ago. Zhang Dong was considered to be one of the rising stars in the senior generation and some eyes were on him. This was at least what this spy network had dug up. Still, his power was unproven in the eyes of most of these masters.

“We will proceed as discussed, you will conduct yourself accordingly and keep a low profile during this assignment.”

Zhang Dong gave his group of elders the last talk before they left outside. They were to mostly keep to themselves, not offend anyone and call him over if it got out of hand.

“That is all, they will probably assign us some kind of hotel or mansion to stay at, so you will probably spend some time there.”

Apparently moving in the city wasn’t such a good idea if you weren’t in good faith with the city lord. The man that owned this city was an old master that was in the great circle of the nascent soul. There were also various other monsters hiding in the background ready to pounce at anyone that didn’t follow their laws.

The seniors nodded, they were still surprised that their young leader chose them to tag along. This was quite an honor to be allowed to witness this mythical city. This was something that they didn’t think they would be able to accomplish in their lifetime.

The Yinglong Pavilion company was the most famous one in the whole empire. Being able to come to their main city was something to die for. They would be even allowed to look at the sights later on or go to the exclusive auction house. It was the biggest one in the whole country and even the Long Clan members went there to bid for treasures.

“United Element Sect, move out!”

Zhang Dong moved outside and the elders were right behind him. They were all core formation experts as being someone below that level would be too shameful for even them. Even though they were old with the help of the improved techniques, these old men and women would give a good fight to anyone in the same realm as they were. They would probably come out on top in most cases.

The time to mingle with the crowds had arrived and the welcoming party was already waiting for them.

Chapter 222

“The first guests are arriving!”

“Who is that, senior? They have a really big ship, are they from one of the top sects?”

“They are from the…United Element Sect?”

Two people were talking with each other. They were looking at seven approaching ships. They could see six regular-sized ones barely keeping up with a really large one made from metal. Even from here, everyone could tell that the large one was something special, it was a heaven grade treasure.

“Haven’t heard of them… the other ships bare the flags of the Limitless Sword Society and the Demon Subduing Sect…”

The junior asked while he kept looking, the senior member took out a scroll with the list of people that were invited. The sects that were coming today were supposed to be at the lower end of the strength spectrum. This meant that this United Element sect shouldn’t be anything special. For some reason, they were being escorted here by two other more powerful sects and their ship looked very powerful.

“Ah yes it's written here, United Element Sect, it's a newly established sect… the only note here is that their Patriarch could potentially be a threat...”

“Ah… I know, their Patriarch apparently took on the Dark Palm sect single-handedly and survived!”

The Junior member said with passion while the senior next to him gave out a sigh.

“You shouldn’t believe the rumors, that sect is new and they only survived thanks to Zhang Dong’s master.”

Most people didn’t want to believe that someone as young as Zhang Dong could go against the old monsters that easily. He apparently fought off five nascent soul cultivators at once, one of them was even a late stage cultivator. Their skepticism was confirmed as the United Element sect was still paying spirit stones to the other sects surrounding it. This implied that they felt inferior and didn’t want to cause trouble with them.

“Is that so?”

“Yes now straighten out, even though this sect isn’t anything special we must show our hospitality!”

They were still guests of the Yinglong Pavilion. Every sect here was considered to be medium sized and with nascent soul elders at the top. Each of them was a potential source of income for this guild of merchants. They were only profit-driven and didn’t care who was feuding with who, if they were able to spend high grade spirit stones they were good to start a business with.

“Yes senior!”

The two men went on their way to prepare the welcome. They needed to guide many of the cultivators to their temporary living quarters and explain the rules. This was neutral ground so fighting was forbidden. Not all of it as sects that had grievances could fight with each other in sanctioned matches. This was also a source of income in this city, betting on the fights between high level experts brought in quite the number of spirit stones.

Back on the Argonaut that was Zhang Dong’s ship, the sect members were gathering upon the main deck. There weren’t that many of them, only about twenty, most of the people on this ship were the crew members. They would be staying at high alert for the entirety of this trip.

They had orders to not allow anyone on board. Not even if they were powerful cultivators, they were to activate the defensive formations and even return fire. Of course, they would only retaliate if they were attacked and call him over to smooth things out. There was a teleportation gate inside the ship, so Zhang Dong could even teleport there to help them out.

He had certain special treasures that linked him up to the ship's teleportation gate. His system wasn’t something that was responsible for this feature. This was something that he managed to produce through the years of practicing his crafting profession. He was already a person that could craft heaven graded items with ease and the same was true for pills.

It wasn’t actually forbidden to take your weapons and spatial rings into the city premises. The Yinglong Pavilion people were confident in their grand formation that encompassed the entire city. It boosted their sides might and the other cultivators had no way of resisting if they got serious.

“Everyone gather up, we will be departing. Captain, I leave the Argonaut in your hands, if someone tries to cause trouble follow the agreed-upon procedures.”

Zhang Dong said while waving his hand around. A large golden veil surrounded everyone from the twenty man group. They started to gently float up and left the protective barrier of their large flying ship.

The people from the other two sects would be also waiting outside with them. They were ordered to remain here to watch and report back to their side. Their own sect leaders would be arriving later as they were from the more prominent sects.

The two nascent soul masters that were with them looked at the golden bubble that flickered with electrical energy. While looking at it they flinched out of fright. The lightning Qi surrounding that bubble was of the utmost purity, they didn’t know how this person could achieve such a mastery at such a young age. They made sure to report their findings and then retreated into their flying ships.

Zhang Dong and his group floated towards the main gate where some people were waiting for them. There was a familiar-looking nascent soul elder there, already waiting for him. He was wearing a top hat and a tuxedo quite different from what the other people wore.
“We meet again good fellow, let me be the first one to greet you here ol' chap.”

The man he was looking at was sticking out like a sore thumb again. He had a western looking tuxedo on just like the last time he met him. At first Matt thought that this might have been the whole vibe of this merchant organization. It would make more sense if they all were wearing western clothing but no. Only this man was doing it.

“Ah yes, greetings fellow Daoist, I’m Zhang Dong, I didn’t catch your name last time we met, it was a bit hectic back then…”

Zhang Dong had lowered his spiritual veil from his sect members and they all moved behind him. They were now looking at the entrance gate of his large city. Normally people from so far away in the lower areas of the empire would be opening their eyes wide with mouths agape. This group of oldies wasn’t doing such a thing though. Their own city walls were at least of equal quality to these.

“My humble name is Sebas Tian, you can just call me Brother Tian!”

The man chuckled while moving closer, instead of a bow he offered Zhang Dong a handshake. This took him slightly back but he returned the gesture while gripping the other man’s hand firmly. He was acting similar to an old English gentleman which was quite out of place.

This brought an idea to Matt. The man probably had similar roots to his lovely wife. She also had an ancestor that was probably from a different world. This man’s ancestor had to be of British descent. He might be able to get more information about those cubic treasures.

He was still in the dark about the strange site where he started his adventure in this world. The person that shortly spoke to him told him to get more of those cubes. He wasn’t able to find any other ones at all. Feng Lena's ancestor also came from another part of the empire or from a totally different country whatsoever.

He scanned his own land with his map and there were no other spots there. If he got this man to speak, maybe he could find one there? This was an unexpected encounter but maybe this trip here wouldn’t be a total waste.

“Brother Tian?”

Zhang Dong raised an eyebrow after the full name got revealed. This only confirmed that he must have some kind of transmigrator or reincarnator ancestor that came from either his own earth or a similar one.

“Brother Dong ol’ chap, you made a name for yourself since the last time I’ve seen you..”

“Ah, a couple of things happened and I got lucky.”

Zhang Dong replied while slightly smiling.

“Nonsense! There is no such thing as luck, only hard work, ol’ chap!”

The man got even closer as the two chatted. The elders behind Zhang Dong didn’t say anything and neither did the people that were standing behind Elder Tian. None of them had a say in this and they needed to remain in place and wait.

Their conversation continued for a couple of minutes before they finally decided to move into the city. The group of old cultivators that was behind Zhang Dong could finally move their old bones.

With the help of the top hat-wearing nascent soul master, they were able to enter without a problem. The man here wasn’t there for only Zhang Dong but he took some time out of his day to guide them into the city.

The two masters exchanged some pleasantries after which Sebas Tian had to return.

“Brother Dong, I will see you at the banquet I’m sure we can discuss the dao there ol chap”

“That we can brother Tian, you’ll have to tell me where you got that hat from....”

Matt was mostly interested in where this man had come from but he seemed like a nice guy. His alignment was also fine at lawful neutral.
After they split up a small group of servants came over. They were composed of good looking women and men only. This was probably a tactic to gain favor with the sects. They would keep them happy with small gifts and beauties.

Something like this would have probably worked on Zhang Jin like a charm. Zhang Dong on the other hand was the faithful type. He was even missing his little potato even more now.

The city was filled to the brim with people but the streets were empty. When he and his sect members were walking through the regular residents of the city had their heads down.

Everyone knew that many powerful people would be coming over. This also meant that offending one of them was a high possibility. Even with the city being protected by the Yinglong Pavilion they wouldn’t help anyone of low status. This was the same in any city in this world.
The group was guided to one of the larger hotels that went by the name of Azure Phoenix Hotel’. They weren’t the first group of cultivators to arrive though. Some other people were being guided by similar servants and already going inside.

Matt didn’t know just how many other sects were coming. There were far less middle sized sects with nascent soul masters throughout the land.

This also wasn’t the only hotel that the cultivators were guided to. Getting a worse place to stay at could also be a cause of fights breaking out. If one sect thought they should be the ones to stay at a more pricey hotel. It could be interpreted as a loss of face when they saw a similar sect as them getting preferential treatment.

He could already see two sects glaring at each other at the entrance to this hotel. They were composed of people of younger ages. The juniors were to the side glaring at each other and the two young masters were already picking fights with each other.

Matt was glad that he decided to bring the old fart group instead. Those just looked at the exchange with spite, those people were not conducting themselves with grace in their eyes.

Now a problem arose. The path towards his accommodations was right between the two sides. From the conversation, he was hearing these sects were rivals. Something about one of their senior members killing the other in some kind of competition or trial recently.

He had a decision to make, would he wait for them to stop fighting or would he just go through? Both decisions had their ups and downs, but the first one certainly would take more time as the shouting match was only getting louder and no one seemed to be interfering.

Chapter 223

“You snakes from the Silver Spear Sect can not be trusted!”

“Who are you calling a snake!? It's not our fault that one of your Golden Saber Sect members tried to backstab our senior brother from our Sect. It was karma!”

The two sides were continuing their quarrel. During an expedition to some kind of secret ground that allowed junior disciples to participate one of the parties suffered a setback. One of their young masters fought another youth of similar status. One of them lost, how it happened was still unclear. He had a certain treasure that marked his killer though so now the two sects were at each other throats.

One side said that he tried to steal the treasure from their junior master and he was just defending himself. These were the people of the Silver Spear sect. While the ones from the Golden Saber Sect claimed that he ambushed their young lord and took his life in an unfair way.

The truth was muddled at this point and it was impossible to figure out who was right and who was wrong. Even if evidence was presented each side could just refuse to believe it. Both sects were of similar strength and status so none of them wanted to back off.

They knew that fighting in this city was forbidden so they were only tossing insults at each other. Also, they weren’t quite ready to fight it out in the arena as their elders had forbidden such acts. They were holding the residence and workers hostage though as no one dared to step forward to stop the arguing cultivators. The laws of the powerful sects didn’t apply to them and they could be murdered in broad daylight. No one would care.

Zhang Dong and his people stopped because their leader did. The group of old men and women behind him wouldn’t act out without him saying anything. The people in front were from the junior generation and at quite the low level.

The United Element sect was probably one of the factions that brought the least number of cultivators. Others would even allow Qi condensation youths to tag along to show them off and maybe forge some relationships. The group in front of them was composed of such youths and the ones fighting were only in the core formation early stage.

From the conversation, you could deduct that these two were young elites. Their ages were probably close to what Zhang Dong was now. Having a core formation level at the age of thirty was nothing to scoff at in this world. Only people with genius-level talent were able to do this, the other way was having a lot of crafting resources.

Matt wondered why there weren’t any seniors with them to stop the fight. The group had probably arrived before his sect. They might have bumped into each other while wandering the city or going out of the hotel. The shouting match had been continuing for a few minutes now and nothing seemed to be being done about it.

The servants wouldn’t interfere and the people from the elder generation wouldn’t either unless a fight broke out. This put Matt in a little bind, he just wanted to wait a few minutes before they dispersed and not stand out. However, if he just stood there like a statue and did nothing other people would think his sect was afraid of these two parties.

He spread his spiritual sense through the area and felt other people watching. Two in particular were close to his level. They were also looking at him, he couldn’t just stand there. This made him look as if he was afraid of some junior cultivators.

At that moment an idea popped into his mind. He knew that if he just walked forward bad things could happen. But what if he could use that to his advantage? A quick plan formed in his mind that could go in two directions. Both of those weren’t anything bad for him so he stepped forward.

He put on a stone-faced expression and the elders behind him followed while keeping a distance. He walked slowly with his hands behind his back, it made him look relaxed and uncaring of his surroundings. He hoped the junior members from those sects would realize who he really was and react accordingly which would resolve everything with less hassle.

Yet reality was cruel and the bunch of kids reacted just like he expected they would. The moment they saw him walking forward between them they scoffed. Zhang Dong looked very young for his cultivation stage. Most people would at most put him as a core formation expert at the early stage.

With two such experts arguing with each other they thought that this new intruder wasn’t anything special. He was clearly ignoring them which inclined a lack of respect from Zhang Dong’s side. Tension was already high so without thinking about the consequences both parties started shouting out towards him.

“Who dares?”

“What is the meaning of this, state your name!”

The two core formation youths looked at Zhang Dong with anger. He looked like someone from their own generation so they weren’t afraid. The man didn’t react though as he just kept walking, it made it look like he was not taking these youths seriously at all. The problem was that he couldn’t really, he was a nascent soul master; it would be seen as dishonorable if he went against people from the junior generation. This matter had to be taken care of by someone from his lackeys, this would be his grandmother in law.

“Do you know who I am, I’m the son of the third grand elder from the Golden Saber Sect!”

“I’m the nephew of the fourth grand elder from the Silver Spear Sect, such insolence how dare you!”

The two continued to shout while Zhang Dong continued to walk forward and just as he was between the two parties a loud voice sounded from the back.

“How dare you two insignificant brats speak in such tone to the Patriarch!”

Granny Maling shouted out from the back while suppressing the two groups with her great circle of core formation aura. The youths that were below the core formation realm dropped like flies instantly while the two that were stronger backed away while grasping their chest.

“P-patriarch?”

They looked at the man that didn’t stop and continued to walk. He didn’t look much older than they were, he might have even been younger. How could someone like this be a patriarch of a sect. He did have a stronger member of the elder generation behind him, maybe he was just from some weak clan instead?

In their infinite wisdom, they shelved Zhang Dong into the young master category that was at most equal to them. He just was lucky enough to have a guardian that was strong. This meant that they could keep belittling him. If the elders from their side saw this, they would surely help them out.

“You dare attack the fourth son of the third grand elder from the Golden Saber Sect! You are courting death, wait till the elders hear of this.”

Matt almost tripped over his own feet after hearing that the haughty young master was only the fourth son. The other youth shouted out something similar as they were resolute in their belief that he wasn’t anyone important. The problem now was that he couldn’t stop, the members from a junior generation were disrespecting him. They were even doing it in public and already some other cultivators were looking at them.

He wanted to facepalm as the first option from his plan had gone astray. At least it was good that he didn’t take his disciples with him. If Zhang Liu was here, he would probably already be beating those two up or challenging them to a deathmatch.

He’d at least thought they would realize that he was someone more important than that. Even though his appearance was youthful, the items he was wearing weren’t anything someone of his age would have. He had various heaven grade treasures on himself, even his robe was a heavenly grade armor that could even transform. If these juniors weren’t brought up with their noses up in the clouds they would have probably realized that something was off about him.

It was too late for that and quite the scene was playing out. His trusted granny was looking really mad and pushed the two brats into the ground with the help of her aura. This caused more people to look and finally, people from their elder generation took notice.

Matt was trying to act like a proper senior by walking forward. His first plan went into the gutter as the people didn’t see him as a nascent soul elder. Soon people were wrestling with his grandmother with their auras and the two youths and the ones behind them were able to stand up.

“Elders, we didn’t do anything and they started bullying us!”

“Yes, that person just pushed his way through us and didn’t even apologize!”

The sides that were previously fighting with each other were now allies. There was a new enemy they could sink their teeth into and that was Zhang Dong. With the elders around the two were now reassured of their victory all of them were at least as strong as that overbearing granny.

The senior members from the other two sect were a bit more cautious though. They understood that the youths haven’t been through many hardships and their view on life was muddled. They wouldn’t just attack someone from an unknown faction. They knew that this was a gathering of all the large sects, they didn’t want to start a war with someone stronger than them.

Still, Zhang Dong was hiding his cultivation level and by the looks wasn’t anyone strong. The person with the highest cultivation here was Feng Maling. The group of oldies behind here wasn’t seen as a big threat either and their side had similar numbers of core formation experts.

“Fellow Daoists, why would you attack our juniors? From where do you fare? I would like to hear an explanation otherwise...”

“Otherwise?”

Matt had to end this farce, it had taken long enough and it was time for plan B to take effect. He wanted to be courteous and nice but this wasn’t possible anymore. He knew that there was a certain dynamic between people in this world. Someone with a higher cultivation didn’t need to answer the questions of someone beneath him. Even if they had backing, until that person showed up they didn’t need to show that much respect.

He was also a person of high prestige. Only other sect patriarchs that were at least at the late stage of nascent soul could speak to him leisurely. None of these people had that attribute. The moment the random elder from one of those sects asked the question Zhang Dong’s aura burst forward.

“Otherwise, what will you do?”

The area was filled with a domineering aura that suppressed everyone from the two sects that were previously fighting. They all were forced down to their knees and finally realized that the person in the white robe was a nascent soul master.

“Will you challenge me to a bout in the arena? Heard that’s how you are supposed to clear up your grievances in this city.”

The elders that asked the question were now sweating bullets. They wanted to run up to their junior members and slap their faces a hundred times. How did they offend a nascent soul monster on the first day of their arrival. Even if their Patriarch came over it would be hard for them to keep face now.

“S-show mercy honorable master, the juniors couldn’t see mount Tai, I’ll be sure to educate them in the future.”

The man talked quickly, other people were looking at them, some even laughing. They were from a prominent sect used to walking over people but now they were kneeling down before someone that looked like a young brat.

Matt on the other hand was waiting for someone else to finally react. He didn’t enjoy bullying these kids or these old farts but he had to seem like a domineering master. If that person didn’t arrive then he would probably end it on this note. This would make his plan B fail though.

“You better, otherwise there will be consequences.”

He said a threat before he tried to wrap it up. Luckily for him, one of the people that he hoped had enough and finally showed up.

“Halt, you dare disregard the Silver Spear Sect while I am here!”

‘Ah yes, just according to keikaku (plan)’

He could clearly see the name and cultivation rank of the person floating towards him.

Chang Yongzheng

|

Nascent Soul Late Stage

|

Affiliation: Silver Spear Sect - Sect Leader

Chapter 224

“What is happening? Who offended the Leader from the Silver Spear Sect, do they have a death wish?”

“Don’t they know that he is known to have quite the temper?”

“That young man is done for!”

“But isn’t that also a nascent soul master… but he looks so young!”

Random people started whispering while glancing at Zhang Dong who was standing in front of the hotel. A lot of the sects were gathering here now so this had turned into a big scene. Other sect masters and elders were arriving and recognized Chang Yongzheng who was floating above.

The big unknown was the person he was glaring at. The man was wearing a strange form-fitting robe and was really handsome. The ladies from the side were smitten by his good looks the moment they saw him. From the way he was presenting himself he looked to be someone important.

“Answer me, who are you to disregard my Silver Spear Sect and bully my sect disciples!”

Zhang Dong remained quiet while the people from the Silver Spear Sect started cheering. With their Patriarch here they had nothing to fear. They still didn’t dare to speak out though. The person there was still an unknown nascent soul cultivator. It would also be rude to speak while their Patriarch was talking.

Zhang Dong had his hands behind his back and eyed the nascent soul master with a side glance. He gave out a harrumph clearly indicating that he was dissatisfied with the man being there.

“I don’t care who you are or to what sect you belong to. I don’t need to explain myself to someone like you!”

The moment Zhang Dong replied the people in the peanut gallery showed shocked expressions. This was quite the jaw-dropper, they expected the young-looking cultivator to bow down and beg for forgiveness. He did the total opposite of it, he reacted in anger against someone that was in the late stage of a nascent soul.

Chang Yongzheng was flabbergasted. Rage flowed through him like lava and his face went red as he stared daggers at the young-looking cultivator. He, like the others, expected this man to bow his head and apologize. He would then leave the whole thing at that and both sides would go on their way. Now, on the other hand, he wasn’t able to do that anymore. This man was clearly disrespecting him, he couldn’t just take it lying down, no he wouldn’t!

“You dare! Do you have a death wish?“

The air around the two became cold and the tension could be cut with a sharp sword. Both the juniors from the Silver Spear Sect and Golden Saber Sect began to back away. No one expected the unfamiliar man to react in this way.

Zhang Dong’s aura pushed against Yongzheng’s and you could see Qi sparks flying around. Anyone below the nascent soul level that was in the close vicinity started getting weak in the knees. If a fight broke out now there would be a lot of collateral damage as even a simple punch from an expert of this level could flatten a large house.

The Patriarch from the Silver Spear Sect was shorter than Zhang Dong. He was an older looking man with a gray beard. He didn’t look like anything special but he was radiating power. He waved his hand and a beautifully crafted silvery spear appeared in his hand. The weapon radiated the might of a heavenly treasure and was pointed at Zhang Dong.

The United Element Sect Patriarch didn’t remain passive. He did a similar wave of the wrist and an intricate sword appeared in his hand.The blade was very straight and had an ethereal feel to it. It was a type of jian sword with a snow-white hilt. The blade crackled with lightning energy that switched between blue and gold.

But before the two men could launch their attacks a booming voice was heard.

“Halt, fighting in Rain Dragon City is forbidden!”

A group of cultivators appeared wearing Yinglong Pavilion robes, one of them was a master in the middle nascent stage realm. He looked at the two men with scorn in his eyes and pointed some kind of golden medallion at them. The moment he did a bubble of energy appeared around each one of the patriarchs.

Zhang Dong didn’t react as he expected something like this to happen. He knew that fighting in the city was frowned upon. There were other ways to go about things like this here. He placed his sword back into his spatial ring and looked at the new person that arrived. It was probably someone from the disciplinary hall of this city.

The Silver Spear Patriarch was less amused than Zhang Dong. He looked at the new arrival with spite and was still brandishing his spear.

“Don’t interfere, that young whelp insulted my sect!”

“It doesn’t matter what your grievances are, fighting in the city is strictly forbidden. If you wish to continue you will have to move to the Rain Tiger Arena!”

There it was, the arena. Things such as it existed in most of the developed cities here. It was a place where people could fight against each other. Killing and crippling were also allowed but fights between powerful nascent cultivators was something very rare. Most of them would avoid such an outcome unless there was a good reason for it.

Zhang Dong was doing this on purpose. This was still part of his plan. The first option went out of the window the moment this nascent soul master appeared. He would have just let it be and walked into the hotel if he didn’t show up. As someone strong he didn’t need to give face to other sect’s junior members. The Silver Spear Sect could have let it slide but this leader of theirs apparently had a short fuse.

The moment he saw his sect getting disrespected by a nascent soul cultivator he jumped out. Zhang Dong also felt that there was another master of similar power still hiding, he probably belonged to the Golden Saber Sect faction. That person was smart enough to not come out. This spared him from potential combat and loss of face.

Zhang Dong was now using the angry Chang Yongzheng as a pawn. Though he didn’t know how far the man would take this. His plan involved moving it towards the arena, to begin with. But if the nascent soul master just apologized he would leave it at that. Something as that would probably not happen though.

“Rain Tiger Arena?”

Yongzheng looked at the man in the white robe. The moment he did Zhang Dong raised his chin to look up to him. The corner of his lip tightened and slightly rose on one side of his face. The moment the powerful cultivator noticed that condescending look he lost it. He could clearly tell that the man was only a middle stage nascent realm cultivator. You could not fake something like this, there was a certain quality to your spiritual energy that gave things like that away.

“Fine, if he dares face me in that arena, I Chang Yongzheng will put my honor on the line and face this young whelp in combat! But does he dare to face me?”

You couldn’t force anyone to fight you in the arena. That was one of the rules that was in place in this city. Both parties had to agree and even sign a contract that would be overseen by the city officials.

Zhang Dong looked to the shouting man and then back to the disciplinary elders and gave a nod.

“Why wouldn’t I dare face someone weaker than me? But are you sure about this? I don’t like to bully old men, you can still save some face and reconsider it…”

He shrugged a bit while replying in a somewhat condescending tone. The people that were there were astonished. Was this young-looking man crazy or something? Why would he scrutinize a powerful sect leader like this? Was he really strong enough to beat him, or was he just putting on appearances to save face?

“You! I will slaughter you!”

The man almost popped a vein in his forehead after hearing what Zhang Dong had to say. He was a powerful nascent soul master from a formidable sect and he was getting disrespected like this.

When he appeared to help his juniors he intended to only reprimand the middle stage cultivator slightly. If he just apologized he would let him be without getting in his way. The man on the other hand didn’t budge and showed hostility towards him.

He had to give it to him, he was really strong for his age. He attributed his haughty attitude to gaining his power too fast and being inexperienced. He had no idea who this person was but he was probably just an elder from another middle sized sect. If he killed him in a sanctioned match no one could say anything against it. The middle sized sects were all very close to each other when strength was involved. Thus they didn’t fear arguing with each other or even doing battle.

“Silence!”

The bubbles radiated light while holding the two people in them, increasing their defensive capabilities as the Patriarch from the Silver Spear Sect was about to force it open with his rage.

“I can’t stop you if you both agree to face each other. This is a serious matter where death is a possibility so think about this hard fellow Daoists. Your belongings will be delivered to your next of kin if this happens.”

The man started explaining the rules of the arena to two angry-looking masters. He was slowly sweating and was nervous. Mostly the people that fought in the arena were core formation and below, the nascent soul masters mostly kept a clear head in such matters. Very rarely they would fight, most of the time it happened when the sects were already at war with each other.

Zhang Dong just nodded and his opponent did the same. He placed his spear back in his spatial ring. He had to show this upstart how the world really worked, depending on the situation he would deliver a crippling blow or kill him outright. He wasn’t that stupid and was already sending a transmission to his retainers. He needed to know who this man was, depending on the outcome he might need to leave him alive. If he was from a weaker sect, it would be fine to maim him and show that he was not to be trifled with.

The disciplinary elder gave out a sigh, he would get everything ready within the next couple hours. He explained where the arena was and that he would prepare everything for the two. They could now get ready by meditating or getting other weapons. Using treasures and weapons was allowed as that was considered part of your personal strength.

The word that two powerhouses were going to fight spread throughout the whole city. The names Zhang Dong and Chang Yongzheng were written on the board in all of the betting dens in the city. After a quick background check their identities were revealed.

The first one was the Patriarch from a new middle sized sect. The number of their nascent soul cultivators wasn’t fully known but it was rumored to be between three to six. The other one was a more renowned sect, their strength would be ranked below the previous Dark Palm sect but not by much.

The feats of Zhang Dong couldn’t be confirmed as other individuals interfered. Due to this, the stakes were against him 3 to 1. The Silver Spear sect’s Patriarch was an old monster that got to the top due to his famous spear arts. He was a renowned spear grandmaster, even seeing him in action would be worth the entrance fee to this event.

Everyone started clamoring to get a ticket, this would be quite the fight. One was an unknown new master while the other one was an old seasoned monster. It was a fight of the old against the young, who would come out on top, no one knew.

Chapter 225

Zhang Dong and his entourage were finally able to enter the hotel that they were supposed to stay in. The people outside had cleared out and went to the arena to get their tickets.

“Patriarch, aren’t you being too rash? Wasn’t there another way to handle that situation…”

Feng Maling asked with visible concern showed on her face. She had watched the whole thing unfold but it was not her place to speak out in that situation. She was also worried that she might have been too rough when shouting at the youths.

“To rash? Don’t think so, think that played out very well actually.”

Zhang Dong looked at the inside of the room he was in. It was very large and exquisite. There was a giant red king-sized bed, its legs were golden and four golden dragon heads were peeking out. There was a large window with a nice view of the city and he had this room all for himself. The other elders would get rooms on a lower level as this one was reserved for him as a sect leader.

“Played out well? I don’t understand…”

The granny wrinkled her nose and touched the base of her neck while asking her sect leader for clarification. Most people would evade combat in a situation like that. Was this young leader still too inexperienced and let his emotions guide his path?

“Grandmother, how do you think a young beast goes about earning respect from its pack?”

He answered her with a question, to which the old woman replied without thinking.

“Defeat an older beast to prove itself?”

Zhang Dong nodded at the question and Feng Maling didn’t really know what to say. This young leader wanted to prove himself to the other old monsters in a trial of combat. This would probably be the easiest and most direct way to gain respect. It was also the best way to lose face if he lost.

“Are you confident?”

She asked while moving closer to her nephew in law.

“Very. You should stop worrying, I know what you are thinking. This move might offend that Silver Spear Sect and its leader but it will also deter others. Also, you should know that our sect isn’t that weak anymore, we don’t need to hide as much as we did before.”

Zhang Dong wasn’t planning on doing things this way at first but an opportunity arose. After showing his might the other sects would probably see him in a new light. With this, he could probably evade any further problems that this banquet would bring.

The old nascent soul cultivators would see him as strong but brash. Thus they would fear to offend him. Offending him could mean being challenged just like Chang Yongzheng was. They would only lose face if they got defeated by a young upstart. Even if Zhang Dong lost or tied he would still be seen as someone strong. Getting beaten by an established master wasn’t that bad to someone that lacked renown. On the flipside, the reverse was devastating to your reputation.

“I probably shouldn’t mention this to your wife.”

Granny Maling nodded to herself while Matt flinched. If news of this reached his wife she would probably worry or maybe fly into an unrivaled rage and try to beat up that Spear sect Patriarch.

“That would be best, no use making her worry in the state she is.”

Zhang Dong got a bit sad at the mention of his wife. He didn’t want to be here so far away from them but he needed to get this done. While the city owners were getting the arena fight ready others were getting curious about it.

The word about Zhang dongs and Chang Yongzheng fight even reached the city lord's ear. This was a very powerful cultivator and he also had backing of a lot of other families. After hearing that the two fighters were from the lesser middle sized sects he wasn’t that interested. He just gave out an order to record the fight as it could be used later.

Not everyone reacted in a bored way as the city lord though. All of the sects that had already arrived were sure to make their way towards the arena. They were mostly there to see the Silver Spear Sect leader’s spearmanship. There was also the idiot who was trying to fight that legendary spear master. They needed to know who was so brazen and brave to do this.

Within a couple of hours, everything was ready for the big event. The arena was really large, a lot bigger than the one that the Zhang Clan juniors attended in Jade Grass City. It had three levels going upwards and in one spot there was a large platform with exclusive seats for the nascent soul masters and their sect members.

There was not much to do for the middle sized sects as the banquet would only start in two days. The price of attendance was only a couple of middle grade spirit stones. This was something that most people in the upper section of the empire could afford.

“Zhang Dong? Never heard of someone like that…”

“United Element Sect, aren’t they just a branch sect from somewhere?”

“Didn’t think we would see master Chang Yongzheng’s spearmanship, this trip was worthwhile. Hope that poor country bumpkin he is fighting doesn’t lose too fast.”

Cultivators chatted with each other before the battle started. Some people were still pouring into the large stadium-like arena and the fighters weren’t there. The two were busy with something else for now.

Zhang Dong moved a quill on some parchment that after finishing glowed with a blue light. He hadn’t used something like this before but he knew what it was. It was a binding contract that would be sealed by their Qi signature.

Contracts like this didn’t see much value in this world. Most of the time they were invalidated by someone with more power. They were used by weaker cultivators though and with someone of a higher standing as a witness.

The Yinglong Pavilion was a strong faction that could act as someone like that. They had a storage area where they stored all of the contracts. In this city what they said was law so with proof of it the other sects could not complain.

What Zhang Dong was signing here was just an agreement of both parties. This was not a deathmatch and if an accident occurred they would need to pay a hefty sum to the other sect.

Zhang Dong wanted to laugh. The number of spirit stones he would need to pay wasn’t that high for any of the sides. For some reason, his side would need to pay more than the Silver Spear Sect if they lost their leader. There was little fear of killing if you just had enough spirit stones.

They both signed it and walked out. Zhang Dong wasn’t planning on killing his opponent even though he could afford the exchange. The price of the man’s life was equal to about one or two heaven grade treasures. This quite frankly wasn’t something too hard for him as with his crafting abode and the right materials he could craft weapons in bunches.

The two masters finally appeared on the stage. Chang Yongzheng was first, he floated to the large stage that was the size of several football fields. The people started cheering the moment they saw the old man with the white beard gently float down. He pulled out his famous silver spear which was an artifact that was handed down from generation to generation in his sect. It was also a high grade heavenly treasure that was always given to the acting sect leader.

“It’s master Chang Yongzheng!”

“He is looking ferocious as always!”

“That’s The legendary Saint Spear of legends, his opponent is done for!”

The people shouted out once more and the nascent soul master reacted by swishing his long robe sleeves at them. The moment he did the crown burst out in cheers even louder than before.

Zhang Dong arrived not long after, there was an announcer as always and he only came out when his name was mentioned. The crowd wasn’t as loud as before as they were more curious than excited about this man’s roots. Why was he here, how strong was he and why would he offend such a famous spear master?

The man was wearing a tight looking white robe with some strange metallic parts to it. His shoulders were covered and looked like they would be able to take some punishment. He pulled out his own weapon which was the sword that he previously used. It looked a lot less intricate than the glowing spear but the experts in the stands knew that it wasn’t behind it in terms of quality.

“If you bow down and show respect I will forget about your transgration, don’t throw away your future, boy.”

Chang Yongzheng said while brandishing his spear. The whole arena ground started rising into the air and was surrounded by a transparent bubble. This was a strong formation that would protect the weaker cultivators from the energy these two powerful elders would exude.

“I could say the same to you, if you bow down and show your respect, I will let you leave with your honor intact. I don’t enjoy bullying people weaker than myself, it would be wise for you to reconsider.”

Zhang Dong replied while his opponent’s forehead vein increased in size. These old masters were used to being put up on a pedestal. Everyone around them just nodded their heads and agreed with whatever they said. This wasn’t respect though, it was just plain fear. No one could go against a person like this, there would be no victory.

Due to this people like Chang Yongzheng were even worse than some of the young masters as they had no one keeping them in check. They mostly grew arrogant with old age as there wasn’t anyone to call them out if they made a wrong decision. The man here would soon have a rude awakening from his life of pride.

The man flourished his spear the moment the announcer gave them the signal to begin the battle. Zhang Dong raised his brow slightly as he noticed that the man was using a familiar skill. An electrical current gathered around him and the spear he was holding began crackling with lightning energy.

‘Interesting… a lesser dao of the storms?’

He wanted to chuckle as he finally met a person who was using this dao. Most people confused his greater dao of lightning with the lesser version. This would make the fight even easier than he expected. As someone with the knowledge of a higher tier dao he could predict the man’s moves even better.

“Take my attack if you dare! Lightning Tempest Spear First Form: Hundred Thousand Thunder Strikes!

The man shouted out his attack before thrusting forward. It was quite a mouthful and the wording explained this technique. It looked like thousands upon thousands of spear thrusts were coming his way. All of them were engulfed in lightning and wind energies. Aiming wasn’t even important as the attack covered almost all of the arena and was going right at him.

“Oh no, the elder is using that Lightning Tempest Spear art, his opponent will surely perish!”

“Serves him right for offending the sect leader!”

The youths from the Silver Spear sect were all there, their eyes sparkling as they had the honor of seeing their sect master’s spearmanship. They were sure to not blink in fear of not catching the master’s intricate moves.

Zhang Dong on the other hand exuded a small amount of aura and surrounded his sword with it. A runic pattern appeared on the blade shaft and he received the strike with his own. The sword movement looked slow and sluggish to the naked eye and it was going against a wave of multiple strikes. From what the people could tell, the white-haired man was done for.

But then something unexpected occurred. A resounding explosion of Qi followed by silence, the defensive formation buckled under the pressure but held out. What the audience saw was unfathomable, the weak looking blade that Zhang Dong thrust forward managed to intercept the spear right at its point.

The older cultivator was baffled by this result, no one had ever defended himself against his attack in this way. He had thrust out thousands of times in a matter of a second but his spear was caught. It was done by a feeble looking sword and the man performing the task didn’t look phased at all.

“Hundred thousand thrusts? Did you even get to five thousand with that?”

Zhang Dong smirked a bit, he wouldn’t just be ending the fight with one move. No, defeating this man too fast would only make people say that it was some kind of fluke. He needed the people to actually witness his might in action.

Chapter 226

The whole stadium went silent. Just a moment ago they saw that overbearing technique of one of the best spear masters in the whole empire. They were ecstatic to witness it in all its glory. This sense of wonder was shattered instantly by the cultivator with white hair. He had just brushed off such an attack with ease, leaving everyone speechless.

“What is this, the Master from the United Element sect has managed to block Chang Yongzheng's glorious approach! How will the old master react!”

The audience was brought back to attention by the announcer’s voice. They instantly cheered out loud and the whole arena started trembling once more. This was more than they bargained for, they expected Zhang Dong to at most doge while getting hit a couple of times. Not to block the whole strike entirely.

The older cultivator looked at the tip of the sword that Zhang Dong was holding. His spear tip was directly pressing into it. He couldn’t make it budge at all and he was even holding his weapon with two hands while his opponent was using just one. Where was this monstrous strength coming from? Was this man also a body refiner?

He didn’t want to believe it but it was hard to deny the fact that this man had caught his attack. He wasn’t just thrusting multiple times with his spear. He was actually creating many copies of his attack with his Qi which made it look like thousands of spear strikes were coming Zhang Dong’s way. Somehow the man he was going against managed to pinpoint the one true spear attack and block it without effort.

After pushing his spear against the sword the older cultivator decided to retreat. His opponent didn’t seem to be bothered by his action and didn’t even follow up with an attack of his own. He just stood there with his sword in hand and one hand behind his back as if he was waiting for something.

“You…”

The old man’s face contorted and his teeth were seen as he clenched his jaw out. The silvery spear that he was holding started glowing once more. He moved it above his head and he began to spin it around.

Chang Yongzheng knew what the younger cultivator was doing. This was something prideful and haughty individuals would do. The man before him was probably convinced of his superiority and that he wasn’t a threat. This was obvious as he didn’t follow up after defending. It was a great chance as the older man was caught off guard.

“Zhang Dong was it… You will regret not striking when you had the chance!”

While speaking Yongzheng’s body started flickering with bright light and then crackling with blue lightning. The spear that he was spinning around produced a giant cyclone that surrounded the whole arena.

The two men were still in the protective formation that surrounded them. The wind elements produced razor-sharp blades of energy that were everywhere. A normal nascent cultivator would be shredded by those in a matter of seconds, nothing remaining but bloody bones.
“Lightning Tempest Spear third form: Execution of the Thunder Tempest!”

The man shouted while Zhang Dong surrounded his body with a thin layer of golden energy. This was apparently enough to defend himself against the thin blades of wind energy.

The people in the audience went wild. The first form of the spear art this master was already breathtaking but this was something else entirely. The amount of spiritual energy that was getting produced was making the whole defensive formation shake and tremble. A little bit more and it might begin to crack.

“That Zhang Dong was just lucky, now when the sect leader is serious he has no chance!”

“Yes, he should surrender and beg the elder for forgiveness!”

The youths and other members from the Silver Spear sect quickly recovered. They started laughing and smiling once more while looking at the unfolding battle.

Due to the tornado inside the ring the visibility of the whole fight suffered. Most people could only see an outline of a man glowing in gold on one side. Then on the other side, there was his opponent glowing in blue light.

Sounds of thunder and lightning frightened some of the weaker cultivators. Some of the nascent soul aura was leaking from the stage which also caused some of them to pass out.

On the inside, there was a giant cyclone. A mix of lightning and wind energies were slowly approaching their apex. Even then, the white-haired opponent didn’t seem to be doing anything besides surrounding himself with his aura.

“Fool, I will show you what happens when you disregard your opponent, let this be a lesson for you, receive my divine attack!”

The old man shouted out with resolve. This third form of his spear art took some time to charge but when it did there was no escape. The moment he lowered his spear the wind and lightning energies would fuse into one grand attack.

The people outside the arena that were directly behind Zhang Dong gulped hard. They knew that if that formation couldn’t take the blow that they could be injured. Luckily right before the old cultivator swung his spear down the formation started glowing.

Another protective bubble appeared over the one that the two elders were fighting in. Then ethereal shackles of some sort wrapped themselves around the glowing orb. This showed that the whole formation had been strengthened and would even be able to take a hit from a great circle realm cultivator.

Chang Yongzheng finally swung his spear down and the whole place exploded. The people in the stands held their breaths as the lightning and wind energies shone in a blinding light.

The protective formation shook under the strain and the first barrier that there broke. The green and blue elemental energies slammed into the second reinforced one while the spectators worried.
What was happening inside that formation was hard to see, the green and blue lights were so bright that Zhang Dong’s faint golden aura couldn’t be seen anymore. Thus most people began thinking that the attack must have gone through and the man inside had been defeated, he might have even been dead.

The old seniors from the United Element sect were sweating bullets. None of them beside Feng Maling knew how strong their Patriarch actually was. The use of soul beasts was also forbidden during this type of one on one arena battle so he couldn’t defend himself with its help. They were expecting the worst but they relaxed somewhat when they glanced over to the old lady. Zhang Dong’s grandmother seemed unimpressed by the whole display of might.

She was one of the rare people that had the pleasure to witness Zhang Dong’s full might. He sometimes sparred out in the Dimensional Regalia space with other nascent soul cultivators. She knew how strong he was and how he compared to the person he was fighting against.

Just as the attack that Chang Yongzheng threw at Zhang Dong had ended something strange occurred. Following a flash of light, the lightning and wind energies started getting sucked into one spot. It was as if a giant vacuum was just engulfing all of the spiritual energy that was trapped with the two nascent soul elders inside.

“W-what is that?”

“How can that…”

The audience gasped as they saw a quite lively looking Zhang Dong just standing there. His opponent opposite him, the old man’s eyes bulging out wide.

The white-haired man was holding his hand up and his index finger was pointing towards the heavens. Above his finger, there was a small sphere about the size of a basketball. It was slowly expanding in size while absorbing all of the energies within the ring.

“You had your fun, now it's my turn. This might not really be the real thing, but it packs a punch, hope you can survive it…”

The orb of light radiated a strange power and the area around it looked to be distorting space. The mass of strange energy started expanding in a matter of seconds and it exuded a lot of heat magnetic and gravitational energies.

Chang Yongzheng looked at the strange attack that his opponent was preparing and charged forward. He wouldn’t let Zhang Dong finish whatever he was doing, if he did he knew it would be the end for him.

“Rude, I let you have your time… buzz off!”

The old spear user thrust his spear forward towards the man that was giving out a tremendously powerful aura. He expected to at least interrupt this ghastly attack and force Zhang Dong into a more traditional bout. To his shock, he wasn’t able as just the massive spike in spiritual energy forced him back.

It was already too late, the attack was reaching completion and he had no place to run. He looked at the huge sphere of light that was up in the air and about ten meters in diameter. He activated his defensive treasures and gathered his energies. If his opponent managed to defend himself, so would he. This attack was very powerful but he doubted that the young opponent would have much spiritual energy left after performing it. In his eyes, if he managed to defend himself it would be his victory.

The people in the audience looked at Zhang Dong moving his finger forward and the sphere slowly descended.

“I don’t really have a grand name for this attack, but you can call it a pseudo-pulsar, now catch it!”

The whole stage trembled and another set of shackles latched themselves onto the protective bubble. The amount of force that was being displayed here started reaching into the great circle level of power. The other nascent soul cultivators started gulping as they noticed this discovery.

A giant explosion rocked the Rain Dragon Arena. The people in the stands were holding onto each other as the protective formation cracked under the strain. The people responsible continued to activate supportive outer shells that kept cracking. Soon the shackles burst from the strain and evaporated into tiny Qi particles.

The protective array burst open and a couple of nascent soul and core formation elders jumped in. They strained their cultivation to block the pressure that was coming towards them. They somehow succeeded to stop the blast from reaching the people outside. Mostly thanks to it having used up most of its energy within the arena.

Everyone was flabbergasted, they looked to the stage that was supposed to be there. The floating platform had been burned to cinders and blaster to rubble. The worried Silver Spear Sect cultivators searched for their elder with their eyes.

“Oh now… the Sect Leader, how could this be!”

They spotted him down on the ground, naked and with his bare bottom raised into the air. His head was buried in the ground below and his body was slightly twitching. He was alive but out cold and his robes had evaporated.

Zhang Dong was still floating up in the air. He gave out a sigh while looking at the destruction that he had caused. He even had to use some of his energies to block out the blast from causing too much damage outside.

He had made this technique for fun. It wasn’t very good for a real fight as it took some time to charge and was very volatile. It did pack quite the punch though but only if the enemy didn’t run away. It was perfect for a small cage match like this where the opponent couldn’t escape.

‘Did I overdo it a bit?’

He glanced at the shiny ass of the elder that he defeated. His body hair had also been scorched, the man might have not survived if he didn’t have enough protective treasures. Zhang Dong also canceled out the attack at a critical juncture as he didn’t want to kill anyone. He only wanted to display some of his power. Now he felt like no one would try seeking trouble with him.

“Senior...Chang Yongzheng, looks to have lost consciousness… the winner is, Zhang Dong from the United Element Sect!”

The announcer called out while the audience kept quiet from the shock of seeing their favorite lose so easily.

Chapter 227

Chang Yongzheng naked ass was sticking out from the rubble. The whole floating stage that the two fighters were on was blown up along with the protective shielding. Zhang Dong was victorious and he was hovering in the air with both his hands behind his back. He was sure to look presentable for the peanut gallery, making yourself look unfazed was part of the plan.

The people in the arena were stunned, the attack that this senior had performed was just too overbearing. In normal circumstances without the powerful protective arrays, the whole arena would have probably been destroyed. The blast would probably take everyone in here out, even most of the nascent soul cultivators wouldn’t escape unharmed.

‘That’s the expressions I’ve wanted to see. It seems like my plan has worked, hope no one will seek vengeance with me after this.’

Matt thought to himself while he glanced at the opened mouths of the cultivators. Everyone was sure that he would lose. He had also told his people to place a big bet on him, he made quite a small fortune in betting a large sum on himself.

He needed to keep up with his haughty exterior appearance for now. If the cultivators feared his might they would think twice before talking to him. No one should approach him without a good reason and the fight didn’t really show much of his true abilities. He wasn’t worried that it would be used to counter his attacks that much.

“Let us depart to the hotel, then you are free to visit the city as you please.”

Zhang Dong waved his hand and plucked the old farts from his faction from the arena. They would pick up the spirit stones later after the dust had settled. While leaving the people kept glancing at his form and after he left the whole arena erupted.

“D-did you see that? Where did such a powerful master come from?”

“This is a big scoop! We must report this to our sect and tell everyone to watch out for the United Element’s Sect”

“How could this be, our Sect Leader Lost…”

Various people shouted out. The cultivators from the sect that Zhang Dong offended couldn’t believe what just happened. Their current sect leader was smashed to the ground like some kind of bug. They couldn’t even see how this happened, there were just giant explosions after one another and this was the result. They quickly descended to the stage and put a robe over their leader’s exposed posterior. He would probably have to disappear from this banquet, for now, the shame was far too big.

A lot of influential people were watching Zhang Dong leave. Everyone made sure to report this to their leaders and elders, this man was clearly someone that you couldn’t offend. Normally even if the cultivator was strong the masters could hope to achieve victory if they worked together. In this city on the other hand they would need to face their opponents in a 1 on 1 match.

This United Element Sect’s leader was clearly a seasoned warrior with a lot of power. When the news and recordings reached the people present in the city everyone gave out a decree. Offending Zhang Dong was out of the question, interacting with him was also forbidden.
The sect leaders were all experienced in the cultivator life. The only reason the Silver Spear Sect leader went through with the arena match was because he thought his opponent was only in the middle stage. No one in the middle stage could actually be so powerful, the only explanation was that he was somehow hiding his true strength.

This was only a half-truth as Zhang Dong was indeed hiding his real power level. Yet, he really was only in the middle stage, not even that close to the late stage with his Qi cultivation. No one suspected him of having an immortal level cultivation manual though. Having something like that was too far fetched, in the minds of these old masters a cultivation manual like that was just a thing of legends.

‘Hope they overthink everything as always and leave me alone now.’

Zhang Dong thought while returning to the hotel. The people there moved their heads down and opened up a path. Everyone was already informed about what transpired in the arena. There was no televised announcement but the communication jades worked well to spread the information.

No one dared look him in the eyes now. He saw everyone looking at the ground, be it, servant or cultivator. The elders and seniors from other sects didn’t dare to offend him anymore. This reinforced the notion that he made the right decision.

If he ignored the commotion or let the juniors fight outside the hotel he might have evaded one issue. The problem was that such events could very well take place all over the city. He and his sect didn’t have much of a reputation.

Factions like that were bullied a lot and had to prove their worth. With a clear show of might, he was now able to protect himself and his people from harm. They would think twice before asking for a duel or shouting out to them. The only people that might think of going against him would be the sect leaders from the more powerful middle sized sects. Those would be arriving tomorrow though and might not take the warnings of others to heart.

Back in the hotel Zhang Dong sat down on a comfy armchair. The elders that he had come with were now allowed to leave into the city if they so desired. Feng Maling and the others decided otherwise. They felt like they were sticking out too much as it was.

This was also why he brought them here. The youths might have gotten foolhardy after seeing their sect leader winning so easily. He didn’t know every person from his sect and the alignments that they had only showed a general idea of their core values. If they started fights with others over small things was unknown.

“That will be all, we will all gather when it's time for the banquet then, if you want to remain in your quarters then it's up to you.”

Zhang Dong said while the group of old people walked out. They were far less adventurous than the youngsters so they would probably stay out of trouble.

He was now left alone in his room with a clear look at the city. It had a similar cultural layout as the other cities but it was somehow busier. Many well lit up signs were all over the place that were mostly just ads. It really showed that this was a city of merchants as stores littered every corner.

‘Should be fine for now, daddy will come home soon…’

He placed a little round plate on the table. It had some strange inscriptions on it. It was slightly larger than a plate used for teacups. He pointed his finger at it and some spiritual energy shot out of it. The plates' inscriptions started to light up and glow in blue color. They changed patterns until finally settling on one while shining even brighter.

He started hearing a ringing sound, the noise was something similar to what people heard when listening to someone pick up the phone. He started tapping his finger on the table that the device was on and caused it to shake due to his increased strength.

Finally, after about thirty seconds of beeping, he heard a familiar sound. The connection went through and a beam of blue light shot out of the plate looking artifact. It expanded outwardly and increased in size the further it went.

Zhang Dong made sure to block out any other spiritual senses with his own aura before activating this device. He didn’t want anyone snooping around while he was doing this.

The blue light started showing an image, it was the face of a beautiful woman with caramel-like skin. This was his wife, Feng Liena looking at him.

What he was using was something akin to a hologram phone. It could also send the image from both places so the callers could see each other on the holographic displays. It was a bit funny but holograms were a lot easier to make in this world than regular flat screens.

He had produced something like this so that he could talk with his lovely wife. This artifact was something the United Element Sect produced and was untraceable by the others.

“Oh, there you are hubby. I was getting worried.”

The twenty-year-old looking woman pouted a bit while looking at Zhang Dong’s face on her side. Her husband just shifted his eyes to the side and scratched his neck. This prompted Feng Liena on the other side to raise a brow and stare. She knew her husband very well by this point, so she knew that he was hiding something.

“Oh nothing, I just had to talk with a couple of elders on the way and it took more time than I expected.”

Due to this treasure, he invented his wife demanded that he call her regularly. Even though she believed in him she was worried that something might happen to him. He was supposed to call her after getting to the hotel but he failed to do so as he was busy thinking about the fight. He also feared that she would worry if he told her what he was planning to do before the match.

“Is that so, my dear husband?”

Zhang Dong gulped as he could hear the tone shift in her voice. He didn’t want to worry her but it would probably be better to just come clean. Otherwise, he would probably need to sleep outside his bed chambers when he got back home.

He wasn’t sure when it happened but their power dynamic equaled itself out after a while. In the beginning stages of their marriage, his wife was very submissive and always listened to what he said. After some time passed she got a lot more comfortable around him and would now sometimes second guess him, mostly when he tried pulling a fast one on her.

“Well… you see when I first arrived here I met this one uncle with a monocle and a top hat, after that…”

He slowly started explaining from the start. Feng Liena just nodded as he continued and he didn’t really see her change her expression much even after he mentioned the fight. She did seem made the moment he mentioned the Silver Spear Sect leader disrespecting him though.

“Hm, Silver Spear Sect… I think I’ve heard about them; they are quite far away from our sect grounds…”

She murmured to herself.

“You did well hubby, you were far too lenient, I would have at least cut off his hand or leg!”

Zhang Dong’s face twitched a bit. His dear wife was a true cultivator, things like face and honor still mattered to her. She wouldn’t let her family be disrespected, she felt like her husband was still a bit too soft. This was also one of the reasons that she sometimes was hard on him. Zhang Dong didn’t really have the values that the usual people that lived in this world had.

So a strange relationship came to be. On one side was Feng Liena that wanted him to be a bit more ruthless against his enemies. On the other was Zhang Dong who wanted his wife to be a bit less ruthless and maybe show some mercy once in a while.

“I don’t know if that man has any backing, it would be unwise to cripple or kill him in the heat of the moment.”

He explained himself and his wife had to agree. While the two chatted another visitor appeared. He could see a child’s face being pressed against Feng Liena’s and it was his little cinnamon roll. He laughed and waved at his cute child, if this went well he would be returning to his family within a week.

Chapter 228

Another day passed, the more prominent middle sized sect leaders finally started to arrive. The news of the arena fight was already widely spread which mostly caused people to laugh at the Silver Spear Sect Patriarch's blunder.

Now the eyes were on Zhang Dong. There were recording devices in this world that were able to catch this fight. They were only available for the more prominent masters as they required a lot of spiritual energy as fuel. They also had a few drawbacks in the way they recorded things.

Most people that saw the recording were shocked at the display of might. Was this Zhang Dong so powerful or was his opponent just old and weak? No one actually was willing to confirm this with another duel as Zhang Dong's plan seemed to have worked.

The biggest downside to this plan was the exposure. Now the other sects would be wary of him and probably make some plans before engaging him in combat. This didn’t matter that much as his personal strength wasn’t everything. He still had his sect members to help him out in a bind.

A group of five ships were flying towards the meeting place of all the sects. They were quite big and had an unusual shape. Instead of the regular boat shape, they looked like large white swords with masts on them.

How most ships operated in this world was with magical treasures that made them float. They would then put large masts on them that would propel the ship forward. Other treasures would blow more wind at the sails or they would glide through the air without the help of such add-ons.

This small ship armada that had a peculiar sword look was almost there. On the inside of the flagship that was the largest, a certain man was sitting. This was someone that Zhang Dong would recognize, a person that he didn’t get along too well. It was the Patriarch from the Limitless Sword Society.

The man was sitting in his own cabin alone. His robe was pure white and it had the symbol for ‘sword’ embroiled on the back. The man was grasping a communication jade in his hand and listening to a report.

“He did?... Interesting…”

He just heard the news about Zhang Dong’s victory and he was surprised. The man that he went against, Chang Yongzheng was someone that he actually sparred against. He considered the Silver Spear Sect’s Leader’s spear to be weaker than his sword but this master shouldn’t have been such an easy opponent.

“Was he lucky or…”

The man thought back to the time that he witnessed Zhang Dong’s might. He had seen him battle the Patriarch from the Dark Palm Sect. He had left an impression on him back then and with this Zhan Jie was itching for a fight. One reason was that he wanted to test the younger cultivator and the other was that he wanted to put him in his place.

The United Element Sect was treated by this Patriarch as a sort of servant. They were paying tribute to the Limitless Sword Society which lowered their status. With Zhang Dong’s victory over a well-established master his sects prestige might be called into question. Rumors might spread that Zhang Dong is actually stronger than he was.

“Hm… we shall see, I need to see the fight's recording first.”

The man placed the communication jade back into his spatial ring. He was itching for a fight but wouldn’t start it without any information. He wanted to prove that his sect was strong and that he was the superior swordmaster. Zhang Dong was also a swordsman, this just made this Zhan Jie want to clash blades with him. He wouldn’t force a fight though if the man remained respectful he wouldn’t really seek trouble.

In the other ships from other sects, similar scenes were playing out. Zhang Dong’s name and his sects became the hot topic of this banquet.

Due to this a lot of people that weren’t there to witness the fight were clamoring for the recording device. This device looked like an apple-sized orb with some intricate symbols on it. A person needed to insert some of his spiritual sense into it and the artifact would show them a vision.

The vision would show an illusion of the fight that had taken place. The artifact didn’t show a hologram as the ones that Zhang Dong had made. It injected the image directly into the user’s mind. They could move around this world of illusions and see the fight from all sides.

The problem was the quality, high concentrations of spiritual energy would warp and change the image inside the device. This meant that the person using this would most likely only see a similar image that the people in the arena witnessed. If they tried going into the middle of the fight where the two experts fought they wouldn’t be able to see much.

Also it was impossible for this artifact to accurately measure the power of the techniques that were used. This was something that only experts in the close vicinity of it would be able to tell. This would also leave everyone to speculate about Zhang Dong’s true strength. Which was something that the man in question was banking on. Leaving himself in a shroud of mystery would keep everyone on their toes.

It took some time for the more pristine sects to arrive. The three that went against the Dark Palm sect all those years ago were all here. Besides them, there were seven more on a similar footing as them.

Even though these people were on the very top of power if you compared them to the other large sects. They were nothing compared to the big three that occupied the middle part of the empire. Those were rumored to have multiple nascent soul masters at the great circle of the nascent soul.

No one was really sure, fights between the big three didn’t really happen very often. They had been like this for thousands of years now. Some new masters came and some succumbed to their old age but no one was willing to go into an all out war.

The sects below those three top powers were a different thing. At most, they had a great circle nascent soul master hidden away. Just like the Dark Palm sect each of these middle sized ones had hidden masters just cultivating and hoping for a breakthrough. They would never show themselves unless their life was in danger and the sect was about to fall.

From time to time an upstart like the United Element Sect appeared. Sometimes they would last and other times they would fade away into obscurity. Some old established sects would also sometimes lose their old masters due to accidents, old age, or cultivation failure.

There was one sect like this arriving. This faction was called the Divine Fist Sect and hard times had arrived for them. They were considered to be one of the very top of the sects below the big three. Very few people ever sought trouble with them and they were known to be a just sect with not many enemies.

Three large flying ships with their flag of a bright golden fist were slowly arriving at the Rain Dragon City. An old-looking man with silver hair was sitting down in a secluded chamber. He wasn’t alone as there was a young-looking woman with golden hair right next to him.

“Grandfather, are you sure we should attend? What if the other sects discover what had happened? What if they already know?”

The girl was there behind the old man, her facial expression showing signs of fright and worry.

“Little Meili, we have no choice. If we don’t attend the other sects will start asking questions. You know what will happen then…”

“But… What if they already know? Wouldn’t it be better to seek refuge behind our city's grand formation? Even if the other sects unite they won’t get through! It might not yet be too late what if the…”

“Child, this isn’t up for discussion!”

The man waved his finger and the golden-haired woman’s lips stopped moving. The girl looked maddened by the elder’s deed but couldn’t do anything about it. She was then brought outside by some senior members that were called in. One of these people moved in and bowed before the old man that the girl called grandfather previously.

“Acting Patriarch, we will be arriving shortly.”

“Ech, didn’t think I’d live long enough for someone like me to become the Patriarch, these are troubling times indeed.”

The other person in the room looked up, concerned on his face.

“That blasted beat tide...if it wasn’t for that…”

The two men remained silent, their sect was going through tough times but they had to attend this banquet. It would seem odd if they didn’t as they were always present as one of the more prestigious sects. Their strength wasn’t what it was though as they had suffered a large setback not so long ago. They were frantically trying to keep everything under wraps but it wasn’t looking good for them.

“Meili… she will remain in the city, I had made some arrangements. She will be safe here.”

The person the elder was talking to nodded as he knew what the old man was planning. In this neutral city, no harm would come to them but when they left and if their secret was out, they would be done for. What had happened to the Dark Palm Sect would befall them. The other sects would probably take this chance before they could recover and strike.

“When we are inside, remember to call me by my name. We can’t let them know that an elder like me had become the Patriarch.”

“It shall be done!”

The two separated and the old man used his spirit sense to scan out the area. His ship was docking now and they would be descending. After going to their hotel they would attend the banquet the next day.

This event didn’t consist of only talking and mingling with the other sects, no. This was also a place to show off. The junior members could participate in various competitions. There would even be a tournament with a spirit stone price.

This was also a place where old grudges could be cleared out. Deathmatches were allowed and would be sanctioned by the Yinglong Pavilion. Anyone refusing to participate would be looked down on but those that came out on top would be praised and rewarded.

One of those people that was considered a winner was sitting in his room. He was looking at the round baby face of his daughter. She was still young and kept trying to grab her father’s holographic head.

“Daddy will come back soon, I’ll bring a present for you, I heard they have a lot of toys here!”

Zhang Dong chuckled as he looked at his daughter that was bumbling about. Soon it would be time to go meet and mingle with the other sects. He didn’t know anyone there but after what happened in the arena the other day he felt like it should be a breeze.

“Say goodbye to daddy.”

“Bwa bwa dwady~”

The child waved her hand at the image of her smiling father before it flickered out of existence. On the other side, Zhang Dong’s face changed to a frown. Soon it would be the time to act, he needed to put on his game face and look as unapproachable as possible.

The oldies from his group would do all the heavy lifting as they were better with politics. What was in store for him he didn’t know but he would face it just like he always did. This time around, he had a whole sect and his family counting on him. Failure was not an option.

Chapter 229

It was finally time for the large banquet to commence. All of the sects had arrived and were already moving towards the area where part of the festivities would be taking place.

Each of these sects here were owners of large tracts of lands with millions and maybe even billions of people living in them. But they were only pieces of a larger whole which consisted of the whole Empire that they were part of.

Every leader from each of those sects was here. They gathered every ten years to discuss and measure their opponents. Some would remain silent while others would boast and seek trouble with factions that they were on bad terms with.

Most sects here were part of the old elite. They had been in power for hundreds or thousands of years. They were mostly here to uphold the status quo, yet some of the crafty cultivators wanted more. Just like with the Dark Palm Sect that used demonic arts to get ahead and finally perish under three others that went against it. The others were looking for cracks in the armors of their opponents and waiting for the right chance to strike.

Zhang Dong and his sect members were walking out of the hotel just like the other sects were. The moment he showed himself outside people started whispering. His face was well known after his small spar against the older Silver Spear Sect Patriarch. He and his sect disciples were nowhere to be seen as they were waiting for him and his group to leave first.

The men moved their heads to the side in fright of meeting his gaze. The ladies looked intrigued and were giving Zhang Dong all sorts of sensual gazes. He was a man of principle though and just kept his poker face up. His elders rubbed their chins and nodded.

They were glad that their Patriarch wasn’t the same man as his grandfather. If that man was here he would have already been choosing his next target from the beautiful fairy-like cultivator women here.

“Senior Dong, we welcome you and your sect members.”

A servant greeted Zhang Dong while standing in front of a carriage. This was with what he and his people would be brought to the banquet. Zhang Dong nodded and entered along with granny Maling. The other old farts would travel in a larger carriage behind them and together.

“Young Patriarch you did well, now no one should search for trouble with us.”

The granny reassured Zhang Dong as she knew the reason that he went through with that fight. Before it she also feared that the sect would be looked down on because of their lack of fame and prestige. Now thanks to Zhang Dong’s show of might she was reassured that nothing out of the ordinary would be happening.

The two of them entered the carriage and Zhang Dong nodded at his grandmother in agreement.

The vehicle they were in wasn’t a plain horse-drawn carriage. No, it was a smaller version of a flying ship with a beast that looked like a wyvern pulling it along through the air.
The seats inside were quite soft and the intricate patterns on them depicted the Yinglong Pavilion’s dragon and a couple of other creatures. The soon took off, the other sects were sure to wait till the ferocious United Element Sect’s Patriarch was gone before also walking out.

“That was terrifying…”

“It was hard for me to hold my breath so long, luckily he is gone…”

The people commented while looking into the distance. They would be following right after Zhang Dong and his party of oldies but they would be sure to avoid him like the plague during the festivities. He seemed to have a short fuse and was even willing to battle with other sect leaders in the arena.

They also knew that during the banquet the duels would be handled differently. They would be a lot more bloody and not in a safe place like the Rain Tiger Arena. Every nascent soul master that had witnessed the battle made sure to advise their sect members to not bother Zhang Dong’s faction. The ones that arrived a day later might not have gotten the memo though.

The regular people were greeted by roars of flying wyverns that were pulling carriages behind them. This was something that the adults were used to seeing every ten years when the sects arrived. The children pointed towards the sky and waved with smiles on their faces. They weren’t allowed to the banquet grounds but they could see the fireworks later that would be happening at night.

There were quite a bit of those flying contraptions in the air, some were being pulled by other creatures more akin to bats others to regular birds. Zhang Dong looked out through the small window at the scenery below, the buildings looked small from all the way up here. The people were the size of ants but if he chose so he could insert some spiritual energy into his eyes and take a closer peek.

“The people in this city seem to be relaxed, the city lord must be a fair leader.”

Zhang Dong mentioned while granny Maling nodded. It was easy to determine how people were fairing in the city. None of them would be smiling this much if they didn’t feel a certain amount of freedom. Most people in this world would even fear looking up into the air. They might catch the eye of some powerful cultivator who might feel offended.

Here the citizens didn’t seem to care. He wasn’t sure if it was a regular occurrence or if the people were feeling protected by the fighting ban that was placed on all the visiting sects.

“Indeed but they pale in comparison to our own citizens, you have done a good job in constructing such a grand city. Some of the elders think that you are being too generous to them.”

The granny continued talking while Zhang Dong looked outside. He couldn’t say that he was keeping the happiness level of his citizens up so that he could earn more Spirit Points in his system. He did prefer to keep them happy, the system’s incentives only made him go further beyond what he would normally do.

He had created many clinics and was using taxes to run them. Everyone had free healthcare which wasn’t that hard thanks to the advances in pill making and his healing techniques. He had scanned all the sect members and knew who to train as a doctor. This saved on time and on money as he was sure that the doctor would do a great job.

Even with that, he had to give it to the man leading this city. The streets were clean and everything looked orderly. Even when he started the fight with the Silver Spear leader the nascent soul guards arrived within a minute’s time to stop them.

For him, it was easy to cater to his citizens' needs as he had the system. It told him what they were lacking and even divided the city into districts. It was like a game of SimCity. He could even see the area his clinics or police stations covered. Then he just needed to look at the map and direct his sect members to build the buildings like in a game. He could then even watch the percentages go up when it was being built.

A person that managed to produce a similar city without help like he did was probably someone very smart. He had visited other cities before he was the king of the land and most of the clans ruining them didn’t care much for the common people in it.

“Oh? They do? Maybe I should see if I’m not being too generous towards them?”

Zhang Dong laughed while his grandma also gave out a chuckle. She actually was all for spending money on the people as it was showing clear results. Their sect was growing strong at a staggering rate; she could even see it contending with the other sects for power soon.

“So that’s where the banquet will be taking place? I guess the city lord didn’t scrooge out.”

He rubbed his chin while looking at the giant castle-like structure that they were heading towards. The eastern styled castle was quite large, giant stone arches and even some smaller floating islands that were producing magical looking waterfalls were part of this structure.

Behind the castle, there was more scenery that he couldn’t see yet. He could feel some powerful beasts roaming there and along with other cultivators. From what he knew these were a sort of hunting ground for the younger generation cultivators to show their might. A giant mountain peak was blocking the view a bit though.

Every ten years there would be a competition and the youngsters would compete for resources and honor. His two disciples were saddened by the fact that they were banned from participating in it. He had made this decision as he was frightened that they could get in some kind of a mess. Their cultivation was also a bit high as the juniors were capped to the foundation establishment level.

This was a classical setup. Young masters competing against each other in a friendly bout. Some of them would get offended during the initial party and then during the competition they would try to kill each other. It was also against the rules for the nascent soul masters to intervene and this was the biggest problem he had with this competition. If he couldn’t save them, he would rather have them train up back home. It was not yet time for them to reveal their might and cause trouble for him or the sect.

It was against the rules to help out but there was one way to avoid your junior’s demise. That was something that he wanted to avoid as it would just bode more trouble.

It seemed like they would be arriving shortly. The beast that was pulling them along gave out a large roar again and started flying down. He could see a nice patch of grass and some people standing below. He knew one of the people that was standing there as he had met him when he was entering the city.

The man was Sebas-Tian that looked like a British butler out of a soap opera. He had it all down to the monocle. He was standing there with quite a large assortment of beautiful ladies. These ladies in particular were wearing french maid uniforms with skirts a bit shorter than would normally be allowed.

The carriage finally landed and Zhang Dong made his way outside. The maids formed a sort of passage for the arriving guests and the person greeting them would apparently be this man. This was a bit surprising, having a nascent soul cultivator do a task like this meant that the people behind him were just so much stronger.

“Good morning ol’ chap!”

The man greeted Zhang Dong in the usual fashion. And even took down his tophat for the greeting. The two exchanged some pleasantries before entering the banquet grounds. There were more people arriving so the butler looking master wasn’t able to follow along.

Before entering further he looked behind him. He could see many carriages big and small flying in after him. Most of the people here were unknown to him but he had gotten a report on each of the sects from Zhang Kuo.

Most of the sects weren’t a problem. Everyone that arrived on the same day as he did was comparable to the Silver Spear Sect or slightly weaker. He didn’t have to worry about those. The ones that were arriving on the second day were the problem. Zhang Kuo even mentioned a couple that stood out from the crowd.

‘Hm, strange… thought they would at least bring over a Late Stage cultivator…’

This was why he was surprised after scanning the exclusive looking carriage from one of those so-called powerful sects. For some reason, they only sent a middle stage elder that would probably be looked down on by the late stage cultivators that filled the sect leader ranks.

‘Oh well, not really my problem.’

Zhang Dong finally turned around and entered the banquet grounds, his people slowly following behind him.

Chapter 230

“Zhang Dong from the United Element Sect!”

Zhang Dong walked through a large door while one of the servants announced his name. There were some people already on the inside and they started whispering around. He had really gained a lot of infamy for this party and he could see it in the other's eyes.

‘Just need to frown and look like the biggest asshole in the room, then they will leave me alone…’

He moved forward while trying to emulate some of the haughty young masters that he had come across in his life. He was clearly giving the ‘Do not approach’ signals and hoped that people would just ignore him.

This so-called banquet would last for a couple of days as they had some events prepared. While the junior members would try to win some prizes they as the nascent soul elders would just watch.

This was also why he didn’t bring his disciples here. With them not in the race they wouldn’t be able to beat up any young masters. Thus he wouldn’t need to interfere when their uncle or grandfather got involved.

The inside of the palace was covered in gold and other precious metals that were high in spiritual energy.

The inside of the banquet hall looked quite nice. It had tables spaced out covered in costly velvet-like materials that also radiated Qi energy from them. They were obviously made from some special silk. This table cloth was probably worth more than someone’s life down in the lower regions.

There were several large crystal chandeliers up on the ceiling lighting up this large hall. Everything here looked like a mix of eastern and western noble decor. With your usual flying golden dragons and phoenix patterns everywhere.

There was also a second level to this banquet area, on the upper level were probably the spots for the sects that arrived a day later. He would be designated to a spot on the bottom floor or at least that is what he had thought. While he was looking for the table he would be occupying with his group of elderly people another servant walked up to them.

“Ah if it isn’t grandmaster Dong, your seats have been moved, please follow me!”

Zhang Dong looked at the man then performed a side glance over to his group. They were also surprised just as much as him. Feng Maling moved forward and was the one to call out to the servant with a question.

“Why have our seats been moved, could you explain yourself?”

She raised her eyebrow and looked at the serving-man with doubt in her eyes. When last-minute changes were happening it mostly didn’t bode well for the recipient.

“You don’t have to worry, honorable seniors, the city elders have decided to move you to a VIP spot after your magnificent performance in the arena!”

The man was quick to respond as he knew what the old lady was getting at. Instead of bad news, it turned out to be good, they would even get to sit next to the more prominent sects.

“Is that so? That’s marvelous, we should move then don’t you think, Patriarch?”

The granny smiled as she knew that this was an honor for a smaller sect like theirs. It showed that the people in this city were keeping an eye out for them and they were showing their respect.

Zhang Dong on the other hand narrowed his eyes while looking at the servant. This caused the man to flinch and sweat in fear. He knew that this senior here had a short fuse and if he got slaughtered by him the city elders would probably not do much about that.

‘God damn it…’

Zhang Dong cursed in his mind, he wanted to be avoided and just sit in the corner while the old farts discussed some cultivation philosophies. He couldn’t refuse the better seats as it would be rude but this would just place him in the spot where the stronger sects were. A spot where more troubles could arise.

“Yes, we should go…”

Zhang Dong nodded while the person that came to get them turned around. He quickly showed them the way while some of the other sect masters looked on with envy. They didn’t say much but everyone could tell that they were quite salty. Going up to the higher level meant that you were being accepted into the more prestigious sects. At least from the standpoint of the people that were hosting this event.

After walking some they were led to a larger booth. It looked like one of those that you would see in a theater and was sticking out slightly. There were various other ones like this all around the top floor and the sect members had ample space to sit in.

The servant was quick to do his bow and walk away. Zhang Dong sat down in the front seat of honor and was now overlooking the rest of the banquet hall. His sect was the first one to get their second level seating so he could examine all of the other cultivators coming in.

There was not much to do so he took his time to count the seating arrangement. On the floor he was on there were nine other booths. This probably meant that there were no more than nine other sects that were on a higher level. He knew that the three that surrounded his land should be in that category.

‘I’m probably occupying Dark Palm’s old booth or something as they were considered quite strong, wonder what the six others will be…’

He knew a couple of names but he was mostly focused on the three closest problems that were draining him from spirit stones. He still wanted to keep appearances up for the time being but now he was getting edged into the privileged section. If the other sects decided to test him again, he might have to make a move. He hoped that his little show of power would make them think twice.

The level below them was really big while the one he and his people were sitting at was closer to the walls. He could see people walking in and getting seated. He had only twenty people with himself but some of the sects brought over a hundred.

Luckily the people had a similar thought to him at the time when he was getting married. Only people of the senior generation would be attempting the main banquet hall. The youngsters and less privileged would remain outside in a different location.

Some of the sects had more elder members than even he had brought along. Twenty wasn’t really a high body count in this world where cities that had ten million people living in it were considered small or medium sized.

From the number of large tables and from how far they were separated from each other Zhang Dong knew how many factions would be here.

‘Ten up here and about forty down there, which puts it all up to fifty sects?’

Zhang Dong tried recalling the map of the empire he was in. It was divided by the large sects into something that looked like states. They were governed by each sect separately and had different laws depending on them.

The lands that these powerful cultivators owned varied by size. How big the portion of the land was didn’t really matter, what mattered were the resources in them. These resources could be anything ranging from spirit stones to even spirit beasts that you could kill and use as crafting materials.

The sects here were involved in a perpetual rat race. Everyone here was trying to one-up each other and somehow strengthen themselves. Their goal was a spot with the big three. Even if multiple of these smaller sects united and attacked one of the large powers they would probably lose out.

It wasn’t a matter of cultivation or manpower. The two large sects and the large clan were just too entrenched in their positions. The number of defensive formations and structures was too staggering. What would await anyone that invades would be certain death from cannon fire or other various high level treasures.

Maybe if all fifty of these sects united under one banner they would stand a chance. Still, the sheer amount of dead bodies that would be produced in a war like that would be staggering. The other problem would be that the other empires would see this as a chance to invade. Making such a solution very improbable even less considering that most of these cultivators didn’t like each other.

Slowly the cultivators in various robes were making their way inside. They were of different skin colors and various physiques. There were even female only sects that made some of the men here crane their necks towards them.

After a while he could finally see some of the top booths getting occupied by some people. He even noticed some familiar figures there, namely the people from the three sects that were surrounding his own.

The people from the Demon Subduing Sect were first to arrive, followed by the Dragon Gate Sect and finally the Limitless Sword Society. The third one that was the most antagonistic towards his own faction was considered to be slightly stronger than the rest. Mostly due to their fanatic sword arts and overzealous ways of training.

Most of the people there had that young lord mentality. They would go out of their way to duel other people and thus they earned a lot of battle experience along the way.

Soon after all the other sects showed up one, in particular, was an eyebrow-raiser. It was an elder that he noticed before, the one that was only in the middle stage of the nascent soul. It was kind of strange for someone like that to occupy the main position as almost everyone was a late stage cultivator.

That was the usual power level of an active sect leader. An old leader would only retire and move into the reserve elder side after someone at the late stage showed up to change them out. The only reason Zhang Dong could think of the man being here would be that the real sect leader was busy somewhere. There also could have been some accidents which made this situation suspicious.

‘Well, not like it’s any of my business…’

He thought to himself while looking at some people that were with him. All of the other people weren’t noteworthy, no other nascent cultivators were with him. Most of them seemed even weaker than the baked potato grandma that he brought along. There was also a peculiar-looking young girl with them, she had blue eyes and long blond hair. She looked more like a western girl than an eastern one and her complexion wasn’t as pale either.

He didn’t have much to do at the moment so he continued glancing in their direction. He even took some time to look at their statuses with his system.

‘Divine Fist Sect? Wasn’t that supposed to be one of the strongest ones around? Why is this guy their Patriarch?’

After some snooping, the system’s window appeared over the old man. His system’s identification skill had somehow advanced further, so he could even see faction names or the positions the people had in factions if he wanted to. The system was showing that the old man there was the current Divine Fist Sect’s acting Patriarch and not just some side elder.

He could think of a couple of reasons why this fact was true. The main one made him recall the old Zhang Clan. Before he came into this world it had lost its leaders as well in a botched expedition. Could this sect have suffered a similar fate?

While he was contemplating some possibilities the light dimmed in the large hall and some music began to play. A certain dandy looking man that he was familiar with walked out.

“Let me thank all of you gentlemen for arriving this day for the annual banquet.”

Apparently it was finally starting, he moved his head down while ignoring the issue with the unknown sect. He had other things to worry about now and they mostly consisted of not standing out.

Chapter 231

Zhang Dong had a small glass of bubbly liquor in his hand. He slowly moved it towards his lips and took a sip while glancing down. What he saw beneath were a group of beauties on their zithers playing a slow song while singing.

He was sitting in one of the booths with a group of twenty elders. Below them, a large group of people was seated around a stage area. The stage was well lit up, it kind of looked like a dancing stage with the floor shined to perfection.

There were some gems embedded in it that were shining bright. If you looked closer from his angel he could even look under the skirts of those lovely ladies that were down on that stage. He was lucky that his wife wasn’t here with him.

He had been sitting here for over an hour already. First Sebas Tian walked out and did a small boring speech. He talked generally to everyone in the room without mentioning anyone in particular.

The Silver Spear Sect was here but their Patriarch was missing which did cause a little scene. The people that had come had their heads lowered and they would flinch whenever he looked at them. He wanted to just wave or throw a kissy face at them if he could, alas he needed to keep his senior attitude up.

He wished that he could be more relaxed around others, the only one he could show his true colors were his closest family. His wife already knew that he wasn’t the super-serious cultivator that she once thought he was. Neither his grandfather or some of his retainers. The only ones that couldn’t see it were his disciples, they were too far gone and would probably never see him more than a master to worship.

Zhang Dong took another sip from his glass and emptied it. He glanced at his own people that looked quite interested in the music. Their eyes were closed and they were taking in the slow tunes. He did notice that the tunes were strengthened by spiritual energy which meant that the women had some kind of Dao of sound. Probably a lesser one that was instrument specific.

After about another fifteen minutes the dancing and singing fairies finally were finished. Some of the younger cultivators clapped, the younger men were clearly enthralled by the women's beauty.

He knew that this wasn’t just a relaxing concert. This was actually a scheme that the people from this city had cooked up. Having powerful cultivators interacting with their beauties could give various benefits to the rich merchants here.

This whole banquet was a place to gain new connections, be it in business or in the family. Zhang Dong theorized that the young beauties were probably wife candidates. in all likelihood behind closed doors, the older members of their families were already debating on which young master to wed them too.

This was one of the more distasteful traditions in this world. He would rather have the men and women be free to choose their husbands or wives. It was very rare that something like that happened. If there was nothing gained from the marriage the parents would not agree to it.

Zhang Dong was lucky enough to marry Feng Liena who was on equal footing with him. If he chose some lowly Qi condensation commoner the elders from his sect would start complaining. At most, they would allow someone like that to be a concubine but not the main wife. Though he was in a high enough position in the sect to do what he wanted, this wasn’t the case with most of the people in this world.

“Fellow Daoists, I hope you enjoyed the melody our young maidens have played for you this day.”

Senior Tian walked out after the musical number was done. He even urged the young lords to give some gifts to the fairy-like beauties that performed them. They would apparently be leaving this hall to go outside and mingle. While the concert was taking place a feast had been given to them so there wasn’t much left to do here.

“Follow me fellow Daoists, our Yinglong Pavilion leader will also be joining soon for the festivities.”

The whole hall started rumbling a bit and a large gate rose up from the ground. The other sect members gasped at the display as this was a teleportation gate. Zhang Dong on the other hand rubbed his chin and squinted.

‘Hm, looks inferior to the one that we have.’

After examining the contraption he was glad that his sect was already ahead of the competition. Even this large Yinglong Pavilion wasn’t as advanced in some ways as his sect. The manuals he had received after that one expedition had turned out to be the most important treasure trove.

The secret ground they were in was in another sect's territory though. He wanted to visit it as it probably would answer some of his questions. He would probably need to put his younger sect members in danger though as it would certainly test them again. But maybe he could somehow enter the closed-door another way. He was able to enter the strange room with the cube without a problem and he felt like it was connected to that secret ground.

The problem was that if he wanted to go there he would probably have to declare war against the sect residing there. He was on the fence about that. He could also try sneaking in but then he would also need to get rid of anyone defending it. There were too many factors that could lead to a war and if he got sucked into that gate his sect might have to face the wrath of the other three sects without him.

The teleportation gate had a similar design to all the other ones he saw before. Some people were already going through it. Zhang Dong and the people that he came with moved from their balcony seats as well.

Everyone slowly moved towards that gate, the people on the lower floor were first, and only after that Zhang Dong and his sect members followed suit.

Everything here was preplanned and every sect was judged and ranked accordingly. His United Element Sect had suddenly joined the upper echelons. At least from the point of view of the Yinglong Pavilion that had placed them on the upper floor. This caused the ones that were left on the lower floors to not be amused.

The only thing that was holding them back from complaining was the fact that Zhang Dong had trashed the sect leader from the Silver Spear Sect in a one on one battle. He had also done it very one-sidedly which caused everyone to be frightened of his might.

The lower placed sects weren’t the only ones raising their brows at this. The other nine sects that were up there with them had kept looking at him and his oldies throughout the whole concert. They were mostly curious as to why the Yinglong Pavilion would place them there. Some of them weren’t amused, it were the sects that were taking spirit stones from him.

Finally, he and his people went through the gate as the first group from the second floor. Only people that were of core formation and above were allowed to walk through it, which left the juniors outside to mingle or prepare for the coming competition.

The teleportation gate brought them to a wholly new place. The moment they appeared there he could feel some wind against his face.

They were quite high up as the air was thin but thanks to his high cultivation that wasn’t really a problem. The puffy white clouds were also hovering above them in the sky really closely.

Apparently, they were on a high mountain peak somewhere in the Yinglong Pavilion’s territory. This was not a pocket dimension or any kind of treasure but the mountain they were on was quite hefty.

As he walked forward he could see people there already talking. There were many tables with various foods and the smell of something cooking filled his nostrils.

‘I guess that was just an appetizer that we were having?’

He walked forward while glancing at the strange-looking fruits and dishes. They were different from what his clan members ate. The cuisine was quite varied and he could feel a high concentration of spiritual energy coming from them. If a person at the Qi condensation level tried eating some of these dishes they might even breakthrough. They also might explode if the Qi concentration was too high.

“Good to see you ol’ chap.”

Sebas Tian was there to greet him, the man certainly liked him for some reason or another.

“Yes, good to see you too.”

Zhang Dong replied while walking forward, some of the oldies from his clan appeared behind him a bit disoriented. They soon realized where they were and continued forward. They were quick to pick up on what this was and started mingling with the crowds. They were instructed beforehand to interact with others to gain information and favor.

He was left with the monocle-wearing man that was apparently done with his job now. Someone else would be taking over and it was apparently the leader of this group of merchants.

He finally appeared after everyone had gone through the teleportation gate. The man had a sharp glint in his eyes. He did look like someone in his 60s like most of the nascent soul cultivators. His hair wasn’t gray though, it was a deep crimson. His beard was in the same color and had an angular cut to it. He was quite short and robust looking which made Zhang Dong think about a certain fantasy race.

“Welcome comrades, I hope we can do business as always!“

The man was sitting in a large throne looking chair overlooking the other people that came. He was under something similar to a giant gazebo. It was made from gold and various precious metals were embedded into the beams.

“Take your time and enjoy the banquet to your heart's content, your juniors will be soon starting with their competition.”

The man said while the people glanced to the side. Zhang Dong followed with his gaze to where they were looking. This mountain was high up and the peak was flattened so that they could stay there. But behind it was something peculiar.

There was a giant labyrinth with walls that were hundreds of meters tall. It was multiple kilometers in diameter and looked truly tremendous from up here.

Zhang Dong spread his spiritual sense into that labyrinth and could feel that there were various living beings there. Not only humans, there were also various beasts and even automatons like the wooden dolls his sect used for some trials.

This would be the proving ground for the junior members below the core formation level. They would compete against other sects and fight the beasts inside. There were various traps and other hard tests waiting for them there.

While glancing at the giant labyrinth Zhang Dong gave out a sigh. He had already witnessed similar proving grounds. He already knew that the young kids in there would probably end up killing each other. The fights for prestige and resources were truly brutal in this world. Luckily his disciples were not here and wouldn’t even be able to participate due to their cultivation level.

If he brought some of the better foundation establishment youths there would probably be a scandal. He’d expect them to just trash the competition at this point. He didn’t want to brag but some of his elite members were just too far ahead of most people in this world. Maybe the kids here were young masters from strong sects but he didn’t think they would match his own top juniors.

He looked at the large labyrinth from all the way up here. A nascent soul cultivator would be able to see everything that was happening there without the need for a camera. This was all thanks to their enhanced spiritual sense.

The junior members were already walking but there looked to be one golden-haired girl getting pushed in by force. It was a peculiar sight to see.

“What is the meaning of this?”

He looked to the side, there was a small group of nascent cultivators arguing and the one shouting was the man that was at the middle stage that he saw before.

His face was contorted and he didn’t look pleased at all. Apparently, something was about to happen but luckily his sect wasn’t the one in trouble this time around.

Chapter 232

The banquet had moved into the next phase. Every influential member from the large sects that ruled these lands was here. They had teleported onto a large mountain peak. This peak was overlooking a giant labyrinth and some people were already moving into it.

The labyrinth was the main competition that the junior members were able to participate in. The Yinglong Pavilion had hidden various treasures in this area and everything inside was up for the taking. Various high quality pills, weapons, and even cultivation manuals that could raise weak sects into behemoths.

These were all treasures that you could gain in this competition. The winner would even get a large monetary reward that consisted of high tier spirit stones. This was a big opportunity and honor for the junior’s that were here. They were all foundation establishment cultivators and even one high tier spirit stone would allow them to live like kings.

They were all motivated greatly and wanted to win this competition at all costs. The treasures wouldn’t just be handed over to them though. There were various traps and spirit beasts littered in the many tunnels. The contestants needed to watch their every step as one wrong turn could mean certain death.

Even with all the dangers that the Yinglong Pavilion had prepared in the competitions, this wasn’t the thing that the participants were afraid of. The things that they would have to fear the most were each other. Most of the deaths and injuries in this type of competition were delivered by the contestants. Battles for the artifacts broke out constantly and there were no rules against it.

Killing and crippling each other was allowed. The nascent soul cultivators above the labyrinth could look over their juniors but they weren’t supposed to interfere. They weren't but they could, there was a certain rule that allowed the guardians to protect their junior members. They would need to either convince the other party’s senior to order their juniors to spare theirs. They could do it forcefully but that had some ramifications later. Sometimes even death battles between the nascent soul masters occurred due to this.

Something like this was rare, one of the sides relented most of the time. No nascent soul Patriarch would give their life to defend a foundation establishment junior. So in general both sides ended up bluffing against each other until one side gave up. Only if both sides were bent on fighting each other a battle to the death would take place.

Something like this was starting, on the large peak, the Patriarch of the Divine Fist Sect was staring daggers at another nascent soul elder. He had noticed that a certain golden-haired junior had been forcefully taken inside the labyrinth grounds. He could see her moving through the corridors with a sword in hand.

“What is the meaning of this, I didn’t sanction something like this!?”

The man gritted his teeth while looking down, it was clear that he wanted to just fly down there and pluck his sect junior from that labyrinth.

“Fang Heng, what do you mean? Your niece wanted to participate in the competition to bring honor to your sect, my sect juniors just lent her a helping hand.”

Another man replied. This person had a peculiar look. His hair was green as jade grass and his large beard looked like thick roots. His skin color was dark and looked like fresh soil that you would use for planting or gardening.

Zhang Dong was at the side and listened with one ear while glancing down at the labyrinth. He noticed who the man was looking at, it was a pretty young lass with blonde hair. It looked like she was being chased by people that had similar robes to this plant looking elder. From what he could tell this sect was called the Yggdrasil Sect.

He was familiar with this name. This sect was also part of the top ten and as the name implied there were cultivators versed in plants. They were wealthy due to producing superior grade pills and spiritual herbs. There were one of the biggest providers of herbs and plants in the empire. It had something to do with how they cultivated, their bodies were similar to plants after they went through some kind of body refining technique.

From his point of view, this tree hugger sect was clearly picking a fight with the other one. Why he didn’t know but it might have something to do with the man’s low cultivation. He could see the arguing elder backing off, the plant looking cultivator had activated some of his aura. He was at the late stage and was clearly more powerful.

Zhang Dong started moving back, this had nothing to do with him and the woman below wasn’t in danger quite yet. He thought to himself that he couldn’t risk getting involved in something like this.

While inching away from the commotion, some of the other cultivators moved closer. They seemed to be in cahoots with the Yggdrasil Sect as they started laughing at the old man from the Divine Fist Sect. This looked very suspicious to him; it was as if they had set this whole thing up. He even saw his old friend from the Limitless Sword Society joining in on the chuckling.

‘Do they want to coax that Divine Fist elder to fight to save his junior or something? But judging by his level he would surely die.’

He glanced over to the labyrinth, the woman was constantly getting chased by the other juniors. They had smiles on their faces as if this was a fun activity. He could even see some other sects joining in the chase, this was probably no coincidence. This looked more and more like something planned.

“You might not know this ol’ chap…”

While Zhang Dong was watching Sebas Tian from the Yinglong Pavilion joined him. For some reason he had come to give him the info about this, probably to gain favor.

“The Divine Fist Sect had tried hiding it but the news had spread, they should have not come here…”

The man was sure to use a special technique to whisper the info right into Zhang Dong’s ear. Apparently, this sect was one of the stronger ones, they were bordering with those tree huggers.

There had been some kind of newly evolved beast that moved in on their land. It was a beast king that could control various demonic beasts. There was a large scale battle between the sect and a monster horde.

There was no detailed info yet but it was clear that the Divine Fist Sect had suffered. The appearance of this man instead of the real sect leader was a giveaway. He was either dead or injured.

“So, are they testing him?”

Senior Tian nodded. The information wasn’t complete so the sect leader of the Yggdrasil Sect probably decided to prod his opposition. If the Divine Fist Sect was truly just an injured animal he would put it out of its misery.

The beast tide was for now just a rumor. The strange appearance of a middle stage nascent soul elder instead of the old Patriarch was really suspicious. Even if he was alive this sect that was already on bad terms with them wouldn’t care. They wouldn’t lose much and they were just targeting a little junior member.

Even if they were wrong and the others came to their doorstep asking for face they could just pay them off with some spirit stones. On the other hand, if they didn’t show up with their sect leader, this would mean that they couldn’t retaliate. It was a low-risk gamble, the junior in question was just a relative of this middle stage elder. No sects would start wars over something like that at most they would need to give up the juniors that did the deed.

“Unfortunately, if the rumors are true then their sect might be done for…”

Zhang Dong looked down at the labyrinth and to the young girl that was fleeing for her life. Then he looked back to the man from her sect. Fang Heng was his name, he was holding onto his own neck while two nascent soul elders were focusing their aura on him.

They were clearly sending him a message. They probably weren’t afraid of facing him in a deathmatch either. There was no winning in this situation if the man tried to act.

Maybe he wouldn’t have to, nothing was written in stone. If the girl managed to survive through the labyrinth then it would be fine. There was a time limit on this thing and it would at most take two days. Even though the area this was constructed was immense, the juniors were already superhuman. They could get through this in two days, it was a closed-off space so there weren’t that many places to go either.

Time passed and the spectacle continued. The golden-haired girl was now running away from her pursuers and she was holding out quite well. She was in the late stage of foundation establishment and was clearly gifted. The problem was that there were far too many people going after her.

Zhang Dong kept glancing between her and the elder from the Divine Fist Sect. He looked defeated and unable to act. He didn’t feel good about himself either, he had to watch this obvious bullying from afar.

The other sect elders that were there averted their gazes. They clearly didn’t want to have anything to do with this. Rightfully so, at least from this world’s standpoint. There was nothing to gain from a rumored broken down sect.

This didn’t sit too well with him. He remembered the old times, his clan was also forced along with him to go to that secret ground. They were brought there as cannon fodder on the whims of a powerful sect. If the rumors were true the fate of these two was sealed, the girl would probably die in the labyrinth and this elder might end in a similar fashion.

He didn’t think the powerful sects would let a nascent soul master just waltz out of here in one piece. After he was away from the Rain Dragon City they would probably strike instantly. The only thing that could save them would be if their sect wasn’t that damaged or if they had some kind of backup from a different one.

Zhang Dong shook his head as his mind drifted in a certain direction. He quickly tried to remove that thought from his mind. Being the person that he was, he was having trouble just sitting there and not helping. These people were just strangers to him, he didn’t really have a reason to lend them a hand.

He was now a sect leader and had to think about his own people. He was also a father with a child and with another that was yet to be born. He couldn’t be alienating other sects in his position, not unless his or his family's lives were at stake.

Though the more this charade continued the worse it became. The girl tried her best but there were just too many people after her. With the added traps and beasts in there, she stood no chance. She was now cornered and battered, no way of getting out of it.

Zhang Dong looked to the old man that was more or less out of commission. The other two sect leaders were keeping him quiet with their superior pressure and he was unable to even speak to challenge them. Even if he did, it would probably be a one-sided beat down.

He looked back to the girl, his emotionless face twitching as he had a hard time taking this sight in. The other people here were doing nothing. His own daughter's face started superimposing itself over the blond-haired girl’s face and he started getting angry.

He did want to help but there was no good reason. How would he explain an outburst, he and the sect weren’t related. Could he just say that he was hired by their leader as a guard? That could make some sense but why would he risk his life for a measly foundation establishment junior.

His system identified her name Fang Meili, she was clearly related to the old man here. He could even see the old man’s eyes watering as he had to witness one of his family members getting attacked.

While watching the girl fighting for her life against six people he brought up his system window. Sometimes this thing worked in mysterious ways, maybe he could help her remotely by boosting her cultivation level or something. The problem was that he needed her to be part of his sect to do that, or maybe a disciple.

While going through the windows he noticed something strange. He did a double-take and his eyes went wide.

‘No… how could this be possible… how far does his influence reach?’

He was now looking at something peculiar, this would probably give him a good excuse to act. The logistics of this circumstance were mind-boggling though but maybe it would all work out in the end.

Chapter 233

Fang Meili had come with her grandfather to this gathering of the sects. She had come unwilling and would have rather remained in the sect. Her brothers and sisters were now in dire need and it felt like she was running away.

She couldn’t refuse her grandfather though, she was the youngest female family member that had survived the beast onslaught. She was also the favorite granddaughter of Fang Heng, one of the more prominent nascent soul elders of the sect. She knew what her grandfather was planning to do but it felt wrong to just run away and live quietly here.

She as a junior member wasn’t allowed to follow her grandfather into the teleportation gate. She was left with some of her sect members outside and they were to wait till the competition was over.

Then it happened, a group of cultivators from the Limitless Sword Society and the Yggdrasil Sect appeared. They made quick work of the senior members from her faction and then forced her to enter the competition.

She was subdued by one of the powerful elders and couldn’t move a muscle. The other people didn’t seem to notice or just didn’t care. She was thrown into the labyrinth and then her nightmare began.

She started running for her life, the people from those two sects had put a bounty on her head. She could clearly hear them mention it, the ones that either killed or crippled her would be given a reward. The junior members from those sects were a greedy bunch. They wouldn't mind slaying a child to gain some favor with their elders.

She fled and fought, she even managed to take out a couple of her pursuers that were stupid enough to get close while being weaker than her. There were just too many of them though and after many hours of running and hiding, she was now against a wall.

She was now grasping her belly, a blade had pierced through it and she was losing blood. Her body was more resistant than a regular humans was but the continued blood loss was getting to her.

She was now looking at a group of people. They varied by age and looks, some were male some were female but each one of them was grinning. They were clearly enjoying this process of chasing her down, they were just treating this as a game.

“I think senior brother should do the honors~”

A girl that looked to be in her early twenties called out from the side. She was hugging another cultivator’s arm closely while smiling.

This was the strongest young master from the group, his cultivation level was in the great circle of foundation establishment. His skin was slightly green and he was clearly someone from the Yggdrasil side. There were some other youngsters here but they knew that this sect was the strongest, they couldn't complain.

“Yes, I think this hunt belongs to the senior brother.”

Other people just nodded while cursing inwardly. They all wanted the promised rewards but could not go against this senior.

Fang Meili just spit down at the ground while glaring at the group of cowards. It was one thing to fight to the death one on one but another to just be hunted down like an animal.

“You’ll never get away with this, you scum!”

She cursed at them while they laughed at her, the senior brother from the tree hugger sect took out a spear. He pointed it at her, it shone brightly and she could feel spiritual energy gathering on the tip.

Fang Meili was far too tired to do anything about it. She had long since burned through her spiritual reserves and was just running on fumes. She would not be able to take an attack even from someone at the early stage.

She knew that this was the end, her grandfather would have probably done something if he could by now. There was no help coming.

She removed her hand from her wound and grasped her weapon. It was a Ji, more popularly known as a type of halberd. It was a large weapon and she could barely hold it now, even with both her hands now.

“Let me end this farce!”

The young man said while scoffing. He could see that the woman here was unwilling to give up, he would need to deliver the finishing blow himself. He bolted forward with his spear, it would only take a little poke with it and the young girl would probably be dead. He could clearly see that the girl was holding herself up by leaning against the wall behind her. She had no strength to swing that weapon.

“Repent your sins in your next life!”

He delivered a thrusting attack forward, his spear started shining and the tip looked like it was spinning around. His hands extended in length and the green glowing spear tip headed for Fang Meili’s head.

The young girl kept her eyes open. This was the most she could do, she really couldn’t move a muscle. Her wound opened itself back up, her past experiences filled her head. It was over, she would die but at least she would look in the eyes of her murderer. Maybe if she was lucky enough to get reborn she could get her revenge.

However, before the spear could reach her head something astonishing happened. She could hear a strong voice fill the whole labyrinth. It sounded gallant and resolute, the moment the people around it heard it they felt weak in their knees.

“That’s enough!”

The young master couldn’t stop his attack anymore, it was flying right towards the girl’s head but this wouldn’t be the end of her. Following the booming voice, something collided with the labyrinth’s array wall.

Just like any good trial ground this one also had a protective barrier around it. It was in place to block out people from interfering and also to block the contestants from fleeing outside. Once you were inside you were trapped and on your own.

The array was attacked from the outside and everyone looked to the sky. They could see some kind of golden light pushing up against the transparent shield. The shield didn’t hold up at all and a golden ray of light invaded the labyrinth. Everyone could feel that the power of this attack was something immense.

This golden light made its way inside of the labyrinth in a certain direction. It traveled at a tremendous speed that these juniors couldn’t follow and finally landed. It connected with the golden-haired girl, the spear was just a second away from blowing her head apart.

The golden light surrounded her body and when the spear hit it, the weapon shattered into a million tiny pieces. The youth that was holding on to the weapon was repelled and flew backward. His body embedded itself into the opposite wall nicely while his sect member went slack-jawed.

Fang Meili found herself floating now, the golden light felt warm and calming. It infused her body with new power and she felt that her wounds were getting closed. In a matter of seconds, the holy healing energies managed to heal her battered body.

This wasn’t the end quite yet. The light didn’t leave, it made her float upwards and into the air as if she was getting sucked into the sky. The other people that were in the trial saw a girl with gold hair flying upwards while flailing her hands around. It looked as if gravity was turned off for her and she was tossed into space.

She flew towards the rift in the protective array that was broken and squeezed right through it before it could mend itself. Soon she was nothing more than a glowing spec in the sky while heading towards the mountain peak where the elders were.

The juniors from the sects that were after this girl were stupefied. Who would be so brazen to go against their elders? Was the Yinglong Pavilion themselves making a move or was there another strong sect that didn’t fear the consequences of a move like this?

Everyone knew that such an act would bring the wrath of both the Yggdrasil Sect and the Limitless Sword Society. The only thing that was remotely plausible was if the Divine Fist Sect had somehow falsified the beast tide incident. The two sects that were going after the Divine Fist Sect had spies that informed them about this. If it came out that they were somehow wrong they could be in for a war that they couldn’t afford.

Fang Meili floated up into the sky, she was moments away from getting pierced by a ferocious spear technique a second ago. Now she was gently flying, the golden aura keeping her warm and protected from the cold weather and winds.

Soon she was able to see the person that helped her. When she reached the top she saw him, a handsome white haired man was standing there. His long hair was fluttering around and he was glowing in the same golden aura that she was. His eyes were crackling with energy and once in a while, she could hear the clap of thunder.

She was brought down right in front of this tall man. The moment he removed the golden shield that surrounded her she dropped down to her knees. She was far too flabbergasted by this whole turn of events that she couldn’t utter a word.

The man that saved her was someone that she didn’t know. Meili recognized him as a Patriarch from another sect, she had briefly seen him sitting in a booth during the pre-banquet pleasantries. Why he was helping she didn’t know, the only reason she could think of was her grandfather.

Her grandfather on the other hand was confused just as the girl was. He had been held back by two other nascent soul masters and couldn’t move a muscle. But then Zhang Dong shouted out and saved his granddaughter. Before he could ask about it the Patriarch from the Yggdrasil Sect spoke up, his tone unamused.

“What is the meaning of this? Who are you to interfere? You better have a good reason for this, otherwise…”

“Otherwise… what?”

Before the man that looked like a sentient tree could threaten Zhang Dong further the man’s aura exploded. The people there were standing closest to him had to even back away. His golden aura began glowing stronger and small lightning bolts in the same color started to appear and crackle.

“A good reason? I have one! Why wouldn’t I aid someone from my own family?”

Fang Meili and her grandfather had floating question marks above their heads. Why was this man claiming that she was someone from his family, was he just lying to save her?

“You jest, you clearly just interfered for no reason!”

The Patriarch from the Yggdrasil Sect wasn’t having none of this, his aura exploded and clashed against Zhang Dong’s but to his surprise, he couldn’t overpower the golden sheen. Zhan Jie from the Limitless Sword Society saw this and aided his ally in the clash, it was now two against one.

The Yinglong Pavilion leader remained sitting there without moving a muscle. He was just waiting for this to play out. The other people in the area started backing away as this looked to be heading in the wrong direction.

“Hoh? You don’t trust my words? Would you believe me if we did a simple bloodline assessment, don’t think you would complain then! I bet the fellow Daoists from the Yinglong Pavilion can perform such a trifling task!”

Zhang Dong proclaimed while inserting more power into his own aura attack. The two men that were going against him were quite shocked that he was able to last against their combined assault.

There was a plan behind this whole scene. Zhang Dong had checked Fang Meili’s status quite thoroughly and he had discovered something interesting. She was indeed related to him, he was her uncle. This of course was only possible thanks to one man, the one man harem Zhang Jin. His grandfather had apparently sired someone from her line and it was someone from his earlier conquests.

He wasn’t sure about the logistics of it all. He could have left her with a baby in her belly and then run, the woman then had the child back at her sect and this child was Fang Meili’s grandparent. Now the only thing left was to prove this and maybe he could evade a fight, if not this might be a lot more troublesome.

Chapter 234

Zhang Dong was just standing there, glaring at two nascent soul masters that were angry. He had come up with a haphazard plan just like many times before. He couldn’t just watch a child getting murdered in front of him. He would hate himself in the future if he just stood by, the problem was that now he had involved himself in this fiasco. He would have to see it through till the end.

He eyed the golden-haired girl with a side glance. She looked rather young and was looking at him as if he was some kind of alien. It would have been good if she followed his lead and acted like his family member in this situation. She didn’t look like the scheming type though and probably didn’t realize that he was trying to help her. That or she didn’t trust him enough to go along with it.

Her grandfather on the other hand had been freed from the massive pressure as Zhang Dong had aided him with his own aura. He was also now looking in his direction with brows furrowed. He looked confused but luckily he had more sense than his granddaughter and went for it.

“Y-yes…, you should pay respect to your senior uncle!”

Fang Heng was now grasping at straws. He had no idea what this man called Zhang Dong was thinking. He had heard about his fight but knew nothing more than that. By the way, he was holding back the Yggdrasil Sect’s Patriarch and his ally at bay it looked like he was a strong master.

He was claiming to be a family member of theirs from his granddaughter's side. If this was true or some kind of ploy he had no idea. At this juncture, he was willing to gamble his life. His favorite grandchild had almost died and he couldn’t even lift a finger. It was this man that had saved her, maybe he was just interested in her for a different reason but he had to risk it. Otherwise, she would be dead for sure, he had to somehow help him.

Fang Meili looked at the handsome white-haired man that was looking to the side. He was currently in a spiritual battle with the two other Patriarchs. He still managed to look to the side and smile slightly.

Before the girl could act though she felt some of that nascent soul energy leaking out. Her whole body trembled from fright and she fell down to her knees while panting. She felt as if someone was holding her throat tightly and squeezing with all might.

“This is absurd! Why should we even let you go on with this farce, you’ve broken the rules!”

“That man never showed any respect for others, he needs to be taught a lesson!”

Zhan Jie from the Limitless Sword Society stepped forward. While his ally backed him up, it didn’t look like this would be ending without a fight.

Zhang Dong could feel the pressure increasing against him and he was having trouble defending himself and the young girl from all this pressure. He was still only at the early parts of his middle stage level so going against these two that were close to the very top of late-stage was proving difficult.

That is if he didn’t use one of his techniques. His Embodiment of the Thunder God technique had been upgraded and he could now use it even better. He took one step forward and a golden hue surrounded his body.

The other cultivators in the area could feel powerful fluctuations of Qi in the surroundings. Zhang Dong’s lightning elemental Qi was of the utmost purity and everyone here could sense that.

The two people that were going against him felt their auras getting shoved back as their opponent walked forward. His energy had the telltale signs of someone at the middle stage but his power was even above theirs.

“Respect has to be earned! You forced my niece to take part in the competition, do you really think I didn’t see that? She was never included in the roster, do you think I wouldn’t notice?”

He had seen some people pushing the blond girl around and forcing her into the labyrinth. During that time he had luckily eavesdropped on them with one of his techniques. He noticed them talk it out with the judges standing guard, they were clearly bribed.

There was a rule in place to register the contestants a day before the competition. The sects that came first could even do it two days sooner. Zhang Dong knew that the people from the Divine Fist Sect did no such thing. They were clearly forced to participate and everyone here knew it. They all kept quiet as it wasn’t their business and they had nothing to gain from alienating the Yggdrasil Sect’s Patriarch.

The two sides began glaring at each other. Fang Heng even made his way over behind Zhang Dong and grabbed his granddaughter. The girl was clearly not powerful enough to take part in this and was barely conscious at this time. She was lucky enough that Zhang Dong had protected her from most of the aura that was seeping out.

“Stop lying, how could that girl be related to you. You are clearly just trying to slander our good names, what gall! Who do you think even allowed your sect to exist for so long? Did you finally lose it? Are you rebelling against the Limitless Sword Society!?”

Zhan Jie retorted while sweating. He could feel that this white-haired man was a lot stronger than he previously had thought. He had the other Patriarch next to him so he had some help, otherwise, he would feel as confident. He wasn’t yet out of his reach, in the sword master's mind he felt like he could win a one on one fight even though it would be a hard-fought battle.

“Rebelling?”

Zhang Dong started feeling apprehensive about this. He didn’t quite want to start a fight with this sect or the other two. It was slowly becoming apparent that he might not have another choice.

“I and my sect have never and never will belong to you, how can we rebel? Do you think that little sum that we pay you gives you the right to our lands? Fine, from this day forth the United Element sect will cut ties with the Limitless Sword Society!”

Some of the people gasped, they didn’t know what this was going but they all felt threatened. Even though this was the Yinglong Pavilion if a fight between two top fighters broke out there could be some casualties.

“Y-you…”

Zhan Jie’s face contorted and he looked like a demon. The man was clearly angered to the fullest extent. Before he could act though another powerful aura filled the area. This aura came crashing down and just evaporated the spiritual energy that these three nascent soul masters were giving out.

“That’s more than enough of you three. There will be no fighting here…”

The man that spoke out was the leader of the merchant faction. He had remained silent and watched on from the sidelines. He had no stakes in either side but he couldn’t let these people just do anything they wanted. This was his city and there were rules that he made.

“If you two wish to continue then you can clash in the arena, not here.”

Zhang Dong and the two other elders started backing off and quieted down. Both parties were actually glad that the leader from the Yinglong Pavilion intervened as none of them were actually willing to fight.

“If what the Patriarch from the United Element sect says is true then I’ll be lenient, first we must check if his claims are true.”

It was time to clear things out here. There were some accusations thrown out there but no proof anywhere. First, they needed to see if this white-haired man was related to the golden-haired girl or not. If he wasn’t then he was clearly just doing this to agitate the other side, for what reason that would be up to debate.

“Bring it out.”

The man clapped his hands and a person brought out a certain treasure. It looked like a chalice that was made from precious metals. The people here knew well what this was as it was a popular item that could test someone’s family roots.

The chalice was placed on a table. A person needed to put a drop of their blood into the item and let it mix with the other person’s blood. If the chalice showed a reaction by glowing then it meant that the people were related to each other.

There were other more intricate artifacts like this. Some sects used them to test how pure their bloodlines were. This was mostly done with a reference to an ancestral senior. They would use their genetic marker as the base and compare the disciples to it. The closer it was the higher the position in the sect or clan for the junior.

Fang Meili looked at her grandfather, the old man just nodded.

“It’s okay Meili’er.”

Not like the two had any other choice. If Zhang Dong was a liar and he was just trying to start a fight they would go down with him.

Fang Heng was already grasping at straws, his original plan had gone down the drain. It was clear that the other sects knew something as they weren’t worried that much when they took his granddaughter away. He was now sure that they were testing him. Probably the information about the state of his sect was already out there. How much was unclear.

The golden-haired girl nodded and moved forward. She was handed a dagger with which she poked her finger with. A droplet of blood landed inside the chalice and the artifact began to faintly glow.

Zhan Jie and the others were curious, was this girl really related to that man. It was really strange that he reacted as he did. A normal person wouldn’t defend someone in this kind of situation from their standpoint.

They could only think of a few reasons that would make him do something like that. Either the girl was really related to him, or he was planning something. He seemed eager to go against them, was he really so brazen and sure about himself?

Zhan Jie's natural superiority complex was clouding his judgment. He was already maddened by the fact that Zhang Dong dared to break off ties and would not be paying his sect its dues. He wanted to show him how wrong he was to go against him and his sect. He didn’t even add the other two sects into the equations as he was confident. His own sect was superior and so was he.

Zhang Dong was now up. He was handed a dagger that was a heavenly treasure, he looked at it for a moment and frowned. It looked like he was apprehensive about using it for some reason. This made the other cultivators question his motives, it made it seem like he didn’t want to go through with this test.

“See, he was lying, he doesn’t even want to proceed with the bloodline test!”

The Yggdrasil Sect’s Patriarch proclaimed while pointing with his finger accusingly. The others nodded with approval as it did look like so.

“No, it’s just… fine…”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh and poked his finger with the dagger. The others looked with anticipation and waited for the chalice to be activated. There was a slight problem though.

“I thought so…”

They looked at Zhang Dong who poked his finger with that dagger but no blood was coming out. The item was a heaven grade treasure but it looked to not be able to pierce his skin. The pointy dagger tip even got bent out of shape when Zhang Dong added more strength to it.

“Sorry about that…”

Zhang Dong handed the dagger back to the person that brought it over. It was now really out of shape and looked unusable. It was clear from this display that this man’s body was something that could resist heavenly grade treasures.

“I’ll just use my own…”

The man then brought out his sword that he once used in the fight against the Silver Spear Sect Patriarch and poked his finger on the tip. Even this item had some trouble to pierce his skin but a small droplet was formed that dropped into the chalice.

The bloodline measuring device started working and it went through a couple of colors. Depending on the shine it gave out it could show how close they were related. It went from red to orange and then to yellow and continued to change. It finally stopped at a slightly darker green which meant that the two were indeed related.

“Green color, this means that they are within three generations!”

Zhang Dong already knew this as his system had shown him this. The person that Zhang Jin had shagged with was Fang Meili’s great grandmother. She was indeed his niece and in the same generation as his two disciples.

The two sect leaders looked surprised, what was the meaning of this? This man was related to this girl, how was this possible?

The two looked at each other and their faces went pale. This was probably a rouse started by the Divine First Sect, they probably lied about the monster attack too!

Chapter 235

The people were stunned. A Patriarch from a new upstart sect was related to someone from a well established one. A previously powerful sect that was now losing power but was that really the truth?

Zhang Dong was to the side, his brows quivered a bit but he managed to keep his facial expression mostly hidden away. He knew those looks that the people were giving him, it were the looks of cultivators that were overthinking. What genius conspiracy theories they were coming up with was something that he would like to know.

He knew that people in this world didn’t think much of luck or coincidences. They thought that everyone that was at the very top of the cultivation ladder was some type of schemer. It was more believable for them that the Divine Fist Sect and the United Element Sect were planning something together.

Luckily for Zhang Dong he had developed a little technique with the help of his system. He could now eavesdrop on the conversations of other cultivators that used special sound moving techniques for it. He could hear what the Yggdrasil Sect leader and his sword-wielding partner in crime were saying. This made his bottom lip quiver as he tried not to smile.

“It was probably a scheme, those two must be in cahoots! That monster tide incident either never happened or it was exaggerated to make us drop our guard. Now they know that we are working together!”

The two continued to talk. The gist of it was that they were convinced that the beast attack was a hoax. Zhang Dong's true identity was now that of someone from the Divine Fist sect. In their eyes, he was probably an agent from this strong sect and the United Element Sect was just a front.

The two now feared that Zhang Dong and his people were placed close to the Limitless Sword Society. They were probably there for a pincer attack, while Zhan Jie’s forces were away their main sect ground would be attacked. They theorized that they had constructed teleportation gates at strategic locations and were now waiting to strike.

“Wait, this might have been a blunder on their part, now their secret is out!”

The two continued further, Zhang Dong’s overreaction was questioned. Probably the golden-haired junior was someone he deeply cared about so it even made him drop his act. He defended her but with this, he brought attention to his true identity. Which was a powerful nascent soul master from the Divine Fist Sect.

This all made sense to them. This was probably why his aura felt like it was in the middle stage but he was so strong. It explained why he was able to defeat the Silver Spear Patriarch so easily. In their eyes, he was some hidden monster either in the late stage or in the great circle. His young appearance was probably just to make others let their guard down around him.

Zhang Dong had to move his head to the side. The things they were coming up with were just silly. They kind of made sense if you looked at it with one mindset but the far-fetched theories fell apart if you really thought about it. They were even thinking that he was the old retired sect leader that had hidden himself away and built power-up in the lower lands.

He didn’t even need to do anything about this, the imagination these people had was truly immense. They just weren’t able to wrap their heads around it just being an act of kindness from his side.

While the two people there were blowing things out of proportion and while the Yinglong Pavilion Patriarch was rubbing his chin, Zhang Dong shifted his gaze towards the two people from the Divine Fist Sect.

He used the same technique to talk with the old man and sent his voice right next to his ear.

“Greetings, I think I might have caused a slight commotion here and for that, I’ll apologize.”

The old man’s eyes quivered slightly but he tried keeping his facial expressions neutral.

“Apologize? You saved my granddaughter, for this, I will eternally be grateful honorable Senior!”

The man replied while using the same hidden technique.

“But… May I ask why Senior decided to help us and how are you related to my granddaughter? I didn’t know that we had such honorable family members as you.”

The man was quite formal and respectful. It was clear from his tone and choice of words that he didn’t want to offend Zhang Dong.

“Ah, I have a strong bloodline technique, it allows me to feel people that I’m close with, It was more or less a coincidence. Who wouldn’t help their cute niece if she was in trouble?”

Zhang Dong replied while just coming up with a plausible excuse. He was actually related to the girl, or at least this body that he occupied was.

“Senior can track a lineage through a technique? Truly fascinating but even with that your actions...”

Zhang Dong knew where the old man was going with this. Even if he was related to this girl, he shouldn’t know her well enough to risk his life. However this was indeed the truth, he did only save her because it was the right thing to do in his opinion. He was the type of person that even in this sort of world didn’t like to see others getting killed. Though he was in the vast minority when it came to this reasoning.

“Well, I know it’s hard to imagine my reasons. How about you could just repay this favor in the future? Forming positive karmic bonds is something that I’m known for.”

It was far easier for Zhang Dong to just ask for a favor in return. Some people did live their life through karma here. If you helped someone they were expected to return the favor, otherwise, they would be sewing bad karma. Which in term would bring bad luck upon them, either in this or the next generation.

The greater Dao of Karma did exist in this world but Zhang Dong’s knowledge of it was shallow. It also tied into the Dao of fate but to affect people's future was something out of his reach, at least for now.

“Good karma? Ah yes, that does make sense…”

The old man replied while digesting the information. At this moment Zhang Dong decided to shift the conversation in a different direction. The two sect leaders that he had gone against him were still speculating with each other. He had to inform this man that he was now partially responsible for their plans.

“Elder Heng, It would seem that your enemies might have gotten the wrong idea about our relationship…”

Zhang Dong gave him a small rundown of the situation. About how the two thought that he was a hidden member of their sect. He explained how the two thought that he was some kind of backup plan. He was there to apparently perform a sneak attack with the main sect if the two other sects ever attacked them.

“This…”

Fang Heng didn’t know what to say. He certainly didn’t know anything about something like this, it did make a lot of sense as Zhang Dong was related to his granddaughter in some way.

“Yes, regrettably that’s not true. It was just a coincidence that one of my family members was related to your granddaughter. You’d know if you saw the rest of my family…”

He didn’t really feel like explaining how his grandfather operated, it wouldn’t bring anything substantial into the conversation so he decided to leave it out. It would also be kind of embarrassing to admit that he was related to someone promiscuous like that.

“This misunderstanding could be a godsend for you but you would have to trust me and explain your situation in detail. I’ve heard that a beast tide ran through your sect and many masters died, even your sect leader.”

Zhang Dong needed more information. If he went along with the misunderstanding he could actually give the Divine Fist Sect some time to recuperate their losses. The Limitless Sword Society would probably also leave his people alone if they thought that Fang Heng's side was still powerful.

“If those two think that their misunderstanding is true, your side will probably acquire much needed time. You could even recover if their spies get caught.”

He knew that if the other sects weren’t at least 80 or 90 percent sure of their victory they would probably wait it out. The same thing happened to him, the three sects left him alone out of fear of his Wei Hung persona. He was also lucky enough to have a system in place that protected him from spies. Without any new information reaching his enemies, they could do nothing but wait, attacking his sect was far too much of a risk.

Fang Heng had to think for a moment. He looked at this granddaughter that was there. She was now standing behind him along with some of the sect elders from his sect. He was a bit apprehensive about this situation.

The man before him did indeed save his family member but his motives were unknown. He could as well be working for those two sects and just trying to get information out of him in a more roundabout way.

This elder had a hard time believing that the other sects would go to such lengths. They already had basic information about the monster attack. They just didn’t have clear numbers of how many people perished. The first incident with his granddaughter was probably what his enemies had planned. This man probably belonged to a whole different faction but if he was telling the whole truth would remain to be seen.

“I…”

The man stuttered, he thought about his situation and if it could get any worse. Was there something he could do without getting outsiders involved? His plan was to quietly leave Fang Meili here and then return to his sect. There wasn’t really a thought about his own survival there, he even feared that he wouldn’t reach his sect grounds after he left this city.

There wasn’t really much he could lose anymore. If the other two sects decided to attack they would probably only be able to bunker up in their main city for a few months. The information this man could spread wouldn’t really add that much.

“Senior asks for much but if what you’re saying is true then maybe my sect can still be saved. I only wish for one thing in return, please protect my granddaughter, if you swear this I will trust you.”

Zhang Dong eyed the blond girl, she had been staring at him for quite some time now. He had probably left quite an impression on her at this point. If he agreed to the man’s terms he would need to take her to his sect. He would also probably need to look after her or dump her onto one of his elders as a pupil or something.

‘Maybe Liena could accept her as a disciple or something…’

He didn’t really need to do this though. He could just walk out of here and worry about Zhan Jie and his cronies later. Getting them to think that he was part of a stronger sect could get him out of a fight later on though. He still had them fearing his master persona too but if he came off too threatening they might try to attack him out of fear.

“You have my word, I can take her to my sect where she will be well protected.”

In the end, his good-hearted nature had come out on top. Now he needed to listen to what this old man had to say and then decide on how to spin this. Zhang Dong hoped that the Divine Sect’s situation wasn’t completely unsalvageable. They still were in a good spot and probably had a lot of cultivation resources. He could probably even add them to his own as future payment.

“That feels reassuring, senior. I will put my trust into you…”

The man finally decided to talk in detail. In a matter of moments, the full truth was revealed and Zhang Dong was already strategizing about how to salvage the situation.

Chapter 236

Fang Heng finally decided to give Zhang Dong a recap of what had transpired back at his sect. The two had some time till the Yinglong Pavilion leader made his decision and the other guests were just whispering amongst each other as well.

“About a month ago we came across a strange set of ruins, this was the beginning of our troubles…”

It all started normally with a new interesting discovery. Some people had dug up a passageway that led them into some underground ruins. There was a labyrinth worth of corridors down there and a team of cultivators was dispatched to map the place out.

There wasn’t much at the beginning but after a week all signs of the first team of cultivators were lost. They couldn’t get any information on their progress and their communication jades weren’t responding. It was as if they just vanished.

This prompted the sect to send out a second party of slightly stronger cultivators to go check. The team arrived at an empty camp with no one in sight. There weren’t any signs of struggle but after some digging, they could see that their sect members had entered the underground ruins.

Most of the team then entered into the underground passages while a few members remained outside. They reported regularly every hour to the people back at the sect. Then at night, there was a worrying report of some strange sounds coming from the discovered entrance.

Soon the second team met the same end as the first one and finally, the nascent soul elders moved into action.

“Yes… if maybe they arrived sooner we could have done something but it was too late, the creature that slumbered there had already absorbed too much blood…”

Zhang Dong raised his eyebrow but didn’t stop the man from speaking. Fang Heng after stopping for a moment continued with the story.

The area was closed off and one of the powerful elders moved in with a weapon in hand. He was greeted by his sect members or at least by what was left of them. They all had turned to horrendous monstrosities, not resembling any kind of demonic beast that they had ever seen.

Some looked like masses of tentacles with eyes, others looked like leeches with giant shark-like teeth. Others were just fused together bodies that gave out dreadful screams of pain that even caused dementia to lesser cultivators.

The monsters then started pouring out of those ruins, attacking everything that they saw. Every defeated enemy was assimilated in one way or the other which made their army grow.

This wasn’t even the worst part, that was the leader of the monsters.

“Wait…”

Zhang Dong had to pause after the man had described the big bad monster that was behind all of this.

“Webbed wings… humanoid in shape… big arms with claws at the end and a face that looks like an octopus… also of giant proportions…”

He gave out a sigh as he knew what this creature was. He had even fought other variations of this beast before, they weren’t at the nascent soul realm though. This one apparently was.

“Something wrong senior?”

“Ah no, please continue…”

The massive monster took flight and caused widespread panic in their lands. Nothing could stop it and the cities it went through turned into its minions. Even their nascent soul masters couldn’t stop it as it continued to even turn them into their minions.

In the end, the hidden elders from the Divine Fist Sect used some kind of forbidden art to critically injure the monster. The monster vanished afterward but they weren’t sure if it was dead or if it was just waiting to strike again.

The reserve elders had used up most of their life force in that attack and half of them died while the other was in a self-induced coma. They were using some healing arts but they wouldn’t be waking up any time soon.

Their sect leader wasn’t quite dead either, he had been infected by the monster's poison. He was apparently being kept alive by some of the sect's healing treasures. This was also why he wasn’t able to attend this meeting.

Fang Heng was the only nascent soul elder that hadn’t been hurt during the onslaught. There were still some lesser monsters roaming around. Their sect was slowly clearing out the infected cities.

‘This sounds like some kind of horror movie, I bet that thing isn’t dead…’

Zhang Dong felt a bit responsible as he had fought those occult beings before. He still was speculating that the first one had been here because of him. He wasn’t sure if it was the same creature, it might have been evolving each time.

He might have to kill it again but this time around he would need to erase every atom down to the soul. He was now a nascent soul master so he could do it this time around.

“I see...I think I need to see those ruins…”

“You want to examine the ruins senior?”

The man was quite surprised. After hearing that story any normal cultivator would evade the trouble. The monster was strong enough to go against multiple nascent soul elders at the late stage.

“Yes, if that monster is what I think it is… then it probably isn’t dead, it will be best to strike while it is injured.”

Zhang Dong frowned, another big problem had fallen down on his shoulders. The monster was very good at regenerating and was probably not dead. The old man was from a sect that used divine energies which made him believe that it was weak to those. This was in all likelihood the reason why it fled.

This also made him more confident as he was someone that was versed in the Dao of the holy element. It was a Dao that was above the divine dao that Fang Heng’s sect practiced.

“It looks like the fellow Daoist from the United Element Sect did not lie, he is indeed related to that junior.”

Before he could think about what to do next the leader from the Yinglong Pavilion finally spoke up. He glanced from the green glowing chalice to him while leaning on one of his hands. Everyone in the room also stopped with their whispering, it was time for the verdict.

“Still, you have interfered in the sacred competition, you have to be fined.”

The man rubbed his chin while looking at Zhang Dong, Fang Meili didn’t even dare to look at the monstrous elder that could smite her with a quiver of his brow.

“A low grade heaven artifact should be enough, none of the other contestants were hurt by him and the competition continues.”

Zhang Dong nodded and pulled out an intricate-looking spear. It radiated the might of a heaven grade artifact and was indeed a low grade one. This was one of his earlier products and was more or less a failure in his eyes. He didn’t want to give weapons that he created to other factions but in this case, it was fine.

He gently guided the weapon towards the Yinglong Pavilion leader so that he could inspect it. The man grabbed the spear by the shaft and started looking over it, after a moment he gave a resounding nod.

“A fine spear. With this your involvement in the competition will be forgiven, if you wish to engage with the other sects in battle then please step forward.”

Zhang Dong looked to the other two. If they challenged him to battle he would accept. Fighting one on one against each one of those two would be better done here. He could at least deliver a long lasting wound and he wouldn’t need to worry about other nascent soul masters getting involved.

He didn’t think that he would be confronted here though, the other two were now suspicious of his motives. For them, this was some kind of scheme by the Divine Fist Sect. In their eyes, Zhang Dong was their agent and might have even been placed here to fight them.

Just as Zhang Dong had reasoned the tree looking elder didn’t make a move. Zhan Jie looked quite maddened and was staring daggers at him but he also didn’t come forward. Zhang Dong could even hear the two bickering a bit as the sword fanatic wanted to do battle with him.

After a bit of glancing from both parties, it was clear that no one was willing to step forward from either side. Zhang Dong didn’t want to be the instigator even though a one on one fight might have been more favorable for him. There was also a chance that something could go wrong, you never knew what could happen. These two elders were also much stronger than the Silver Spear Sect leader.

“I see that no one wishes to step forward. Let us continue with the banquet then and forget about this little incident.”

The commotion was finally over and the competition continued. The atmosphere was quite tense and people kept looking at Zhang Dong. After the drama was settled he remained seated with the elder from the Divine Fist Sect and his granddaughter. She was allowed to stay here under their supervision.

They continued to silently discuss with each other while the young girl was kept out of the loop. She had enough maturity to know that she didn’t have any say in this conversation. She would wait for her grandfather to speak up.

“Here take this.”

Zhang Dong took out a small box and handed it to Fang Heng. The man looked at the item and could feel that it was a complex artifact.

“This is?”

“It’s a beacon, take it to your sect when you return and activate it in a safe location. I will be able to travel directly to you then.”

The item that he was giving the old man was a portable teleporter. He didn’t want to go with them immediately. They didn’t need to give out their plans to their competition, it would be better if they thought he was back at his own sect.

“Hoh… thank you senior.”

The man looked at the artifact and placed it in his spatial ring. The other people could see them but what the item was no one knew. It looked like a square box with some runic designs on it.

“You just need to add some spiritual energy into it with the correct code and it will activate.”
Zhang Dong explained how the device worked and also gave Fang Heng the correct code to activate it. There was more than one of them, they were in place to alert him if the one activating the beacon was in trouble.

“Anyway, Fang Meili was it?”

Zhang Dong had finally finished up his conversation with the older man. They had decided on a plan of action and now they just needed to get through this banquet. The competition wasn’t quite over and it would probably take another day for the juniors to finish up with this one.

“Y-yes honorable senior!”

The young girl flinched when her name was called and dropped her head instantly.

“Ah, you can relax. Think your injuries should be healed, does it hurt somewhere?”

Zhang Dong asked while scanning the younger girl with his spiritual sense. The girl just blushed a bit after feeling what the man was doing, his eyes were very deep and mysterious.

“I’m fine senior, you don’t need to worry about me.”

The girl started bowing repeatedly while panicking. It seemed that she wasn’t used to interacting with people like him that much or she was just the shy type.

“That’s fine then, your grandfather and I have discussed a couple of things and one of them concerns you.”

Zhang Dong turned to face Fang Heng. The old man just nodded as he knew that it would be better if it came out of his mouth. She would be returning with Zhang Dong and his people while her grandfather would be going back to his own sect.

With the other factions blowing things out of proportions with their imagination they should be able to return home safely as well. Returning back home was the first thing Zhang Dong was planning to do. His wife was close to giving birth and then he had a squid monster to face off against, this time around he hoped it would be the last time…

Chapter 237

The banquet came to a close. The winner of the competition was a junior member from one of the ten greater sects. It was not the young master that went after Fang Meili’s life. After getting repelled by Zhang Dong as he was saving the girl one of the other young masters betrayed him.

This was something only natural, he got stabbed in the back during the whole commotion and no one even knew who was the perpetrator. He wasn’t dead but heavily injured and his battle prowess sunk low. If he wasn’t from one of the better off sects he would have probably ended up dead.

There of course was a fighting tournament that luckily ended within the day. With the help of pills, the junior members were able to recover their wounds and stamina. This was quite the opportunity for the young warriors but for Zhang Dong it was just boring.

On the third day, it was finally over. The other sects sometimes gave him strange looks but no one took him up on the offer for a fight. If it wasn’t for the people from the Divine Fist Sect then he probably would have coasted through this banquet with no incidents at all.

They did give him some valuable information about an old enemy though. He knew that the monster that he would fight wouldn’t just pose a threat to him but all the other people in this land. He didn’t think that the other sects would help out though. They would only get involved if their factions were directly involved and in danger.

He, on the other hand, saw the bigger picture, if the monster kept creating more abominations from the cultivators it slew then soon the whole empire would be overrun. He saw first hand how the monster could evolve by sucking energies from other living beings when he fought it the first time. He needed to go back to his sect and prepare, maybe even get some of his sect elders involved in the fight.

The senior members from his sect that he brought along didn’t get into any trouble. Some of them even managed to make some lesser connections. He left it to them to make some trade deals as they did have many materials they could trade for.

In his dimensional regalia, there were various high level spiritual herbs and even minerals now. The more spiritual energy they inserted into that immortal treasure the larger it became. Somehow all of that energy didn’t just dissipate but it combined into the land and created more. Even some pockets of precious metals started popping up for the sect members to mine and use for crafting.

“Well then, I will be off. You should be careful of the Yggdrasil sect, they might try something during your return, activate the beacon if something occurs and I’ll come aid you.”

Zhang Dong was in the hotel now and talking to Fang Heng. It was time to say their goodbyes.

“Senior Dong, you have already done so much it would be rude for me to demand even more help…”

The old man clasped his fists and did a small bow his granddaughter that was standing behind him did the same.

He was afraid that the old man would be ambushed during his return. The other factions were probably planning such a thing before he got involved. Their speculations didn’t mean that they would drop their old plan. However, it was likely that they would make some changes.

He needed them to get that teleportation beacon there. Without it, he would need to make the journey there himself. This would take him through enemy territory and if he was spotted could cause more trouble for him.

He couldn’t just transfer himself to places that he had never been to before. All of the teleportation gates he used had their own coordinates. These couldn’t be changed, if they were then a person going through one could end up dead.

People weren’t sure what exactly happened but they would sometimes get teleported to some random location. This could be inside of a wall or a volcano. If they were less lucky they would never return, lost within the gate, or just being disintegrated into particles.

Zhang Dong deliberated on lending his new ally his flying ship. It would probably be strong enough to protect them from any enemies. He didn’t want to endanger his own people too much though or lose a very important asset in enemy territory.

He also couldn’t make the journey himself with the old man. He was too worried about his wife and child. It was around that time and it could happen at any moment. He knew that the birth could be very dangerous for both of them, only if he was there to aid Feng Liena would he feel at ease.

“Fine then, take care on your journey and I hope you will make it safely back to your sect.”

“You too, Senior. I hope our paths will cross again!”

Fang Heng clasped his hands and turned to his granddaughter. She was next to the two while they were talking so she heard it all. The old man placed his hand on the girl’s shoulder and gave her a contemplative look before speaking out.

“Take care of yourself and listen to your senior uncle.”

The girl had tears in her eyes while looking at the old man that was slightly smiling. She didn’t want to leave and going with this man was a big risk. There wasn’t much that she could do though, she was just a lowly junior at the foundation establishment level.

“I… will I ever see you again grandfather?”

Fang Heng looked at his granddaughter and placed his hand on her head.

“Silly child, your grandfather isn’t so easy to kill and I’ve also made a promise with your senior uncle that I will reach our sect!”

He smacked his own chest with some force and then finally parted with Fang Meili. The girl watched as her grandfather flew away towards the ships from the Divine Fist Sect. The other members from her sect followed right after her.

“Young miss, we need to go…”

A female voice called out to Fang Meili. She turned to face this person and saw a girl close to her age. This was one of her maids, she and another one would be coming with her to tend to her needs.

Fang Meili just stood there and looked at the man that had saved her. She still had trouble processing everything that had happened.

The man called Zhang Dong looked at her back. She couldn’t tell what he was thinking from his facial features. He was quite the handsome man and if it was any other occasion she would have probably been head over heels for him.

This wasn’t the case, she was feeling pathetic for not being able to do anything. Soon her sect where she spent her entire life might not even exist. The only person that could aid them was standing before her. How far he would go to aid them was unknown, her grandfather was putting his trust in Zhang Dong. She couldn’t do the same; she was still skeptical of his true motives.

“Fang Meili was it? You’re going to glare a hole in my forehead if you continue like that…”

The chuckled slightly while the blond girl opened her eyes widely. She didn’t know when but she started rudely staring at him. The moment this fact was revealed one of her maids stepped forward.

“Please have mercy, my lord, the young lady didn’t know her place.”

She dropped down to her knees and started begging. Fang Heng that was of similar status as this man was now gone. Without him around the maids worried that their young miss could get into trouble by offending Zhang Dong.

The young lady in question started trembling slightly, would she get punished already. Staring at someone as established as this person would be considered a huge offense. Some people took things like etiquette very seriously. In some sects like that she could even be sentenced to death along with her maids.

“Please my lord anything but the young lady, punish me instead!”

“Yes great lord, punish us instead.”

She saw her two maids going down to her hands and knees with their heads lowered. These two were servants assigned to her when she was but a child. They were in their 30s and started out as teenage girls. The two girls were very loyal and were even trying to give their own lives away for her.

She couldn’t allow this, this was her mistake. Even though she didn’t trust this man, he was someone from the older generation. He was someone that her grandfather called a senior. He was clearly lowering himself before this man but she dared to stare at his face for so long.

“No please, punish me instead, my maids didn’t do anything wrong, it was my inexperienced senior uncle!”

She followed suit and was now kneeling down. Her head was down and she wasn’t even looking up.

Zhang Dong looked down at the girl that he was supposed to take care of. He was trying to ease up the tension with a small joke but the other’s took it the wrong way. He as always forgot how these people worked.

For them, it was impossible for someone from the elder generation to be joking around with a junior. Not unless they were related or had some kind master-disciple relationship.

He just stood there shocked at the display, soon the three girls were kneeling. The elders that were behind him didn’t help either as in their eyes this was an obvious offense. Some of them even looked like they were unwilling to let this pass.

“Such rudeness, is this how you should act around someone that saved your life?”

The one walking was Zhang Dong’s great grandmother and also his wife’s. She looked quite maddened by the fact that this girl had the audacity to stare at the sect leader with such irritation. The other oldies that were very much people that followed old traditions just nodded. From their point of view, the young woman would have to be punished in some way.

Before that could happen and this whole situation got out of hand Zhang Dong raised his hand up. A golden aura surrounded the three kneeling females and moved them all back to their feet.

“That’s enough. You lot should knock it off, we don’t have time for this and those are our guests. I promised her grandfather that I will take care of them, she is also my niece, so show some respect. Now let us depart!”

He surrounded everyone with his aura and started flying towards the Argonaut. He knew that if he let that continue for much longer that something bad could happen. One of the maids would probably try to end her life to appease the big bad elders from the United Element Sect. She would even think that her life would be well spent by offering it to the senior members.

“Relax, I have promised to your grandfather that I would protect you. You don’t need to kneel and I would like you to refrain from doing such things in the future.”

Zhang dong said while they quickly flew towards that giant battleship that was waiting for them. The three women could only stare at each other without being able to react.
The Argonaut was still hovering outside the city grounds. It stuck out like a sore thumb due to its massive size and strange design. For the time being there was a shield around it as some people did try to enter it. They were promptly blasted away into the stratosphere.

“Also don’t worry about your grandfather, he won’t die so easily.”

It was time to return, if it would be smooth sailing on the way back it was hard to tell. For one thing, there was still the problem of the two sect armadas that had escorted him here. After the fiasco that happened back at the banquet, he wasn’t sure if they would just let him go back home that easily.

Chapter 238

Fang Meili and her two servants were now flying through the air. They had apparently overreacted a moment ago and this man didn’t seem as stuck up as some other nascent soul masters.

This wasn’t the big surprising part though. They all were from the Divine Fist Sect and all of them practiced some form of divine arts. These arts harnessed holy energies from the world to power their techniques.

The golden shield that Zhang Dong surrounded them with was of very pure holy energy. The group of girls was at quite low level compared to this senior member. But even they could feel how pure and how powerful this energy was.

All of them knew that if you wished to have such a pure aura around yourself you had to be a good person. Fang Meili had witnessed the divine aura of her grandfather and some other elders before. This one was far more pure and gentle than that, it showed her that this man was probably someone trustworthy. Someone that was evil or malicious could not produce something like this.

If someone killed a lot of people their killing aura would seep out one way or the other. A life of slaughter would also impede a person’s progress in the divine arts. You had to keep your soul clear of unnecessary negative emotions if you wanted to progress in them.

This was also why this purity of holy energies was mind-boggling. Normally even the grand elders from her sect would have at least one or two negative thoughts. These would delude their divine aura and lessen its power. Zhang Dong on the other hand didn’t seem to have such an impurity in his aura. Either he was a saint or there was some other secret to why he was so pure.

Fang Meili was far too stressed the first time she met this man. Her grandfather also instantly blocked out other people from infecting her with their spiritual energy. She didn’t have the time to process the information.

Now, she was slightly more reassured in going with this uncle of hers. She did even recall one of her grandmother's having some kind of love affair hundred of years ago. Maybe this man was related to that love affair.

“Get ready, we will be living immediately towards our sect grounds and we won’t be waiting for the other sects to escort us back!”

The girl was brought back to reality by her new uncle’s deep voice. The other sect members that consisted of old men and women nodded with agreement. One of them that had really dark skin then spoke up.

“I agree, the Patriarch from the Limitless Sword Society didn’t look pleased, they might try to force our hand.”

The girl frowned when she recalled the man in question. Zhan Jie was the leader of that sect, they were also part of the group that was chasing after her in the labyrinth. One of their members even landed a strike on her leg that caused an injury. She swore that in the future she would have her revenge, she just needed to get stronger.

In a matter of moments, they all left the city. They were flying through the air and in a flash arrived in front of a strange-looking flying object. The golden-haired girl and her servants went wide-eyed at the sheer size of this thing.

It was a lot larger than the ship that they came in and looked to be made from metal. Some strange buzzing sounds were coming out of it and even the girls could see a large number of cannons poking out from everywhere.

The barrier that the ship had opened up a small circular hole through that all of them flew through. Zhang Dong’s barrier kept things like G-force outside so anyone inside wouldn’t feel sick.

All of them finally landed on the deck and were greeted by the ship’s captain. The man gave some kind of strange salute. He was also wearing unusual clothes and a strange looking hat. The young lady and her maids kept looking around, everything looked new and mysterious to them.

“Report!”

Zhang Dong called out while the man that was the captain nodded.

“Yes sir! We have remained on high alert, some of the sects tried testing our defenses but as instructed we retaliated accordingly!”

“Good, anything else?”

The girls just remained staring there, no one moved from their spots while the man in charge was speaking.

“The Limitless Sword Society ships have surrounded us from all sides and have been watching our movements since two days ago. The Demon Subduing sect and the Dragon Gate Sect have remained neutral and they have even begun pulling their ships away after your arrival.”

The Dragon Gate Sect and the Demon Subduing Sect didn’t seem like they were willing to tussle with Zhang Dong’s faction after his power move during the banquet. There were too many unanswered questions for those two to interfere.

“Dragon Gate… even though they were the ones inviting us here, we didn’t get much time to talk…”

Zhang Dong said while tapping his finger against his thigh.

“Don’t worry Patriarch, me and the elders have managed to talk business while you were busy. We will bring the paperwork to you later as the Dragon Gate sect is willing to do business with us!”

One of the old men jumped in while clasping his hands together. The girl just listened while trying to figure this United Element Sect out.

From her point of view, their leader was really strong but his people didn’t look that imposing. They were just a bunch of old men and women in the core formation stage. It didn’t look like they would be making the jump towards the nascent soul stage either.

The flying ship on the other hand looked like a technological marvel. She could feel that it was a heavenly treasure but how strong it really was compared to the other flying vessels was still to be seen.

“Hm, we should talk about this inside…”

Zhang Dong said while looking to Fang Meili. The girl lowered her head slightly while still being a bit scared.

“Take these three to the guest cabin, treat them well, and don’t let anything happen to them. The rest of you return to your stations, we will be returning home at full speed...”

The man said before turning around. His long white hair slightly bounced around as he made his getaway.

Fang Meili and her servants were guided through the metal monstrosity. On their way to their cabin, they could see United Element Sect members rushing around. They were wearing strange militaristic type uniforms and seemed somewhat organized. She didn’t recognize anything that they were carrying but she somehow knew that it was related to weapons.

One of the crew members let them inside a certain cabin. It was quite large and looked like a hotel suite. Inside the spiritual energy was high and they could even see food placed on one of the tables. There were several beds in this room along with windows through which they could see the scenery outside. Only after the person that took them here left did the girls speak out.

“Young lady, we need to be careful, that senior looks benevolent but it might be a trick!”

One of the maids said while the other nodded with approval.

Fang Meili moved toward one of the tables. There was a juicy looking apple just there, she took it into her hand and then took a large bite out of the fruit.

“You two are worrying too much, not like we can do anything about it. I’ve promised grandfather that I would follow … my Uncle to his sect…”

She paused before referring to Zhang Dong as an uncle. Everything was still surreal and she was still digesting this whole situation.

“Not like we could do anything about it… you’ve seen it... “

Fang Meili dropped down onto the largest bed and looked up at the ceiling. Her maids moved closer but knew what their young missy meant. Not like they could run away, even if they got outside this ship there was no place for them to go.

The other sects had already figured out that their Divine Fist Sect was weakened. If it wasn’t for Zhang Dong, Fang Meili would already be dead.

“I owe that man… uncle Dong my life… I will wait and see… he said that I shouldn’t worry and that I will meet my grandfather again…someone with such a pure divine aura shouldn’t be a bad person...”

The two maids also nodded at that point. That senior did have an unusual divine source to himself. It was above anything that these three women had ever seen, far above any elder from their own sect that they knew.

Before the three could get comfortable a red light started flashing in their room and they could feel that the ship started to move.

“Code red, Code red… Everyone is to proceed to the battle stations.’

The announcement was loud and the whole flying ship started shaking violently. The girls looked at each other in surprise. They didn’t have time to even fully sit down and now there was some kind of problem.

All of them moved towards one of the windows that let them see the outside. They could see three large more traditional looking ships flying their way.

“Is that the Limitless Sword Society emblem?”

“Those bastards want to attack us!”

The two maids cried out in fright. They were very much scared of that bloodthirsty sect. From what they knew it was one of the more ruthless ones. The people from that faction were known for their love for battle. They always liked to make their swords do the talking instead of bargaining or going for a compromise. They along with the Yggdrasil Sect were their biggest enemies.

“Calm down you two, look at that…”

Fang Meili pointed towards the three ships coming their way. They weren’t getting closer instead it looked like they were slowly getting left behind. This ship that they were flying in was slowly picking up the pace and leaving those smaller ones behind.

“How fast are we going?”

“Was it always that easy to run away?”

From what the girls knew flying ships of that size weren’t the fastest. Even as a heaven graded item the sheer size made the whole vessel slower.

But there they were, leaving the other flying ships in the dust. The trio continued to look outside the window and they could see more ships appearing. They continued their chase but it didn’t look like they would be catching up anytime soon. It really looked like their group would be making a clean getaway. That was before they felt a rumble and then saw the protective barrier flickering.

The girl's cabin was in the back of the ship so they couldn’t see what was happening in the front. They could see the shield flickering multiple times which probably meant that they were getting attacked by something. The ships that were left in the dust also started catching up.

The alarm kept ringing and it looked like the members from the United Element Sect would be getting involved in the fight.

Fang Meili couldn’t just sit around in this room without any information. She decided to peek outside and luckily the door to her cabin remained open. There were also no guards around to push her back in.

“Young lady you mustn't! We were told to stay here, it might be dangerous outside!”

The maids ran after their young miss that decided to go outside. She remembered from where they arrived and it didn’t take her long to reach the area outside. The ship crew was far too busy with their own assignments so there was no one to stop this trio from snooping around.

The moment she was outside she could see it. There were multiple burning flying ships around them along with cultivators on swords. There was a full-blown aerial battle taking place and explosions were happening everywhere.

“Face me, Zhang Dong!”

A booming voice was heard by her and brought her attention to the sky.

“You are even dumber than I had anticipated!”

She saw the man that brought her here. He was floating directly above the flying ship with a sword in hand. His opponent was the sect leader from the Limitless Sword Society. With him there were two more nascent soul elders, it looked like her savior was outnumbered.

Chapter 239

The United Element’s Sect’s flagship had left towards their sect grounds. The cultivators that had escorted them here were less than stellar about them leaving. The Argonaut just sped away leaving the three ships that were chasing them behind.

Zhang Dong had hoped that with his ship's enhanced speed he could just safely return home with haste. This wouldn’t be that easy though as a certain person was already waiting for his arrival.

It was a classical ambush with multiple flying ships waiting for them. The people that were here were from the Limitless Sword Society without the aid of any other faction. The ships from the Demon Subduing Sect didn’t seem to be there anymore. Probably their leaders decided to evade this battle after the strange happenings during the banquet. It seemed that Zhan Jie had other plans for the United Element Sect.

Even though there was only one faction here, Zhan Jie wasn’t the only nascent soul master that arrived. There were two other people floating slightly behind him and both of them radiated nascent soul might.

Zhang Dong was standing around in the ship's bridge. The whole crew from the ship was looking at the screens and they could see the ships that they left in the dust closing in.

“Those two behind him are only early stage masters, can I leave them to you, Captain?”

He asked while looking at the rough-looking cultivator. The man looked like an old fisherman, his skin was tanned and his face looked scratched up. He also had an eyepatch over his eye and Zhang Dong totally didn’t only choose him for his looks to be the ship's captain. He had some skills to back up that look of his.

“Leave it to us, Patriarch! The Argonaut is more than enough for the likes of them!”

Zhang Dong nodded while moving outside, before leaving he just gave one last order.

“You are free to remove the limiter, use the main cannon if you have to.”

The man just saluted, the whole flying ship started buzzing. It was time for everyone to head to the battle stations.

Outside Zhang Dong could see canons rising up and appearing on the main deck. These were all manned by train cultivators and all could fire condensed spirit bullets.

Those cannons were already large in scope but they all paled compared to the monster that was hiding inside. The ship's main cannon would only be activated when it was required, the power drain was quite staggering.

While the whole ship was transforming the enemy cultivators weren’t passive. The leader from the other sect started shouting out the moment he noticed that Zhang Dong was leaving the confines of his ship.

“There you are, face me Zhang Dong!”

He looked over to the man, he already had his sword unsheathed and pointed at his head. He wasn’t sure what this guy was thinking, he should know better. He himself had already proven himself in the arena and given the chance didn’t think he would lose to this guy.

“You are even dumber than I had anticipated. Are those two behind you your backup plan? I guess you are at least smart enough to get some help.”

Zhan Jie went red in the face while the two elders behind him moved closer.

“I don’t need their help to take care of someone like you! Elders destroy that ship and bring me that woman, I need to hear the truth from her!”

Zhang Dong realized this man’s genius plan. He probably thought that he was indeed part of the Divine Fist Sect.

The only worry that Matt had now was if the person from the Yggdrasil Sect was as daring as this guy here. He was one thing, but that old man wouldn’t be able to go against a late stage cultivator. Though without him activating the teleportation beacon he wouldn’t be able to help him.

For now, he had to worry about himself first. He was still up against three nascent soul cultivators. This reminded him of the fight against the Dark Palm Sect. That time he was lured into a trap and almost killed due to ignoring the weaker cultivators. This time around he would be more careful, he also wasn’t alone, he had some backup.

Even before the fight could start the massive Argonaut gave out a strange sound. It started radiating energy and the cultivators around the area could feel it rising. The seemingly low graded heavenly treasure started giving out telltale signs of a middle graded one. It also didn’t seem to be stopping just there as the power levels continued to rise.

“Well then, I hope those two can take care of themselves…”

Zhang Dong smirked while his sword appeared in his hand. Lightning covered his body and he just shot forward, his sword strike was met by Zhan Jie that was forced back while his fellow sect elders looked on with horror. They couldn’t follow Zhang Dong’s speedy movements at all.

As they turned around to aid their leader they were met with another problem. A barrage of Qi bullets flew right towards them as the massive flying ship started attacking. The Argonaut 1 wasn’t just aiming for the two nascent soul targets, it was aiming for every ship in the area.

The two fast-moving human targets managed to dodge in time but that wasn’t true for the slow-moving ships. Their shields weren’t strong enough to resist the concentrated fire and they started exploding. The cultivators inside started to quickly abandon their ships as they escaped outside.

“How could this be…”

The two nascent soul masters found themselves dodging a barrage of fast-moving projectiles. They could feel that if they got hit by one of them they would be in serious trouble.

This meant that other people below their realm stood absolutely no chance. All of their ships returned fire, the core formation experts that were flying around did the same but the massive metal behemoth remained in place. Its shields lasted through the combined retaliation attack and the ship remained undamaged.

The massive fortress of the ship started to move, its guns firing in all directions. The smaller enemy vessels stood no chance. Their firepower and even their maneuverability was lower than this mass of metal that kicked up a storm like winds whenever it moved.

It wasn’t quite a one-sided slaughter though, the enemy cultivators still had two nascent soul masters on their side. These two old men stood together and started shielding some of the ships from the cannon fire. The Argonaut was good at hitting large slow-moving targets but when it came to small human-sized ones it wasn’t as accurate.

It soon turned into a battle of attrition where the massive ship continuously fired at the core formation and nascent soul cultivators that were dodging everything they could. The people from the Limitless Sword Society were quite good at flying on their swords. Which was the cause for prolonging this battle.

While the whole area turned into a bright light show, further up in the clouds two men were facing off against each other.

Zhang Jie and Zhang Dong started colliding in mid-air. Their sword attacks rained down against each other like a torrent of water. Each time they clashed they produced a booming sound that broke the sound barrier apart.

The shockwaves created from these clashes were periodically pushing the clouds they were fighting to the side. After a couple of exchanges, both of them flew back, both of them didn’t suffer even a little nick

“Is this all?”

Zhan Jie snorted as this was more of just a prelude to what was to come. It was normal for two fighters to measure their skill level by exchanging some blows. These weren’t meant to kill but just to get a grasp of your opponent.

“I should be saying the same thing, if that was it… it would be better if you just turned around. I’m really not someone that likes to bully weaker people, you can turn around and our sects can still coexist with one another.”

Zhang Dong spoke out while looking at his opponent. He knew that people like this Zhan Jie didn’t react well to taunts like this. In this situation, though it wasn’t a taunt, he didn’t feel like he was weaker in any shape or form. He would let this transgression be and even let them keep their lives if they just left.

“Coexist? Turn around? Are you mad! You should be the one groveling and asking for forgiveness, that fool from the Yggdrasil Sect might be wary of your motives but this Zhan Jie never flees from a good fight! You will fall to my sword like everyone that came before you!”

Zhang Dong just started spacing out after his opponent started giving him a long speech. At least he got some information out of it. Apparently, the leader of that other sect had told this guy to not engage.

This meant that they were probably unwilling to act just yet. Fang Heng's chances of survival had increased as they would probably not chase them after he left. The Limitless Sword Society leader was here so the old man should have a clear path home. That is unless there isn’t another battle happy sect leader after them.

“Fine, have it your way. I might have been lenient with your types in the past but too many lives are at stake. Let us get this over with.”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh while Zhan Jie started fuming with anger. He waved his hand and his spatial ring was activated. In a matter of seconds, thousands upon thousands of white swords were hovering around the sword cultivator.

“I will show you why they call us the Limitless Sword Society!”

There were swords everywhere, they circled around the whole area and slowly started taking the shape of something. Zhang Dong wasn’t passive though, he also activated his spatial ring and a couple of swords shot out, eleven to be exact.

He let go of the sword he was holding on to and the dozen blades placed themselves around his body. They paled in comparison to the huge mass of metal that finally took on the shape of a lotus flower with Zhan Jie in the middle.

The opponent in the white robe was surrounded by what looked to be a mass of metal. There were so many of those swords that they made the lotus flower have solid mass. It wasn’t an illusion it was a giant flower made from swords.

With a wave of his finger, one of the huge silver flower petals parted from the sword formation. It gently floated as if it was getting carried by the wind but in a matter of seconds, it shot forward. Thousands upon thousands of blades rained down on Zhang Dong, each one of them infused with the man’s nascent soul aura.

A dozen blades that were surrounding the sect leader from the United Element Sect sprung into action instantly. They started spinning and circling around his entire body while deflecting the rain of swords. The sound of metal clashing against metal at supersonic speeds couldn’t even be heard.

Zhan Jie’s had a smirk on his face after sending his first petal down. Soon it started contorting in the opposite direction as he saw that all of his swords were getting deflected. The twelve weapons that the man produced were somehow able to deflect or slice them apart. Not even a single strand of his hair was being damaged.

“How could this be…”

“What? Do you think even one of those earth grade blades can scratch one of my heaven grade blades? You think I didn’t notice that you only have a few heaven grade ones hidden in there…”

Zhan Jie’s forehead started showing quite a thick vein before he waved his finger again. Another two petals parted from the lotus flower and shot forward. Their aim to kill the man that wasn’t even moving from his place.

Chapter 240

Zhan Jie’s facial expression was mixed. He was standing in the middle of his Limitless Lotus Sword Formation that his sword sect was known for. It was the pinnacle of their power and it was a technique that brought them countless victories.

The look of confusion and anger was directed at his opponent Zhang Dong. The man that he was facing didn’t move from that one spot for the entire time he unleashed his technique. The thousands of swords that he was utilizing were being repelled by just twelve blades. These blades danced around at speeds that even he had trouble following.

“This can’t be possible... “

He shook with indignation while moving both his hands forward. Like a conductor directing a symphony, he started moving them around at a fast pace. The shiny silver lotus flower petals that were made from his swords started flying forward.

This technique was supposed to slowly wear down the opponent's defenses while drowning them in sword intent. But whatever he threw at Zhang Dong the man didn’t seem to be moving from the spot he was standing in. It was as if the technique that he had spent countless years on honing was useless.

This was something that he couldn’t just let be, his pride didn’t allow it. All of the silver petals were utilized at the same time. The sheer concentration required to control this many flying swords was something noteworthy.

Zhang Dong managed to bounce or shatter every incoming sword with ease. His opponent wasn’t willing to give him room for breathing as he saw a mass of swords getting in position around him.

The sky was blocked out by the shiny silver metallic blades. It looked like a million weapons were pointed straight at his head while he only had twelve to defend himself with. Even while looking at all of those he didn’t falter and just kept his gaze at the person controlling them.

Zhan Jie without missing a beat swung his hand forward as if pointing his army of swords to go get this enemy. The blades reacted by simultaneously charging forward at sound breaking speed. They were thousands of small jet planes on a collision course.

Zhang Dong’s aura exploded as he activated his defensive formation that only consisted of a dozen blades. These sharp treasures were clearly superior to the ones that were coming this way.

But they were like a large tree against a tsunami, would they still be standing after the massive wave of blades hit?

“Your sword intent is strong but it won’t be enough! Now die!”

Zhan Jie shouted out while confident in his victory. Each blade that he sent had his sword intent included in it. This was the crystallization of all his knowledge and life as a swordmaster. How could a pseudo swordmaster like the one he was fighting against here be his match?
Before the mass of edges infused with spiritual energy and the dao of the sword, Zhan Jie felt a jolt run through his entire being. He wasn’t the only one affected as the descending blades also trembled. It was as if they were going up against a superior predator.

“What?... no how could this be…”

Zhan Jie’s eyes went wide and he almost got a heart attack. What he saw was something that he didn’t think was possible.

Sword intent was a fabled state of mastery over the sword. A swordsman that had mastered it could even produce sword energies that could slice apart opponents.

This wasn’t the pinnacle of swordsmanship, there was another fabled stage that surpassed this. There was close to no one that had reached that stage in many thousands of years. The ones that did were just a few and mostly hidden away as the sect reserves as they were hidden grandmasters.

The Limitless Sword Society leader could hear something akin to a heartbeat coming out of his opponent’s twelve blades. This sound resonated outside and affected his large flying sword formation quite drastically.

The twelve swords charged forward releasing massive surges of blade energies outwards. The moment this wave of dao connected with the large mass of metallic blades a giant explosion occurred.

Zhan Jie flinched while flying back, all of his swords started trembling and slowly cracks were appearing on all of them. The ones that were closest to Zhang Dong just shattered instantly as they met their match.

“S-sword Heart!”

Six of the swords that were hovering around Zhang Dong’s body broke out from the formation. The haven grade treasures were bathed in golden light that included sword intent and sword heart. The radiation of these energies could be felt by every cultivator in the area which caused them to stop.

The core formation experts from the sect that was attacking the Argonaut were shocked. Their flying swords started trembling as if they wanted to flee from this place. The blades of these practitioners had something like an instinct.

Weapons above the earth grade started getting something akin to a spirit. It would only fully awaken when they reached the heaven grade. But even now the tiny not fully formed primal souls in these blades were crying out in despair. They wanted to flee or swear allegiance to the person that was able to use sword heart.

The people on the Argonaut 1 were also surprised. It wasn’t often that their sect leader showed off his skills. They had no idea that his mastery of the sword had reached this high. They felt proud, their grand leader was a sword grandmaster, a fabled existence in the whole empire.

The person that was up against him started retreating. The lotus flowers that were shining brightly while reflecting the sunlight started shattering into tiny fragments. The six swords continued to bulldoze through them, chopping them apart into tiny fragments.

Zhan Jie received a big hit to his stamina. This formation was very taxing on his cultivation, with the destruction of his blades he was getting weaker and weaker with every passing moment.

He wasn’t even able to retrieve his massive collection of blades that took him hundreds of years to procure. The swords just trembled in the air as his enemy's sword heart overwhelmed the sword intent that he had mastered to its pinnacle.

He was still unwilling to surrender or run. This sword formation was only one of his techniques and he didn’t feel like this was over yet.

The man clasped his hands together and his whole body started glowing white. A roar of a dragon was soon heard after as it flew up into the sky, Zhan Jie on its head with his main sword in hand.

Zhang Dong didn’t remain passive either. His body turned to gold as a similar massive beast shout could be heard in the surrounding area. His massive golden dragon soul-beast was summoned instantly to clash against the other one.

Zhan Jie was also in the possession of a dragon type soul-beast. His was a classical eastern dragon that looked more like a serpent with deer antlers and silver scales.

The two beasts clashed in the sky against each other. The clouds were pushed apart and the earth trembled below as the two masters collided with each other.

The people from the two opposing sects halted their advance while backing away. The two nascent soul elders that were going against the ship looked up while evading cannon fire.

They could feel that their leader was losing. His sword formation was already broken and shattered weapon pieces were raining down from the sky above.

The two looked at each other and nodded. While backing away they also brought out their own soul-beasts. Instead of attacking the ship with them they turned around and flew upwards. They decided to help their sect master with the fight while their beasts kept the massive ship busy.

They were underestimating the flying behemoth too much. This was just what the captain of the Argonaut was waiting for. The moment they were summoning their soul-beasts was the moment that he gave the order.

“Activate the Gungnir! Aim for the soul-beasts!”

The massive ship’s deck started spreading apart. On its bow, a large compartment was opening up. something that looked like a cannon was pushing itself outside while the machinery made space. The cannon didn’t have a traditional circular barrel, it had a pentagon shape instead.

The cannon appeared outside and was already gathering power for the shot. The spiritual energy was making the air outside warp. Many tiny blue lights converged onto the canon’s opening as it charged up for its attack.

“W-what is that… watch out brother!”

The two nascent soul elders finally noticed that something was off. They were concentrating on creating their soul-beasts and allowed the ship to power up its main cannon.

Just as the two large creatures were formed the cannon was also ready.

“Charge at 76% captain.”

“Doesn’t matter, take aim and fire!”

The person in charge of the new weapon grabbed what looked to be a joystick in hand. He was looking at a screen, this screen was showing him the scenery outside. There were a couple of circular indicators lining up and when they locked on one of the beasts the man pressed the button.

A strange sound escaped from the cannon right before it was activated. A giant spear of blue light shot forward, in a fraction of a second it was already at where the target was. The nascent soul masters that were there gathered up their energies in the hopes of producing a shield.

Everything was bathed in blue light and the people that were standing outside of the blast point were blinded. A massive ear shattering explosion occurred, the spot where the two soul-beasts were in looked as if it was on fire. It looked like a small blue sun appeared and was destroying everything in its path.

From inside that blue sun, strange screams and shrieks were heard. The two soul beasts didn’t have enough time to escape and took the brunt of this massive attack.

The Gungnir Cannon’s muzzle let out some smoke after it was fired, tiny electrical discharges bathed the bow of the ship. People could clearly follow the path of this cannon’s attack, right to the explosion.

After the dust had settled, the two massive soul beasts remained missing. They were turned to fine particles and their masters suffered a large backlash. If a person’s soul-beast died the cultivator would take direct damage to their own soul. Sometimes this was even fatal if the connection between master and beast was strong.

The two old men’s fighting potential fell by more than fifty percent. They cough up massive amounts of blood while escaping. They weren’t even thinking about helping their sect leader anymore, now their own lives were on the line.

This was a giant hit to the morale of this sword sect. Two of their masters were fleeing while being severely injured. What was left was a group of core formation cultivators that couldn’t hope in defending themselves against this massive flying ship. The only thing that could turn the tide was their sect leader.

All of them quickly looked up, their leader was still up there fighting Zhang Dong. What they witnessed was another brow raiser.

An even brighter flash of light followed by the parting of the clouds. It was as if the heavens were being cut apart.

This wasn’t their master performing this terrible swordmaster technique. This was the man from the United Element’s sect instead. On the receiving end was Zhan Jie.

He didn’t know how this could have happened but it did. His eyes were moving apart from one another at this very moment. It was as if he was becoming wider but in reality, he was sliced right in the middle.

His body was severed from head to groin and his body was parting to the sides. Even at this moment of death, he couldn’t process what exactly he witnessed. His vision was blurring and the last thing he saw was a man bathed in golden energy. The man didn’t look glad over his victory at all. The only emotion that could describe it, was pity.

Chapter 242

Zhang Dong set himself before the engine unit of the Argonaut 1. He sat down in the lotus position and started gathering all of his spiritual energy. Golden lightning bolts started appearing all around this closed-off space in a matter of moments.

These beams of energy started pelting the floating device in the middle of the room with their might. The decahedron item that was the main battery started spinning around and the tubes connected to it began absorbing the newfound power.

The captain of the ship sat down in his seat while one of his crew members spoke out.

“Captain, the ship's power is quickly rising, it's going to go over 100% soon!”

“The Patriarch is aiding us, activate all the engines. We will be heading straight towards New Spirit Spring City at full throttle!”

The people on the bridge nodded, the person responsible for activating the ship's bonus thrusters moved a large handle forward. The whole ship shook violently as it jolted forward.

On the outside, the massive Argonaut 1 was surrounded by a blue shield. It started flickering with some lightning and even turned gold due to the new power source. The whole giant ship then shot forward like an arrow.

Zhang Dong wasn’t willing to wait here as the word of him slaying Zhan Jie had probably reached everywhere. There were other people watching over this battle which would spread the news faster.

This was a good turn of events as it would give other sects something to think about. The Limitless Sword Society Patriarch was a famed swordsman. This same swordmaster was bested in battle by a relatively unknown master. This validated Zhang Dong’s strength even more than the battle he had during the banquet.

The person in question wasn’t bothered by the rumors that would be spreading. He just wanted to get his people back to his sect grounds. He couldn’t leave this ship unprotected in enemy territory and they did need to go through the lands of other sects. The same three sects that had destroyed the old Dark Palm Sect.

Even with this power up the ship would need some time to return to the borders. Zhang Dong could teleport back home, but unless it was really necessary he needed to power the ship for it to go faster.

………..

While the giant behemoth was causing widespread panic the life of the new recruits back at the sect continued.

Cheng Yun and Yang Rong were done with getting their basic body refining technique. To their surprise, there wasn’t just one technique for everyone. There were multiple ones and supposedly they were picked out by the sect to fit their bodies.
Yang Rong was now sitting in his dorm room with his brother. He thought back to the time that he first entered the brand new library. He still could remember the goosebumps that he got after seeing it.

Firstly, the building was truly humongous. It had several levels but the first floor was the largest area of them all. This floor that the junior Qi condensation disciples were allowed in had a staggering amount of manuals in it.

Yang Rong was slightly scared that he would be unable to pick a good manual for himself. He also didn’t know how to spend his merit points, there were just too many options to choose from and he had no one to point him in the right direction. His old brother from the tribe was in a similar situation.

Luckily for the two, the United Element Sect elders had thought about the confusion that the new disciples would have. There was also a limited number of techniques a person should learn. There wasn’t time to master it all, it was better to specialize in something than be average at everything.

But how would they know what they should specialize in?

Normal disciples needed an experienced teacher to figure such things out. Unless they were born with a specific obvious talent they would need to go through years of training to just figure something like this out.

In this sect, things were a bit different. At the new library building, the juniors were greeted by another hologram. This one explained to them how they would be able to procure the correct cultivation books.

There were multiple screens spread out at the library’s entrance. These screens were the newest addition to the sect's resources and worked akin to computers. They had a limited usage as they were only for picking out books from the database.

The person needed to have their merit emblem scanned by this machine and it would first show them their statics. After they activated this machine they could pick out books for themselves. Some as the free ones they received just needed to be chosen. If there wasn’t enough stock the books would be printed out by a printing device.

There was also an option of direct knowledge insertion into the disciples' minds. This type of knowledge transfer required the use of points but could aid people in understanding difficult techniques.

This wasn’t the interesting part of this machine. The thing the disciples found astonishing was how it proposed manuals to them based on who they were.

This was all possible thanks to the extensive scanning that was done in the beginning. The sect had a whole database on the disciples. The library software could see what the people were good at and could propose techniques that fit their disposition.

With this, they didn’t need to pick out skills at random or ask the teachers to point them in the right direction.

This also saved them from spending their hard-earned merit points on expensive techniques. They could end up getting something that they had no talent for and wasting their time and merits.

Cheng Yun ended up with a Qi condensation manual for people good in the earth element. The library system pointed out that he had 87% proficiency in that element and his second-best one was fire at 67%.

Yang Rong on the other hand was the exact reverse of this tribe member. He had 89% fire element capacity while only having 57% in earth and all the other ones were below 50%. He was now focusing on techniques that mostly belonged to the old Huo Clan.

This had saved the two youths a big headache down the line as the two wanted to follow in the Patriarch’s footsteps. They were both going to go with lightning element techniques. To their dismay, they both had bad compatibility with it. After long consideration, they decided to go with the things they would be good at.

They could now see that it was the good choice. After acquiring their Qi condensation manuals they were already making progress. After the first day, they were coughing up black blood and sweating dark green liquid from their pores.

The new line of techniques was already removing the impurities from their bodies and making them stronger. They felt like they could mercilessly beat up their old selves from a week ago if they tried now.

“So regrettable… the Patriarch’s lightning techniques look so overpowering and stylish…”

“I agree… but Grand Elder Qiang’s are also fine, he is supposedly the second strongest member from our sect! You at least have Elder Qiang… I don’t think there is anyone proficient with the earth element at the grand elder level in the sect...”

Cheng Yun grumbled while hovering a small rock above his index finger.

“That’s true… maybe you can be the first one to make it there junior brother.”

The two laughed while moving down from their beds. It was time to head out towards the sect, there was much for them to do besides cultivating in their dorm rooms.

They could visit free lectures where teachers would help them understand their Dao paths. They could also go to the training areas like the gym. These two quite liked to perform muscle training and due to the Patriarch’s more muscular form, they wanted to achieve a similar physique.

There were a lot more people with the same idea than others might expect. At the gym, there were many people pumping iron.
This was also quite a novel experience for everyone here. Mostly at other sects, the disciples were left lifting heavy uneven stones. Maybe just holding them above their head at uncomfortable positions.

There weren’t many factions that studied the art of muscle training. Most of the students performed stamina raising tasks without getting a full-body workout every day.

In this sect, a strong body was the basis of your cultivation path. With the help of specialized pills the juniors could replenish themselves each day and continue working on the other. There was no need to wait for recovery and they could push their bodies to the limit.

This was another day like that. Cheng Yun and Yang Rong were doing this together as they were advised. Everyone was supposed to get something as a spotter. This person would aid the person that was lifting heavy weights if it became too much.

Yang Rong was laying back with a metal bar in his hands. On the sides were circular weights of the exact same size. He was doing some bench presses while Cheng Yun hovered his hands away from the bar slightly. When Yang Rong’s arms began to tremble it was the time to push on and cheer.

“One more senior brother, you can do it!”

Yang Rong’s face started getting red as he pushed and pushed. His hands began shaking furiously as he gave his all. Cheng Yun was focused on the bar ready to grasp it if something went wrong.

If his brother wasn’t able to lock out his joints he would need to aid him. If he dropped this heavy bar with the weights down he could injure himself. Luckily he managed to push through and rack the heavy bar back onto the bench press rack.

The two then exchanged places and Yang Rong started spotting Cheng Yun instead. The cling of metal against metal was heard in the whole area. The gym was filled to the brim and some people were even forced to wait.

Most of this building was filled with sweaty men. The women mostly came here to use the squatting racks. The body refining techniques that they possessed used a lot of kicking movements and less punching techniques.

The sect had to separate the males and females in this building. The men couldn’t help to stare at the junior and senior sisters. They were wearing form-fitting leggings while performing the heavy lifts. A lot of men had discovered a new found love for those work out clothes after seeing them in action. They tended to promote the rear end of the female form quite a bit.

“Did you know, our Patriarch had gone to the other sects on some kind of official business…”

“Oh, do you know what it was about?”

While working out some of the junior members that were resting started talking. Words of Zhang Dong’s expedition was already reaching the ears of this sect. The news was spreading at a rapid pace through the entire empire.

“Think there was some trouble? But our Sect leader easily bested someone in an arena battle… Think it was someone wielding a spear? I’m not really familiar with the other nascent soul masters...”

The youths had sparkles in their eyes while mentioning their sect leader. In their minds, it would be a great honor for them to get noticed by him. Still, the news of him fighting other sect leaders was a bit scary. The youths weren’t feeling confident in their own abilities quite yet. It was too soon for them to go into war with other sects.

Soon the aforementioned leader would return and more news would be spreading. Not of a war or a tragedy but the arrival of a new life instead...

Chapter 243

A group of guards was making their rounds on top of a steep wall. This wall seemed to stretch for kilometers and there was no end visible in sight.

They all were kind of bored and not really keeping much attention to what was happening around them. It was nothing new, they did this multiple times for years. There was no reason to push themselves, doing the bare minimum was enough.

Due to this, they were all a bit slow on the uptake when it happened. They heard a strange rumble and then the whole place began to shake. The thick bricks on the walls started cracking from some kind of pressure.

This was indeed strange as these walls were reinforced and had lasted without taking any damage for multiple years. The soldiers looked around while moving their spears and bows forward. Soon they saw something in the distance.

“W-what is that? Quick, we need to alert the elder!”

Before they could react they felt a massive oppressive force wash over them. This was clearly a nascent soul aura and it was coming off from the approaching object.

The soldiers on the walls were mostly cultivators in the foundation establishment realm. They were even on the weaker side of that. People that were forced to perform tasks like this were mostly ones that failed to advance further.

This was a border region between two sects and they were the first defense as well. They were mostly here to man cannons that had a power similar to core formation elders.

But now they were a bit preoccupied with trying to resist this massive pressure. They were even unable to fire at the fast-moving object that was speeding towards them.

Suddenly an elder appeared that could actually move. He looked out into the distance and narrowed his eyes. The moment he realized what was coming his way he started to sweat.

“M-make way!”

He called out while flying to the side. He realized who the faction coming was and had decided to let them through.

A massive iron fortress that was covered in golden energy pushed on without stopping. There were no words exchanged between the people at the border wall and the passing forces.

The moment they flew over the wall it started crumbling apart and even more, cracks appeared. No attacks were needed, just by being there this object was causing massive destruction in its wake.

“E-elder… we need to report back to the sect, our Demon Subduing Sect is being attacked!”

A man on a sword appeared and flew over to the only nascent soul cultivator that was there. The elder looked at the core formation master and narrowed his eyes. He moved his hand up and promptly smacked the other man’s head.

“S-senior?”

The man held his hurting noggin while being flabbergasted.

“You fool! Do you know who that was? Do you want to get me killed like that idiot Zhan Jie?”

The nascent soul master started cussing out his junior in front of everyone. The lower cultivators didn’t know why but the man had a reason to be like this.

He received the notice that Zhan Jie had intercepted Zhang Dong from the United Element’s Sect. Both of them had thought but who won was now clear.

This left the Demon Subduing Sect in a bind. Should they aid the Limitless Sword Society and go against the new rising power? Or should they wait this out and take a more passive approach?

This was also what the Dragon Gate Sect Patriarch was thinking about. While the decisions were being made in the background Zhang Dong was still seated in the engine room.

They had just arrived at this Sect’s territory. If they flew through it they would arrive faster at their home turf. He was slightly worried that they might have gotten attacked, he felt the nascent soul cultivator on the outside. He backed off quite quickly and didn’t even shout at them, this kind of showed him this sect’s stance.

While giving it all to power this power-hungry beast of an engine he was looking at his system screen. His wife was part of his sect so he could see her status. It showed him various things along the lines of potential and devotion.

This wasn’t what he was interested in though. She had a certain trait in that large table which was the indication for her pregnancy. The worrisome thing was that it had ‘Imminent’ written next to it.

He wanted to teleport there right this instant but was afraid to leave the people of this ship alone. He was in the territory of a sect he had shaky relations with. If he just left the Argonaut could be captured. The ship had a lot of firepower but that was against other large targets.

Hitting even an early stage nascent soul cultivator was hard. Even worse when there were multiple cultivators firing back. This sect had at least ten of those nascent soul elders flying around in these lands. If they let them be like the one at the border region was debatable.

Zhang Dong needed to force it through with all his might. He took out a handful of pills from his spatial ring and munched them down.

He felt invigorated after swallowing these high grade pills that he himself had made. With the boost of spiritual energy, the ship flew even faster.

The people on board weren’t having such a grand time. The ship wasn’t constructed to take this much power. The gravitational forces that the huge ship had to go against also exceeded the advised limits.

Most of them were glued to the floor and unable to move. The Captain was still sitting in his large chair but his whole body was sinking into it. His cheeks looked squished and his eyes were closed as he tried not to pass out.

The people weren’t in danger but some of them were passing out while unable to handle the increased speed.

The ship turned into a blur in the sky, stopping it now was practically impossible.
……………..

“Uhhh… that was a strong one…”

Feng Liena was laying back in a large bed while grasping her tummy. There were other sect members in the room with her.

There was a large intricate formation drawn on the ground with the bed she was on in the middle of it. There were several cultivators sitting in strategic locations giving out a similar holy aura to that of Zhang Dong’s.

This was a previously prepared birthing chamber prepared by the greatest medical minds and formation experts that the sect could muster.

The previous birth of the young lady was already a miracle and the Matriarch was bedridden for weeks afterward. Zhang Dong had chosen to prepare for the second time, his wife was adamant about getting another child even when he was against it. He was fine with one miracle but was afraid of the consequences. Feng Liena on the other hand wanted to have another go at it.

This had been prepared beforehand to make the second attempt much smoother. There was a little problem as the formation required Zhang Dong to be there. Otherwise, it wouldn’t work at full capacity.

He was the only one with pure enough holy energies to make this process halfway safe. The others hadn’t progressed in their Dao enough and were only core formation cultivators. Feng Liena on the other hand was a nascent soul master, someone greatly above their power level.

“Mwomy…”

A small child was in the room, holding her was Zhang Jin. Other members from both the Zhang and Feng Clan were still in the room but most were outside.

“Don’t worry, mummy will be alright, daddy will come back soon…”

Feng Liena replied while looking at her daughter that was in her grandfather’s hands. She was sweating profusely, she had gone through this ordeal once before but this time it was even worse.

The whole room was glowing with faint golden energy. The runic symbols pulsated with faint light as the whole structure was still missing it’s main battery.

“Yes, we need to leave your mom, for now, you’ll have to play with grandpa for now.”

Zhang Jin smiled while looking at Feng Liena. She was close to giving birth and he couldn’t let the small child witness something like that. The child sniffled a bit as she was carried away.

“What of my husband?”

Feng Liena asked while gritting her teeth, she could feel that something was wrong. The previous experience wasn’t this bad, she had a tough time staying awake. She also denied the usage of any painkillers afraid that they would affect the child inside her belly.

“The Patriarch was stalled during his return by the Limitless Sword Society leader…”

One of the maids explained what transpired and how Zhang Dong needed to slain Zhan Jie during his return. The news was troubling as her husband reassured her that he wouldn’t be seeking any trouble.

“At least he is safe, he will have some explaining to do when he returns.”

Feng Liena chuckled while another jolt of pain ran through her body. She couldn’t help but scream out in pain. The people around her were quick to react, they inserted all of their spiritual energy into the holy formation. With the influx of the healing energies the pain slightly subsided and the Matriarch was brought back before she could pass out.

Soon another jolt of pain ran through the woman’s whole body. This time around her whole body convulsed while giving out a menacing aura. The energies inside her body were going berserk due to the birth.

The oppressive aura caused everyone in the room to shiver. Some of the lesser cultivators even passed out instantly.

Suddenly a portal of bluish light sprung open right beside the bed that Feng Liena was shuddering in.

A panting Zhang Dong walked out, it looked like he was in the middle of swallowing something. He was sweating all over quite uncharacteristic for a master of his level. He had somehow managed to push the ship towards his own territory and appeared here to aid his wife.

The moment he entered the entire formation churned with power. The whole room turned into a golden spectacle. The people could finally let out a sigh of relief as the Patriarch arrived.

“What took you so long.”

Feng Liena replied in a weak voice while Zhang Dong grasped her hand. A pleasant feeling washed over her instantly as her husband shared the burden with her. His face contorted slightly as he transferred most of the pain that his wife was feeling towards himself.

He wanted to give his wife a hug but he needed to move into a specific location in the room. Some of the maids moved in place and took care of Feng Liena’s needs while he squatted down.

He placed himself in the center of the formation and began inserting his holy energies into it. The room lit up once more, many tiny golden fireflies appeared and started dancing around. They all gently flew around Feng Liena’s belly and started slowly falling onto it. The moment they did they were absorbed, their healing energies aiding in the birth.

Seconds turned into minutes and minutes turned into hours, soon the whole process had taken over a day. The people outside were pacing back and forth.

Everyone that was closely related to the sect Patriarch and Matriarch was here. Their disciples and close family members, even close friends like Huo Qiang. All of them were worried as this birth was a special one.

They all waited patiently without saying anything. They could feel the powerful energies coming from the room within which gave them a reason to rejoice. They knew that Zhang Dong was working diligently, soon they would be adding a new member to the Zhang family.

Chapter 244

“Have you heard?”

“About the banquet?”

“Yes, the ship the Patriarch left on arrived the other day, he apparently killed one of the sect leaders that we were subservient to…”

“Do you think we will be going to war?”

Two sect members were talking to each other. Rumors had reached everywhere now, the death of Zhan Jie was no small matter. It could be the prelude to another extinction event like a war.

“What are you two mumbling about!”

Another female member from the sect walked out to interrupt the conversation.

“Stop talking about nonsense while the Matriarch is…”

The woman didn’t get to finish her sentence as the whole area around them rumbled. The people here were tasked with watching over security around the Patriarch’s mansion. In it, the Matriarch was apparently giving birth to her next child. The whole process had already lasted through a few days.

Suddenly the clouds parted, the ground rumbled and the beasts around the whole sect started howling loudly.

Everyone in the sect could feel that something strange was happening. They all looked to where the clouds were opening. A bright ray of light descended onto the residence of their Patriarch.

Zhang Dong’s home was right up in the sky overlooking the whole sect. Due to this everyone in the whole sect and even the city could see this strange phenomenon. It was as if God himself was descending down and illuminating the path.

“What is happening? Are we being attacked?”

Someone asked while looking around. The ground was shaking, the tremors were concentrated on where the large castle in the sky was.

Suddenly a large golden beam of light shot out from this flying building. It bathed the surrounding area in its light causing the rumbling to cease. Soon a large rainbow appeared illuminating the floating castle and pointing right at the Patriarch’s villa.

“This isn’t an attack… that’s…”

“By the immortals, That’s the elusive phantasm rainbow…”

Right after the sect member could finish the rainbow started shifting in scope. It became larger and larger, finally turning into a huge rainbow dragon that gave out a ferocious roar. The image of the beast soon faded and the clouds closed themselves up as if nothing had transpired. The people that witnessed this strange occurrence had their mouths agape.

“Was that the Empyrean Rainbow Dragon?”

Everyone shook violently while looking up into the sky.

“This is truly a good sign, a dragon has been born, it must be the Patriarch’s child!”

The people started rejoicing in the streets. A strange phenomenon like this meant a couple of things. First that the child that was born this day was blessed by the heavens. It also signified that the youth would be quite the character and should be primed to become a powerful master. That is if he managed to reach his true potential.

While the regular cultivators were cheering in the streets Zhang Dong was still sitting down in the middle of the array formation. All of the other aids that he had trained for this occasion were passed out. This was fine as everything was now over and the child was born.

His current appearance wasn’t that great. He looked as if he had lost some weight during this process. His long hair was disheveled along with his robe that was drenched in sweat.

Even though he was tired he used the rest of his strength to stand up. He moved forward towards the bed that his wife gave birth in. He moved his hair to the side and straightened himself out.

He could see a tiny person rolled up in a towel being held by his wife. She looked even more tired than he was but she was still conscious. She was looking at the tiny person that just escaped her belly.

“Congratulations Patriarch, it’s a healthy boy.”

One of the nurses told him as he moved closer. He could hear his son crying his little eyes out. He was given a smack to the bottom by the nurse as he took his first breath.

Zhang Dong moved closer and looked at his newborn child. He did a quick examination to check if the boy was healthy, to his surprise he was more than that.

‘Heavenly Body constitution?’

He could see his son’s statics and they were quite pristine. His potential was a whooping A++, the highest that he had ever seen in this world. He also possessed a special constitution, from what he knew such a boon would hasten his progress.

He would be primed for the heavenly Dao, which was something he himself was good at. He did practice the Heavenly Lightning arts, this meant that his child took after him more than his mother. This was the reverse of what happened with his daughter that was more inclined towards her mother’s Dao.

“He has your eyes.”

Zhang Liena called out weakly while looking at Zhang Dong. He had momentarily stopped moving but after hearing his wife he moved closer and grasped her hand.

“You think so?”

He looked at the little munchkin that came out of his lovely wife. His skin color was a bit more inclined to her’s. He did have his eyes though and also the white hair color that Zhang Dong was known for. This might have been the effect of having that rare constitution though.

“Do you want to hold him?”

Liena asked in a tired tone, even though she was a nascent soul practitioner she was quite tired. This birth was a lot harder than the previous one and it was probably due to his son’s special trait. Nothing good came easy in this world.

Zhang Dong gently grasped the wrapped up baby that was still crying and was sure to hold his head up. This wasn’t the first time he was holding a newborn so he wouldn’t be making the same mistakes again.

He looked at his son and the little one looked back. The moment the two eyes met the child quieted down. The little baby looked very interested in the man in front of it. Soon the child started closing his eyes, probably tired after bawling for so long.

The Father just smiled at the tired little potato. He then waved his hand around and his gentle aura spread throughout the room. The bed that Feng Liena was resting in was lifted up from the ground. Zhang Dong took off to another room to get some privacy, some of the maids following after him as they needed to tend to the new baby.

After some alone time with his new family member, the child was left with his mother to rest. Zhang Dong on the other hand headed out of the room. He needed to tend to his other child, Little Xiu was still waiting outside with her grandfather and the others.

He made sure that his wife and child were tended to and then he left. When he opened the door outside he was greeted by his close friends and family. Zhang Jin, Xue, Jie, and Liu were there as well as Huo Qiang and even Zhang Zhi had come to pay his respects.

He could tell that the latter had recently broken through but it didn’t seem that he had yet reinforced his cultivation. This was an unwise move but the man wanted to show his respect to his Patriarch.

“We have heard the good news, congratulations Dong’er.”

Zhang Jin was the first one to speak up. Zhang Dong nodded and could see his grandfather's two main wives next to him. For this occasion, they weren’t even fighting, which was truly something uncommon.

“Dada!”

He plucked Zhang Xiu from the ground and placed her in his arms. His daughter giggled as he gave her cheek a big smooch. After some head patting, he turned to face the others.

“Congratulations Master.”

He nodded a couple of times as people started to congratulate him on the success.

“How is the child?”

“He is fine, he is sleeping with his mother, both of them went through a lot… don’t think it would be wise to try this a third time…”

Zhang Dong laughed weakly to himself. After this birth, he came to the conclusion that it would be dangerous to have a third child. From what he knew it was already a miracle that Zhang Liena was able to bear two kids.

Nascent Soul masters were built differently than lower-ranked cultivators. They were walking spiritual energy generators, akin to nuclear reactors. Their bodies had to be in tune with the world around them.

A pregnancy brought chaos to their bodies, the spiritual energy was thrown into disarray. This caused danger to the unborn children, even during the months of pregnancy Zhang Liena needed to stop cultivating. She focused all of her attention on the child inside her belly, keeping it healthy while trying to keep the energies in her body in check.

It would be possible for both of them to perish if she suffered some kind of injury or shock. This is also why Zhang Dong had told her that he didn’t want any more children. The pregnancies seemed to be getting worse and the next time he might not be able to do anything about it.

“He also has quite the special constitution… I noticed some kind of omen outside…”

He was focusing on keeping the array formation working so he couldn’t see the rainbow dragon too well. The people outside were quick to inform him of the joyous sign.

“Empyrean Rainbow Dragon?”

Zhang Dong nodded as he also knew what that meant. He also knew that a favorable sign like that could also spell disaster.

It showed that his son was special and if nurtured well would be one of the strongest cultivators in the world. This was a good thing for the sect, who wouldn’t want to have someone like that on their side?

The problem wasn’t his sect but the others. If they got wind of something like that they could react poorly. Something like assassination attempts might happen. Some of them might try nipping the bud before it can bloom.

“We will have to increase the security around here…”

“Don’t worry Master, I will protect him with my life!”

“Me too!”

Both Zhang Xue and Liu moved forward, their eyes were sparkling as they already fell in love with his daughter. He always could use good seniors to help his children out in the future and these two were very reliable and trustworthy.

“Well that’s reassuring, I bet little Jun will love his senior sister and brother when he grows up a bit.”

Zhang Dong patted Liu’s shoulder and then Xue’s while walking around with his daughter in one arm. This was a joyous occasion and he was quite tired. There wasn’t much time to rest though, he still had some problems to contend with.

He had promised Fang Meili and her grandfather that he would help them. He knew that the location of the Divine Fist Sect’s main city was further away. Fang Heng would take longer to arrive there than he did while flying the Argonaut. That time should be very soon though, he needed to check if he activated the beacon.

It would be great if he could get some sleep before that and also if he could eat. He was popping spirit replenishing pills for the past few days while controlling the healing array.

“Jun? Have you decided on the name already?”

He got brought back to reality by Zhang Jin’s question.

“Yes, Liena decided beforehand.”

He smiled while walking, he wasn’t good with the names of this world so he left it to his wife. He also didn’t want his child to end up with a name like he did.

For the time being, he headed out to get some rest, after eating some and showing the baby to his daughter he would need to check up on the Divine Fist Sect situation.

Chapter 245

Two days had passed since the new life’s arrival. The people in the city were still in the middle of a large party. Because of the birth of the Patriarch’s son, the sect let even the citizens have a blast.

They sponsored drinks and food to the masses so that everyone could enjoy this happy moment. The people rejoiced and as proper citizens drank themselves silly till they all passed out. Probably a lot more lives were conceived that night but that was a story for a different time.

It was the middle of the night, the sounds of laughter and music could be faintly heard outside. A white-haired man was walking through a long hall. He was wearing a loose robe and some casual slippers. They were the kind that a person would wear at home, unseen by praying eyes.

This was Zhang Dong walking towards a certain room. He was holding a tray with some food on it, a bowl with rice porridge that consisted of spirit rice. This was food specifically prepared for Zhang Liena. He preferred meat dishes to the rice ones but his wife liked something more traditional.

The large door parted as Zhang Dong opened it up with his nascent soul aura. He walked inside while the entrance gently closed behind him without making much of a sound.

“Dwady~”

On the inside of this room, there was his whole family. His small daughter Xiu was to the side and looking at her baby brother with a finger in her own mouth. She turned to her father when she noticed Zhang Dong entering.

“Yes, it’s me, your daddy!”

He just smiled back while slowly walking towards his wife. Zhang Liena was actually looking quite healthy, thanks to the healing formation the whole procedure went rather well. Her body’s energies were still slightly in disarray after giving birth but she was recovering her strength at a steady pace.

“Here have some porridge, it has some regenerative properties and is made with seven-star spirit rice.”

The tray that the bowl was on made a clicking sound and four legs appeared out of it. It then floated over to Zhang Liena’s spot and placed itself right in front of her. She had a nice large white spoon on it and some napkins as well.

Zhang Xiu looked at the floating tray with sparkles in her eyes. She was at that age where every day there was something new to behold.

Zhang Jun, her little brother was right next to the larger bed in which Zhang Liena was in. He was fast asleep in his crib. He had just finished eating his own meal and now it was his mother's turn.

“Dwady, dwady!”

“Ah, yes yes.”

Zhang Dong chuckled after looking down at his little munchkin. He used some of his spiritual energy to lift up his small daughter along with some stuffed animals in the room. He made them slowly float around the room, his daughter was quite fond of flying around. She might have gotten it from him as he also enjoyed this ability the most.

“Thank you.”

Liena called out while moving her hand over to the white spoon. Her husband took one good look at her and grimaced slightly. He could tell that she hadn’t fully recovered and that breastfeeding the child was probably the most she could do.

After taking one bite and gulping it down her hand started trembling. He could see Liena straining herself a bit while trying not to show her discomfort.

“Here, let me help you…”

This bed was quite large, there was enough space on it for him to comfortably sit down next to his wife. He took the white ceramic spoon and took some porage onto it. He then guided it towards Liena’s mouth while smiling.

“Say Aaaaaaa~”

Liena blushed a bit but didn’t resist. She felt a bit reserved about being babied so much but let Zhang Dong feed her. She opened her mouth and took the food in, as she chewed she could hear the voice of her daughter from above.

“Ahhhh…!”

Zhang Dong looked up and could see his toddler flailing her arms around in all directions while staring at them. He realized what she was trying to say and made her float towards the bed.

“Want some too?”

“Yesh!”

Zhang Dong looked to Liena for a moment and their eyes met. Both of them chuckled while he scooped up some porridge. He guided it towards the child's mouth while making airplane noises. Zhang Xiu opened her mouth wide and chomped down on the tasty porridge that was quite nutritious.

Some of the liquids ran down Xiu’s cheek as the spoon that they were using wasn’t made for kids. There was a bit too much in it for that small toddler to enjoy without it getting a bit messy. The mess was promptly cleaned out with a handkerchief that floated from the side.

‘Having something akin to telekinesis does make your life easier…’

He chuckled to himself while giving the rest of the food to his wife. One bite was enough to fill up Xiu’s small tummy. This porridge was specially made for Liena so too much of it could prove bad for his daughter as it had too much spiritual energy in it.

The body of a young child would have trouble handling such a thing if she ate too much. Luckily her father was a nascent soul master who had some ways of dispersing the excess into the surrounding.

“You’re doing well my dear husband. But it feels like I’m also getting treated like a child.”

Zhang Liena giggled some more while watching the empty bowl of food and tray float into the distance.

“It’s good to be spoiled from time to time, you should enjoy it my cute wife!”

He replied while disrobing. He set the velvety fabric to the side while revealing a set of boxers underneath. He had recovered after draining his body of a lot of his vital energies and was back to his prime physique.

He then scooted right beside his lovely wife, his hand going right under her head as he assumed the big spoon position. Liena just waited and snuggled up next to him, the two hadn’t had the pleasure of sharing the same bed in some time as he was busy at the banquet.

Little Xiu wasn’t left floating in the air either. The small toddler was also brought over to sleep with her parents and right between the two. Both of them gave their child a smooch on the forehead before relaxing. So ended the day with the whole family spending the night together.

There were some rough patches here and there as the newborn did wake up during the night. After a quick diaper change and some hugs he was all fine though.

In the morning Zhang Dong slipped out from the room while his wife and children still slept. He slowly closed the door so that they wouldn’t notice and gave some instructions to the maids.

He finally headed out to take care of some business, the issue with the Divine Fist Sect was still out there.

He looked at a circular-shaped object, this was a second teleportation beacon. This device would create the portal instantly if the one that he gave to Fang Heng was activated. The problem was that it wasn’t and it had been close to a week since the day he saw them off.

He needed to make a decision, to either wait for it to activate or go there directly. He also was apprehensive about leaving while his wife wasn’t fully recovered. She was surprisingly healthy but she would probably be out of commission for at least a week.

A lot of things could happen in a week. The Cthulhu monster variant that was probably there could come out of hiding any moment. He wasn’t sure how strong it was, the more he waited the stronger it would become and the more potential deaths could occur.

For now, he decided to wait and meet up with the other person involved. He had left Fang Meili in the Argonaut with her maids without saying much and he needed to get her settled in here. He was now heading her way, she was brought over to the west wing of his mansion.

His house was more of a castle than a mansion though. It had to even be divided into four wings and one central square in which there was a large garden with a pond and even a hedge maze.

‘That girl has to be worried about her grandfather. She had to see her people be murdered and then be smuggled away here. She also almost died in that competition…’

He recounted what he knew about the girl's predicament in his mind. If he was in her situation he would probably be terrified. Unknown place, unknown people everywhere, and no strength to getaway.

‘At least she came with those two maids, hope she doesn’t feel too alone…’

He walked through the long halls of his mansion while some of his maids greeted him. This place required a small platoon of servants to maintain. He was against getting a huge house like this, it was a waste of resources in his opinion. The sect could use this space for something more useful.

He had to relent in his opinions as the sect leader had to have the most exquisite looking abode. He also earned quite a bit of money himself so he could afford it. He still didn’t like to stand out like this but he had gotten used to it.

He continued walking until he saw a certain person waiting for him.

“Greeting Master.”

What he saw was a beautiful young woman with pure white hair just like his. She was one of those fabled beauties that could shake kingdoms and cause wards. Some people labeled her as the most beautiful woman from the sect but in his opinion, that spot was reserved for his caramel skinned wife.

This legendary beauty that had a giant fan club in the sect was his disciple and went by the name Zhang Xue. He had called her over as he had a small task for her.

“Greetings, let us walk.”

The girl nodded and remained a step behind her master. She was more of the silent type compared to her brother that was more energetic. That one had mellowed down after the years as he had to now take on the role of the elite senior brother.

He was proud that these two had become respectable adults but they still had their weaknesses here and there.

“You’re probably wondering why I called you over Xue. I have a small task for you.”

Previously he would ask people for favors but nowadays he changed his conduct to fit more this world’s standards. Asking your disciples for favors wasn’t something a respectable master would do. They only needed to give them tasks and they would be carried out.

“There is a certain person that I want you to take under your wing, she is slightly younger than you but I think you should get along. She is also your cousin… we have to thank your grandfather for that…”

Zhang Xue listened to the words of her master almost tripping over her own feet at the last part.

“Y-yes? Of course Master.”

He needed someone to take care of the girl while he was out. He worried that she might be bullied while he was gone. He was free of the family and sect politics as he was the strongest cultivator here.

This wasn’t the same for others though. He knew that everyone was in a rat race trying to get ahead in any way they could. They were schemers left and right, everyone wanted to rise up as high as they could.

He worried that his new relative could be shunned by some jealous sect members that would feel threatened by her arrival. She was Zhang Jin’s descendant and the situation in his household was quite chaotic.

While talking the two finally arrived at the guest room. After taking care of his new niece he needed to decide on his next move. Would he stay and wait, or set out on a journey towards the Divine Fist Sect?

Chapter 246

Fang Meili was pacing back and forth in her room. She had been stuck in it for some time now. After the Argonaut arrived she was finally able to disembark into the new and unknown sect.

She had no idea where her supposed uncle had gone but the people from his sect had told her that he was busy. She was stuck here throughout the whole birthing process and couldn’t leave even during the festivities.

She only had the status of a guest and was confined to this room by the person that brought her here. Besides the sect leader, the other people in this sect didn’t look very welcoming. During her arrival, she saw some of them looking in strange ways at her. The workers were whispering and everyone was giving her the cold shoulder.

“How much longer will we be stuck here? What about grandfather?”

She called out while glancing through one of the large windows. This room had all the facilities needed for them to live in but it was getting boring. Cultivation to fill in the time was not on her mind as she was too nervous.

“Don’t worry young miss, I’m sure your uncle will return in due time. Would you like to eat something? This treasure is filled to the brim, we don’t need to worry about food!”

One of the maids replied while opening a large white box. Inside the air was chilled and it looked like a closet with shelves. There were various spirit enriched food items all sorted in there. It would probably last them for at least a month without any refills.

“Yes, and we have this magical device to give us some information!”

The second maid called out while pointing at a flat square object mounted on the wall. From time to time it would activate and a fashionable lady would give out information. Not so long ago she announced the birth of Zhang Jun, the newborn son of Zhang Dong.

“If what the person said was true, then your honorable uncle is probably busy with his child. We must be patient and wait!”

“Why don’t we play this game in the meantime? There is surprisingly more to it.”

One of the maids pointed to a table. On that table, there was a sort of checkered patterned box. There were sixteen small figurines on each side. For someone that came from the modern world, this object would be easily identified as it was a chessboard.

Fang Meili looked at the table where the game of chess was placed. She had tried it previously and already figured out that this wasn’t a simple game. A person actually had to think about their moves ahead of time.

The chess pieces even had different kinds of movement akin to lower and higher realmed cultivators. In her opinion, the king represented the hidden masters that couldn’t move nonchalantly.

The limited movement showed her how the ones in power had to limit themselves. The Queen piece was akin to a nascent soul elder or maybe a sect leader that had more freedom than the old council members.

There was also a fascinating mechanic where a simple pawn could ascend to another role. When they reached the end of the chessboard it could be replaced for even a Queen! It was like a cultivator surviving through a life of hardship and finally reaching their goal.

Fang Meili gave out a sigh, even though this game of chess was interesting the maids she was with weren’t worthy opponents. They weren’t good at thinking ahead and just randomly placed their pieces on the board. Always reactive and never proactive.

While she was thinking about giving the game another try she heard a knock on the door. This was more or less only a courtesy knock as before any of the girls on the inside could reply the door started to open.

Meili was stunned at the appearance of the person that walked through that intricate white door. It was a beautiful jade-like beauty that overshadowed any she had previously seen. Her fair complexion was exquisite and went together with the long snow-white hair.

Her eyes looked like two blue gems, while looking at them she could swear that she could see tiny electrical arcs jumping around. Her figure was very well proportioned, her hip to waist ratio was right on point and her chest was neither too small nor too big.

She was that one in a million beauty that could make empires crumble and even old monsters would have their hearts torn asunder. For some reason, this beautiful person was walking towards her.

“I apologize for the delay.”

Fang Meili was brought back to reality by a familiar voice. It was her white-haired uncle that was also quite the looker. The beauty that walked in front moved to the side after opening the door. It looked like she was opening it for her uncle to let him in.

“No need to apologize Senior Uncle!”

The girl clasped her hands and did a small bow, the two maids behind her did the same while scooting closer.

“Congratulations on the birth of your son.”

She added while looking back up. She still wasn’t sure about this man’s motives. He brought her here after saving her from that dreadful competition. The only thing that she wanted to know is how her grandfather and her sect was doing. She didn’t want to be rude and ask too many questions in unfamiliar territory.

“Thank you. You don’t need to be so uptight, you are part of the Zhang family line. You’d be a branch member if we were in the old clan but so am I.”

Zhang Dong smiled slightly while shrugging. She noticed a slight twitch on his face when he was talking about the family situation. Apparently, he wasn’t someone of a remarkable bloodline but he did somehow end up as the sect leader. His new line of descendants would probably form the new royal-like bloodline.

“I actually came here to introduce you to someone.”

Zhang Dong said while looking over to the woman that had walked into the room before him.

“This is my niece Zhang Xue, she is your cousin from your great grandfather's side.”

Fang Meili was astonished that she shared the same genes as this otherworldly beauty. She didn’t consider herself that beautiful even though the people around her would tell her otherwise. Her proportions were plainer and she didn’t have that jade-like skin as most of those beauties had. Her hair was also blond while most people preferred pure black or pure white hair.

“Your grandfather from my side of the family is also here… but you’re probably better off not visiting him…”

Zhang Dong turned his head to the side and coughed into his hand while the woman next to him held her head down. Fang Meili could have sworn that the beauty was blushing as if she was embarrassed about something. Meili on the other hand was a bit interested in this new grandfather, he was more or less responsible for this encounter.

“This isn’t the reason I came here though, it’s about your other grandfather, Fang Heng.”

Meili tensed up the moment she heard her grandfather being mentioned. She couldn’t really read too much into Zhang Dong’s facial expression but from his tone, she could feel that something was off.

“I have to regretfully inform you that he hasn’t contacted me since we parted at the banquet…”

Zhang Dong informed her about the situation as he didn’t want to keep things hidden from the girl.

“I will have my sect members try to contact him and get more information. For the time being, you will have to remain here, I did promise to take care of you in your grandfather's stead and I’m going to stay true to that promise.”

Meili was glad that the man was sharing any type of information with her. It wasn’t anything good though. She had no proof if what he was telling was the truth but there wasn’t really a reason for him to lie. There wasn’t much she could offer him in return and he was already wasting valuable resources on her.

“Xue here will help you around the mansion and sect. You will receive an inner disciple emblem, for now, it will help you to get around the city.”

He explained a few things to her: this so-called emblem was something akin to a master key. She would be able to apparently also buy food and items with it in the city. She would also receive some other things like a communication device and even a personal bodyguard.

“Xue will explain everything to you in detail, I have to tend to some sect business so I will have to excuse myself. If word of your grandfather or sect reaches me I will be sure to send someone over to give you word.”

Meili remained quiet while the United Element Sect Leader continued to talk. It was very rude and unwise to interrupt someone like him. She wouldn’t have an option to ask any questions either as he left this Zhang Xue. He made a quick exit after the short explanation.

The door closed behind him and the two girls and two maids were left in the room. She was now left with the unknown beauty, not really sure what to do. She could tell that the other woman outranked her also in cultivation so she had to be respectful.

“Junior greets senior sister…”

She clasped her hands together and did a formal bow once more. The maids mimicked their young missy.

“You don’t need to be so formal dear cousin, just as Master said you are part of our family, first you should take this.”

Zhang Xue handed Fang Meili the shield looking emblem that was similar to the one the new disciples had gotten. It was one meant for inner disciples though and was a lot more intricate.

Meili noticed that this cousin of hers also possessed one of those. It was attached as an accessory to her robe. She also remembered seeing ones similar to it mostly worn on the shoulders of the other cultivators.

She also was surprised at how this Zhang Xue was referring to her senior uncle.

“Master?”

Zhang Xue chuckled while covering her face with her long sleeve.

“Yes it’s unconventional but my uncle is my Master. He is the most honorable person in this sect!”

The girl looked outside the window as if she was trying to proclaim to the world that Zhang Dong was the greatest master in the whole wide world.

“Master has urged me to give you a tour of this villa, we also need to visit the sect facilities and the city. There so much to see but so little time, we must depart dear cousin!”

Zhang Xue stopped reminiscing about her glorious master and turned to face Fang Meili. The city was huge and so was the entire sect. Giving this girl a tour of all that it could offer would probably take more than a day.

“Ah of course, I will abide by senior uncles and senior cousin’s wishes.”

Fang Meili was still feeling a bit stiff, this lady here was acting very welcoming but it wasn’t so for everyone else. There could be various reasons for it but the most important thing was for her to watch out.

Even though she had the sect leader’s protection she didn’t know how far this shield would go. Even this woman here could easily dispatch her for whatever reason. She needed to be careful and respectful.

Soon the two girls left the confines of the large guest room. The two girls set out to tour the sect compound. Their senior uncle on the other hand had a big choice to make.

Chapter 247

Zhang Dong left the two girls alone in the room and left. He was hoping that Zhang Xue would keep her safe and also show her around the sect. The two were around the same age with the blond girl being slightly younger.

He hoped that Zhang Xue would open up to her new cousin. He picked her as she was his disciple and he trusted her to follow his orders. He also couldn’t let Zhang Liu take the job, that disciple of his had a problem in the form of Liena’s sister to contend with.

Feng Nuana barricaded herself as his fiance and wasn’t allowing him to even interact with other women. He wasn’t sure why the younger sister was so different from the older one, but he was glad that he ended up with Liena that went by Zhang Liena nowadays.

In the old days, the women from the Feng Clan rarely changed their clan name and took in female children only. With the sect taking over now they were just regular disciples so their outlook on things had changed. Also after Liena married him she decided to change her family name to be more traditional. This caused some friction between the Feng Clan members that were afraid of losing power and prestige.

That’s why he was worried about his new niece a bit. He didn’t think anyone would do anything drastic knowing he was involved. There still were other family members in the sect that would probably see the new person as a threat.

The inner sect politics were a convoluted thing that he tried to avoid. Some people liked to make their own little factions and help them rise up to power. They wouldn’t be able to threaten his position as he was the strongest but in the lower sections of the sect, some infighting occurred.

Zhang Dong gave out a sight while flying away, he had other things to worry about than sect politics now. Time was of the essence and he would need to clear his schedule to resolve the new problems.

The first one was the problem that arose from him offending the Limitless Sword Society along with the Yggdrasil Sect. He slew Zhan Jie their Patriarch in one on one combat and this news was already known in all of the lands.

Normally if you killed a king from another country it would result in a war. In this sect-run empire, things were a bit different. The sect leader’s position was a high one but they could still be replaced. In most sects like the Limitless Sword Society, the decision-making process was more democratic than people might think.

Most of them had something like a council of elders in the background. They would be the ones to actually make the decisions. The sect leader was just a figurehead that decided on regular sect decrees. When it came to outside politics and diplomacy, such councils started getting involved.

This Limitless Sword Society council was probably in the midst of making a decision regarding this. There was a chance that they would take up arms and attack them. Something like that actually had a low probability of going through.

Like five years ago, it took three of the other sects banding together to take out the Dark Palm Sect. They also only attacked when Zhang Dong was keeping them busy. They only attacked after he killed a large number of their nascent soul elders.

He believed that if the other two sects refused to co-operate the Limitless Sword Society would have to take this hit to their face.

Zhang Dong already showed his hand by defeating two sect leaders in single combat. Both of them were late stage cultivators and masters at their own craft. He was also one of these masters that had learned the sword heart. This would also be something that the old nascent soul fogies would be afraid to go against.

There was also the Divine Fist Sect that was rumored to be backing him. He knew that it was impossible to place spies in his domain. Information about this not being true would probably never leak outside.

How this would play out depended on the Dragon Gate Sect and the Demon Subduing Sect. He had better relations with the sect leaders of those two sects. The one from the Dragon Gate one was actually interested in doing business with his sect.

He was even the one that held out an olive branch towards him by inviting his side to the banquet. Though Zhang Dong didn’t get to speak to Xu Qing, their leader at all. He was preoccupied with the Divine Fist Sect debacle and now it continued on.

“I gave Kuo the orders, maybe the spies had figured out something from the rumors…”

Zhang Dong took off into the distance while leaving Zhang Xue and Fang Meili to figure things out themselves.

After a moment or two, he arrived at a new location. He flew down into a large pagoda-like tower that stood in a walled-off section of the sect. No one besides core disciples was allowed here and it was also manned by them.

This was a building set up for his information network. This was the place to receive new intel on other factions and even individuals.

Every strong power required an agency like this. The other sects and factions still kept sending various spies into his domain. He just decided to return the favor and create a spy network of his own.

He left Zhang Kuo as its leader, the man was one of his most trusted advisors. He had long forgiven him about the Jade Grass City incident and the man continued working to prove his devotion towards him and the sect.

Thanks to him they had a mature information network throughout their whole domain. They even had sleeper agents placed inside the three surrounding sects.

Thanks to Zhang Dong’s improved disguising technique they were able to replace almost anyone they wanted. They were spies trying to infiltrate his sect all the time. It was easy to capture them and then to replace them with someone of his own people.

The great part about this technique was that it was easy to switch out their spies and even jump to a new persona if they ever got caught. The agents could even switch themselves out so that they wouldn’t need to live for years in a foreign land. Never to see their own sect members or families ever again.

Most of them were quite devoted though. There were many specialized techniques they were taught free of charge. A lot of people just took this job for the guaranteed rise in cultivation. Spending over ten years at an enemy camp was nothing for people that could live for five hundred years.

This place looked more like an office building on the inside. Many TV screens littered the inside along with cubicles. The sects technological advancement was pushed in the direction that he wanted.

Being an avid gamer and procrastinator in the old days he decided to bring over graphical interfaces that he was familiar with. For Matt, it was an easier way of sharing information than communication jades.

Those were still being used but it was easier to use a monitor screen with a presentation when more people were involved. Fast learning modules were possible as well but there could be some drawbacks as headaches.

“Greetings Patriarch.”

He nodded slightly at the guards greeting him. Without answering he moved over to Zhang Kuo’s private office. He mostly showed up without prior notice but normally if someone wanted to see Zhang Kuo who was the chief intelligence executive they needed to make an appointment. Depending on their rank it could take days or even weeks for it to come through.

“Any word from our friends from the Divine Fist Sect?”

Zhang Dong asked after entering Kuo’s office. It was spacious and the view from the windows was quite breathtaking.

The Intelligence executive was buried in paperwork that needed signing and approval. He had to read through a lot of reports that the spies sent periodically.

Zhang Dong could see Kuo standing up instantly from his large black leather chair. He looked like a CEO from a large company now and had a large luxurious office to show for it.

“We have received no news from the Divine Fist Sect. After you arrived we had our agents ask around in the other sects. Our information chain doesn’t yet reach that far, I must apologize Patriarch but we have no information regarding the elder you met at the banquet.”

Zhang Kuo continued with his explanation. The other sects are keeping the information concerning the Divine Fist Sect hidden. Kuo’s Spies only resided in the three major sects around them as well. They didn’t yet spread out into the other ones in the empire as this department of intelligence was still in its infancy.

The only thing they could go off was rumors and general knowledge. The Yggdrasil Sect had apparently moved their forces towards their borders but they were on standby.

“Are they feeling out the situation after the banquet incident?”

“That is probably so Patriarch, the death of Zhan Jie had also caused a couple of other incidents. Our spy reported that the diplomatic talks at the Limitless Sword Society are underway but for the time being it looks like they won’t be able to strike. The other two sects are taking a passive approach.”

This was good news for him. It was improbable that they would attack them if the other two big sects didn’t form a pact like last time.

“After Zhan Jie’s death the Limitless Sword Society's prestige is being questioned, some of the other factions are making moves in the background. Assassination attempts are probable, It’s unlikely that their council of grand elders will be willing to make a move against us without the help of the other sects.”

Zhang Kuo listed all the important things that the spy network could get but one question remained. What happened to Fang Heng, was he attacked while returning to his sect? Or was it possible that he managed to get back to his territory but still was unable to activate the teleportation beacon? It was also possible that this device was somehow damaged during his return as well.

“That is all Patriarch, I will send you the detailed report to your communication jade.”

“Good job, notify me if you get any information regarding the Divine Fist Sect, even second-hand information or rumors.”

Zhang Dong saw himself out after getting the quick report. His plan of teleporting to his destination would probably fall through. This left him with two options, either to wait for the beacon to be activated or go there himself.

He would need to travel there somehow while being unnoticed. The trip there wasn’t that long if he flew there at top speed but it wasn’t that easy. He would need to go through enemy territory. The other sects wouldn’t just let a powerful nascent soul cultivator into their lands that was also the sect leader of another faction.

He would probably need to go incognito as one of his personas. Lei Yinglo might have to make another appearance. This name was already known throughout the lands. He was viewed as a powerful rouge cultivator that liked to battle demonic beasts and cultivators.

Getting past the other sect borders could be possible as a hunter. If asked he could just tell that he was going after a ferocious demonic beast that was seen in Divine Fist Sect territory. He could also try sneaking there.

The biggest dilemma for him was leaving his newborn and wife behind. She hadn’t yet recovered but there wasn’t much time. If that monster continued to be left unchecked it could pose a threat to the entire empire or even the entire world.

“I’ll have to explain it to her…”

He flew back towards his mansion yet again. He needed to stock up on a few things and then convince his lovely wife that he wasn’t going into a death trap. He didn’t feel like lying to her would be a proper thing to do. He would rather disclose everything to her, breaking her trust was something that he wasn’t willing to do.

Chapter 248

“Cat hulu?”

“Cthulhu”

“Cthululu?”

“Cthulhu…”

“Cut-a-who?”

“Close but...you know what? it doesn’t even matter…”

Zhang Dong was in the room with his wife and his son. The boy was getting nursed by Zhang Liena right at this moment while his father was trying to explain to her about his favorite monster nemesis.

He had already explained the situation at the Divine Fist Sect and now just wanted to describe the monster that he needed to face.

“Does this really require your attention? Can’t we send Qiang instead, he loves things like that, he will be thrilled to face off against something that gave you trouble.”

He was worried about this, she wasn’t so keen on letting her husband go into unfamiliar lands to fight against some kind of occult monster. From her perspective, they could dispatch one or two nascent soul elders that they now had.

“We can even lend him Zhang Zhi, those two should be enough to handle a demonic beast.”

“Buaaahh…”

Their talk was interrupted by the sound of a baby. His son Zhang Jun was placed over his mother’s shoulder and performed a magnificent burp. After getting his mouth wiped he was carried over to the crib by one of the maids. She was part of the sect and a trusted member so the two could talk freely around her.

“I understand your point, but those two are a bit…”

“Foolish? Simple-minded? Dense?”

“You don’t hold back much my wife... I was thinking more in line with overzealous. Don’t think they were made for tasks requiring stealth. If we send them together we might as well just declare war on the other sects.”

Zhang Dong was afraid that those two would cause trouble. He could already see them picking fights with almost anyone they met along the way. Then if anyone even dared to speak ill about the United Element’s Sect Zhang Zhi would be the first one to pull out a sword and bisect them.

He was the poster boy for a fanatical sect member. Huo Qiang on the other hand just liked to fight. He would probably go out of his way to pick fights with other nascent soul masters if he just got the opportunity.

The sect leader here wanted to avoid things like this. His plan was to disguise himself as a wandering cultivator and travel through the territory of the other sects. He could pretend to be a core formation expert as traveling as a nascent soul master was dangerous. If someone wasn’t affiliated with a strong faction they could be seen as a large threat.

“Certainly that could happen…”

Liena frowned a bit while looking at her husband. He returned the gaze while furrowing his brows. He knew that look she was giving him, it was a look of anger with some concern.

“I wouldn’t be going if it wasn’t necessary, that monster can’t grow any further. I can always summon the elders if I get in trouble.”

Zhang Dong had a big ace up his sleeve. After upgrading his system he could summon some of his minions to his location. He didn’t even need to set up a teleportation gate. Depending on his follower's devotion towards him he could choose to bring them over to his location.

This function required spirit points, how many depended on the devotion rating and then the realm they were in. Summoning core formation cultivators cost less than doing it with nascent soul ones even if they had lower devotion.

“Can you summon me then?”

“You? Why would I ever do that? You should rest!”

Zhang Dong raised his voice slightly at the proposition. How could he call his recently pregnant wife over to battle a dangerous monster?

“Rest? I will be back on my feet within the week, don’t look down on Zhang Liena!”

He flinched a bit as he felt her aura spike. Her angered voice was raised and caused the windows in the room to vibrate. It also caused the baby to wake up and cry in the process, luckily the maid was quick to calm the little guy down.

“B-but think of the children...”

He scratched his head not really knowing what to say. He could see that his wife made up her mind, she also was wearing a teleportation ring and could transfer herself to his whereabouts. He could of course block this function but then he wouldn’t be able to get to her if anything happened either.

“I am thinking about them. I can’t have their father put himself in danger while I sit here doing nothing! The servants can tend to them!”
Zhang Liena looked at him with narrowed eyes. He didn’t know that she would react in this way but deep down he was glad that she cared. He knew that she should be recovered in about a week's time and this would also be the time he would need to reach the Divine Fist Sect area.

“I can just summon Qiang and Zhi, they will be more than eager to help…”

“Hah, I bet they will but you know well that I am the third strongest elder in this sect! With that little toy, you made me, I could even defeat that Idiot Qiang myself.”

Zhang Dong thought back to this toy that she was talking about. He did put in a lot of blood, sweat, and tears in making it. He had created that artifact to boost his wife's fighting prowess as she had to halt her cultivation process while taking care of his daughter.

Liena was making some sense but he still didn’t want his lovely wife to get involved in a brutal fight. He would probably need some help though, the last time he faced off against the monster it also had minions. This version had more time to prepare, it could have an actual army lurking in those ruins it was hiding in.

“But…”

“No buts, if you don’t make a promise now, I will just follow after you myself.”

Zhang Liena said while pouting slightly. She turned her head to the side as if being offended. He knew that she wanted the best for him and was just afraid that he could easily perish outside the sect.

‘Sigh’

He placed his hand on the woman’s head while shaking his own around.

“You know my wifey, you were a lot easier to convince in the old days.”

He thought back to the times that he could just bullshit his way around most of the arguments. After living with him for so many years his lovely wife had picked up on some of his lies or exaggerations. She knew that her husband wasn’t the monolithic giant sect leader that everyone thought he was. He made mistakes like anyone else, she was just worried.

“I promise to seek your aid when I get into trouble, but you must also promise me that you won’t overwork yourself.”

He went down to his knees as his wife was sitting on an exquisite white couch. She was in the middle of pouting and looking to the side. He grabbed her soft hand with his own and delivered a small peck to it. Liena gave out a small blush and looked down. Even though she had gotten more daring with the years she was still quite weak when he showed her some affection.

“Hmph!”
She gave out a cute sound unfit for a lady her age. Zhang Dong just smiled and moved his hands around his wife. He carried her over to the bed that had a better healing formation around it.

“I’ll be taking my leave now. Take care of the little ones and try to save your strength. I’ll keep you informed in the usual way.”

The two finally parted with each other and he walked out of Liena’s room. He checked on the beacon one last time before placing it back into his spatial ring.

Zhang Dong then promptly disappeared from within the sect grounds a couple of minutes later an older looking man in a dark robe could be seen flying through the air. He looked grizzled and had many scars on his face. He decided to go with his old demon hunter persona for this mission, he used it from time to time to fight off demon beasts when he got bored.

He used a blade to fly on but his speed was several times faster than of a regular core formation expert’s. While in his own sect region he could just use his full cultivation to propel himself forward. When he reached enemy territory he would need to slow down.

If other nascent soul experts felt an unfamiliar aura of similar strength they would surely fly towards it. He needed to take his time in passing through unknown lands. The other sects didn’t see core formation cultivators as big threats so if he paid the toll he should be able to pass through their cities and borders.

‘Haven’t done this in a while… feels refreshing to spread my wings from time to time.’

He looked at the passing scenery that was quite beautiful. This world was a lot more fascinating than the previous one he lived in. People tended to flock to larger cities as many violent beasts roamed the lands. Thanks to this, nature was mostly undamaged, things like air pollution and waste products were rarely seen.

As a sect leader, he couldn’t leave the premises of his main sect city. His adventuring days had been halted and he concentrated on his people. He had helped them design the city and also used his personal funds to raise the living conditions of his citizens.

His policies were seen as very magnanimous and the people living in these lands were very thankful. He had placed police units across all the major cities in the area, even where other large clans resided. Thanks to this, the order was being kept and fewer people died due to things like greed and face.

There was still much to do but it was impossible for his hands to reach everywhere. Even as he was flying through some of his lands he could see impoverished people. This mostly happened in poor villages or tribes, his sect just didn’t have the capital to take care of everyone.

The only thing he could give them was the possibility of improving their lives. It was up to them to take control of their life and rise up. He was also of the mind that he couldn’t make everyone over-reliant on the sect. They needed to be able to take care of themselves otherwise it would spell disaster if a calamity arrived.

He sped through the forests, it was the same one that he had arrived into this world. It spread through much of the lands and was unused due to the low amount of spiritual energy.

Thanks to this the large sects didn’t bother to expand their borders here. If he used this path he would be able to keep his maximum speed up for a bit longer. Without any distractions, he passed through most of his lands. He arrived close to the border, this one was with the Limitless Sword Society.

This was the fastest way towards his new destination but would also be dangerous. He would certainly be attacked if they discovered his true identity.

“Time to sneak in…”

He covered himself in spiritual energy and dived down. The moment he approached the ground it parted. He tunneled himself down while spreading the ground with earth elemental techniques, his aim was to burrow himself out on the other side of the border. He purposely picked a spot that was far away from any nascent soul cultivators.

“I must hurry, that monster might be slaughtering that sect even at this moment. Can’t let that thing’s corruption spread outside…”

Chapter 249

“Run away Little Su and take your mother with you!”

A bald man shouted while holding a large saber in one of his hands. There was an arrow sticking out of his shoulder yet he was standing tall.

“No, father!”

He was standing in front of two women, one looked to be his wife while the other one was much younger, probably his daughter. He was staring at a group of people in shabby clothes. They had weapons in their hands and were slowly surrounding this family of three from all sides.

“Not so fast old man, those two are precious goods, we can’t have them running off! Get them, boys!”

“Yes, senior brother!”

It looked like a group of small-time ruffians, there were five of them with the largest man being the leader. Due to the woman’s hesitation, their escape route was cut off and it looked like it would be over for this small family of three.

“Don’t blame us, blame yourself for coming to this place, fool!”

One of the men laughed while swinging his sword at the father. The man managed to receive the strike and even push the attack back. To his dismay, he wasn’t able to react to the second bandit who managed to stab his unkempt blade into the father’s side, blood was seen instantly.

“No! Father!”

“Honey!”

The two females screamed out as they saw the father fall to one of his knees. He used the saber as a crutch to support himself but his vision started getting blurry.

“Leave my wife and daughter alone, you bastards!”

Two of the bandits quickly grabbed the unprepared girls and held them by their hands. They had to watch their family member getting his weapon taken away with a well-placed kick. It looked like it was over and that the criminals were on top.

“Hah, serves you right. Only an idiot takes their family through these lands, what were you trying to achieve, idiot?”

The bandit leader chucked menacingly while his men started pulling the two women away. The father tried to get up but another bandit instantly kicked him in the stomach.

“Let me go you bastard!”

The daughter cried out while biting the man on the hand that was holding her. This caused him to lose his grip, the girl tried using this chance to pull away but got held back by her hair.

“Damn slut!”

The angered man yanked her back and delivered a hard slap to her face. This caused her to groan out in pain while falling down to the ground.

“Hey be careful, don’t damage her face, we won’t be able to sell her like this.”

The leader barked out at the other man that shrunk back.

“You can have some fun with that old hag, this one belongs to me.”

The boss smirked while looking at the younger girl. He could see shock and indignation in her eyes. He was the type of man that loved to see the fear in his victim’s eyes. He licked his lips while moving closer.

The only person that could do anything was getting stomped by his junior brothers, he on the other hand was planning to enjoy this young girl to the fullest.

“Don’t worry, this senior brother is really gentle. I’ll teach you how a real man does things!”

He laughed while doing an obscene hip thrust, the young girl could only look with shock as the ugly bandit got closer. Her mother flailed around but she was far too weak to do anything, the father was already close to dying.

In her heart, she prayed for a miracle. This wasn’t how it was supposed to be, her whole family wanted to leave this godforsaken land. They were so close, only a few more days and they would have been on the border at the promised land.

This land was supposed to be ruled by a just leader. Someone that actually cared about his subjects. There was enough food for everyone, the streets were clean and his forces patrolled the areas which kept bandits like these away.

In the time of her despair, something happened, there was a rumble. The earth started shaking as if a large earthquake was upon them. The bandit leader almost fell over as even he was affected by the earth’s movement.

“What is that? an earthquake?... no… something is coming…”

The man looked to the side and could see the ground rising up about fifty meters from where he was standing. It burst open quite fast and he could see a man rising out from it. The man flew up into the air but there was not a speck of dirt on his dark robe.

The bandit leader dropped whatever he was doing as he knew that someone like this was far above him. The way that he was staying in the sky without a worry in the world showed that he was a master at the core formation level. This was someone that he could not offend.

………………………………………………….

This man was Zhang Dong, he had just reached the border that his sect and the Limitless Sword Society shared with one another. He had submerged himself underground and used his system map to evade detection. He didn’t really have to do this but he wanted to be sure that no stray sentries detected his presence.

After traveling several kilometers from the initial entry point he finally decided to go outside. Traveling underground was a lot slower than flying through the air even though it was safer.
When he got outside he saw quite the scene, a standard robbery with attempted murder and rape.

“Is this some kind of new world record?”

He thought back to his old days when he used to fly around without any worry. He always came across people getting mugged and robbed whenever he went. He attributed it to the world just being really bloody where only the strongest survived. This was also the reason why he created his version of the police force so that he could let them handle it.

So here he was, just starting his week-long adventure and already witnessing a crime in progress. He looked down with narrowed eyes at the bandits that had clearly noticed him. He saw them on his system map, but they were at the lower end of Qi condensation so he deemed them harmless.

They were clearly too weak to be members of the Limitless Sword Society. Thus he decided to come out here as he was losing too much time tunneling as it was.

He couldn’t let this go on for any longer. He could tell that one of the people that got attacked was critically injured. He started to descend towards the group of Qi Condensation cultivators, it was a rare occurrence for him to interact with weak people like them. He could already see the bandits shaking from feeling his suppressed aura.

“G-good day H-honorable Elder, can this lowly junior be of assistance?”

Zhang Dong saw the person with the highest cultivation level going straight down to his knees. He wanted to commend his quick wits, he instantly assumed the subservient position. He was only at the 5th level of Qi condensation but outranked everyone here besides him.

“Just be quiet.”

Zhang Dong didn’t really feel like he needed to talk to this man. He already came across many idiots like this. They used the small amount of power to walk all over weaker people but when someone slightly stronger appeared they fled or prostrated themselves instantly.

It was debatable why they ended up like this. Was it bad parenting, maybe lack of them? Did they see someone else living their life like this and just copied their ways?

Zhang Dong didn’t feel like people were born evil or that they weren’t redeemable. Correcting their behavior would be exceedingly difficult and there was a point of no return. He would never be merciful to people that killed without rhyme or reason.

He reached out his hand and pointed out with his finger. This digit started glowing with a golden hue. A tiny ray of light shot out from it and flew towards the collapsed man. The golden energy seeped into his body while making it glow radiantly.

Everyone here was staying quiet, they weren’t sure what this master was doing to this man. They knew one thing, that if he wanted he could slay them with a tiny fart. To their surprise, the man that was on death’s door started looking better. In a matter of moments, all of his wounds closed up and he opened up his eyes.

He was now healed. The man looked around confused as he had lost consciousness after getting severely beaten by the bandits. The last thing he remembered was trying to save his daughter and wife before the stomping began.

“W-what?”

“F-father!”

The daughter was the first one to react. She was still young and emotional, while the others were scared of moving while a core formation expert was around, she didn’t. She hugged her father while sobbing as he had almost passed away.

“Well then, I don’t have much time. Now Choose, a life of servitude or death? Ten seconds should be enough to make a decision.”

The moment Zhang Dong spoke out a massive amount of killing intent washed over all of the bandits. They were pushed into the ground and could only shake with fear. They knew that this man was serious, the reason he was doing this was unimportant as he was someone far above them.

In their minds, they could only blame themselves for being too weak to retaliate. There was not much remorse in their thinking as it didn’t even dawn on them that he was punishing them for the attempted murder and rape.

“I… I will swear allegiance to the venerable senior!

“M-me too.”

“Yes, we all swear to serve you!”

Not having much choice they all crumbled under pressure. The moment they agreed to the proposal they could feel something invading their very being. It was some kind of soul shackle being placed upon them and they had heard rumors about such things. If the man wished he could easily destroy their souls.

“Now you three on the other hand…”

Zhang Dong in his demon hunter persona looked at the family of three. It was strange that they were here, how did they end up in the middle of nowhere with bandits? The closest settlement was a few days away on foot for normal people and it seemed that is what they did.

“Honorable senior, please spare my family, I will also swear my life to you!”

“F-father!”

The man also went down to his knees and started begging him for his life. The wife was closely second as she also begged for their daughter’s life. It made it seem like he was some kind of evil cultivator trying to use them as some kind of test subjects or resources for pill making.

“Relax…”

He pointed his finger at the group of three. They could feel something being inserted into their dantian, it was some kind of strange energy but it didn’t feel malicious.

“I’m not going to harm you. I have given you control of these idiots here, you can do whatever you wish with them. If they try to hurt you, their very souls will rapture and break.”

He quickly explained that these five bandits would be bound to them. He on the other hand started floating up into the sky. He didn’t have time to escort these people, with these five bandits they should be fine in this low-level area.

“You there, give them an order.”

He pointed to the daughter that flinched a bit. She complied with the request telling the bandits to stand up on one leg.

“Uh?”

The men found themselves compelled to do it. If they tried resisting a sharp pain would wash over their bodies rendering them immobile.

“Well then, take care and try not to get in trouble…”

He finally took off while looking at his map. He had already placed waypoints on it after looking through the map of the empire. He would go through less populated spots evading large cities and heavily guarded locations. If he was lucky, he would arrive in the Divine Fist Sect territory within a week.

The family of three was left baffled by the occurrence. Even after the man left the bandits found themselves under their spell. It was now on them to decide if these criminals deserved to live or die.

Chapter 250

Zhang Dong left the bewildered family along with the small group of bandits. He chuckled to himself as they all had silly expressions on their faces. Probably because they were all still alive after coming across someone of his caliber.

He didn’t have time to stick around and help out anymore. The reason for them being in this desolate spot was unknown to him and he would keep it that way.

Zhang Dong whizzed on his flying sword through the lands while keeping a low profile. He looked like your generic rugged cultivator with no home. The sword he was using looked shabby from the outside.

This was done on purpose to evade conflict with any other core formation cultivators. If he wore multiple high-level trinkets he could as well just write ‘Rob me’ on his back and wait.

‘I seem to have forgotten how the world really looks outside my own sect…’

While flying as fast as a jet plane he had some time to look around these lands. He was now in Limitless Sword Society territory. He could see the usual low-level beasts roaming the lands which weren’t anything out of the ordinary. But when he approached human settlements he noticed the disparity.

His plan was to evade them but with his nascent soul senses, he could peek at these smaller cities from afar. He did all of this without the worry of getting detected. What he saw there painted a picture of how the other sects saw their people or rather how they didn’t see anyone besides their own worth investing in.

There was widespread famine and lawlessness. He could see ruffians and robbers roaming everywhere, maybe this was why that family was there. They might have been trying to escape from all of this.

The cities here were more akin to his territory before his sect took over. Even in the first large city, he visited all those years ago things weren’t great. He almost saw people getting run over by a carriage. He was able to save them then, but this was only possible because of his high cultivation realm.

He was saddened by how people had to live here but he couldn’t help them. He needed to finish his mission first. If he wasn’t successful, bandits and robbers would be the least of their problems.

So Zhang Dong looked into the distance and flew off, this time around he used various aura hiding treasures along with ones that would make him hard to detect or even see.

It was thanks to having these with him that he was certain of continuing his journey forward without being detected.

This world was truly vast, even though he was limiting his speed he would be able to make a round trip around his old planet in less than a day. Even with that kind of speed, he would need a whole week to get to his destination.

Out of boredom, he started looking around. The weather kept changing one hour he could be going through snowy mountain peaks where there was nothing besides frozen ice and death. While in the next he was whizzing through tropical weather in a jungle area. He felt like he was stuck in a game and going through different biomes each time.

In reality, he was traveling through a vast expanse. Along with the spiritual energy changes that could alter the surroundings it all made sense. Many times did he want to stop and take in the scenery while relaxing. The forests and untouched lakes were truly breathtaking. Places like this just made him want to take his family and relax while taking a dip in one of the many giant lakes.

Regretfully most of such beautiful places remained untouched for a reason. Even now as he was passing through a clear lake he could see a massive shadow lurking below. If he lowered his altitude he would probably get attacked by the monster living in the deep below.

Human cultivators might have been strong but they were far from the strongest beings in these lands. Magical beasts were born stronger yet humans had more ingenuity to go further in their life. They were also much better at working in a group while beasts kept to themselves or at most stayed in small groups with an alpha ruling over them.

Zhang Dong made sure to activate his system map while going through these lands. He didn’t have any luck in finding any of those strange dead zones. He wanted to get another of those cubes which could get him some information about the person who sent him here.

He still had many unanswered questions that needed to be asked. For some reason though, he had a bad premonition about the person behind it all. Everything was shrouded in mystery, there was also that secret ground. It was located in the Limitless Sword Society area which they poached from the Dark Palm Sect.

He was contemplating about taking this part of the land back into his territory, now after defeating their leader there was no reason not to be a bit brazen.

‘I should probably look into it after I take care of Squidward, one thing at a time…’

He gave out a sigh while continuing with his journey. He passed the Limitless Sword Society area without many incidents. Along the way, he helped out a few people that were down on their luck. He did it with minimal effort, time was still of the essence.

One day passed and then another one. Soon he was deep into the empire and far away from home. He periodically sent some long-ranged messages to his wife thanks to his faction system. Communication jades and other devices didn’t have enough range for things like this.

Even with it, there was a slight time delay between his direct messages. When using the system for communication it would look like a conversation through the internet. Both parties would see text popping up in front of them. He was limited to people that had their devotion above 90% for this which was only a handful. His wife was luckily one of them.

‘I’m approaching the Divine Fist Sect territory, for now, I haven’t encountered anything out of the ordinary.’

He pressed send and could see an indication that his wife had received the information. Regretfully there was a downside to this way of talking. The person receiving the DM couldn’t respond normally. They had a limited array of emojis that they could click. They had thirty seconds to reply to his text.

‘Thumbs up followed by a kissy face emoji, then a lot of heart emojis…’

Liena wasn’t very good with picking out those and he very rarely used this system to contact anyone. Thus he sometimes had trouble understanding what his lovely wife wanted to say to him. This time there were a lot of hearts so everything must have been going well back home.

‘There is still no reaction from the beacon even when I am this close…’

He grumbled while flying forward. He was lucky enough in evading any other nascent soul cultivators and was now only a few hours away from his destination. He hoped that he would figure out what happened to his new niece’s grandfather after he got there.

Zhang Dong looked at his map and compared it to the map of the Azure Dragon Empire that he had in his possession. He was sure that he was in the right place, after getting through the mountain range that was in front of him he should be able to see the border walls.

‘What is that?’

On the other side, he was forced to slow down. What he saw was peculiar. He could clearly see the fifty-meter large walls that continued for kilometers. This was a standard for keeping territories separate and wasn’t the surprising thing that he saw.

‘That’s a lot of fog…’

Mist, white and thick. It was everywhere it was spilling over the walls even now and inching forward into this land bit by bit. Even with his enhanced senses, he couldn’t see inside of this strange fog. He could feel small amounts of demonic qi coming off from it, he had a sinking suspicion that it was related to his favorite monster.

He examined everything from a safe distance, he wasn’t alone here. He had discovered other cultivators keeping watch and they were not from the Divine Fist Sect. They were surprisingly from the Silver Spear Sect that he had beat up the leader off. This sect was one of the ones that bordered with the faction he was going towards.

They were mostly core formation and foundation establishment cultivators. These walls stretched for many kilometers in two directions, the nascent soul elder responsible for them would probably be somewhere in the middle of the border. He purposely moved to a spot where he could evade such an elder.

‘If it’s just them…’

He waved his hand around while his body rippled. His form faded out of existence as he blended with the surroundings. This was one of the new techniques that he had learned. It was a good technique for espionage as it rendered you invisible to people below your cultivation realm.

Zhang Dong floated gently towards the walls, using too much spiritual energy could give his position away. He remained standing in the air right before this strange white mist. All of his senses were telling him to not go in there. It was as if something in there was going to devour him whole.

It was too late to turn back though but before entering he turned to the side. There were some other cultivators floating on their swords. Before going in he decided to eavesdrop on their conversation. Maybe they would shed some light on it all, he was quite lucky as one of the junior members was just making a report to the commanding elder.

“Senior Elder, the evil fog is slowly progressing into our sect. No information is going through inside and the Divine Fist Sect isn’t responding either… our scouts haven’t returned either…”

He got the gist of it while listening to the report. It didn’t answer any questions but he had a suspicion about how this strange fog worked. Luckily he was the right person for this job, maybe the only right person for it.

‘I’m glad that I went with gold and not violet that time…’

He smirked while finally deciding to get in there. His body blurred for a moment and the white mist parted for a second as he dived in. The elder from the Silver Spear sect turned around to the spot that Zhang Dong dived in.

“Was it my imagination?”

“Elder?”

The man turned his head back to the junior member while nodding.

“Right, keep monitoring and await for our scouts to return. Keep your distance from this evil mist, I fear that it’s the work of demonic cultivators. I will bring this information to the sect, we must have one of the grand elder’s act!.”

“Understood elder!”

No one here would go out of their way to investigate further. Most of the people were convinced that this fog was poisonous or might affect someone’s mind. It was time to inform the higher-ups and have them act while they observed from outside.

It was progressing slowly and was keeping away from their side of the border so they didn’t have a reason to act just yet. They still hoped that the Divine Fist Sect would take care of this problem as it was coming from their lands.

Unbeknownst to them, a certain person was already inside. His appearance started to shift into a handsome man with white hair and a robe of the same color. His eyes glowed with golden light and his body was covered with the same type of holy energy.

‘I hope that I’m not too late…’

A note from Kuropon

Well, Happy New Year Guys~

Chapter 251

He was finally at his destination, how it looked was a lot different than he had expected. When using his own eyes he could hardly see anything past ten meters in a circle around him. He had placed his flying sword back into his spatial ring by now and was just floating close to ground level.

“It’s really quiet… too quiet… where are all the animals?”

He wasn’t far away from the border wall now. He was expecting to get to the bottom of this but he couldn’t see any bodies to tell him their tale. He did see some claw marks on the border wall and they weren’t that old.

“Maybe I’ll find something further in…”

This was still far away from the main Divine Fist Sect location. He used his system map to place a waypoint marker. He placed it on the location where Fang Heng was supposed to be. He was still surprised that there was no word from him whatsoever, it was odd but there could be one reason for it.

Before continuing further he decided to stop and land. He stretched out his hand while opening up his palm. He used some spiritual energy to slowly suck the mist towards his palm. He started condensing it together while gathering the fog up in a more solid form. He only stopped after getting about a marble-sized item, what he was left with was a cloudy dark gem that radiated strange energy.

He looked over it and could feel a peculiar demonic like aura coming off it. He gave it a little poke with his finger but nothing seemed to happen. The second test was similar but this time around he dispersed the holy energies from his aura that were protecting his finger.

There was a response. The moment his skin made contact with the concentrated mist he could feel his energies being drained. He quickly defended himself against them by reapplying his holy aura.

“It’s draining my vital energies… but that’s not all…”

He took out a teleportation beacon from his spatial ring. This one wasn’t the same that he gave Fang Heng, it connected back to the United Element Sect’s teleportation gate. He tried activating it but for some reason, it wasn’t working. Something was blocking out the signal from going through entirely.

“So it’s because of this mist…”

Zhang Dong had his answer to why he couldn’t get in touch with the Divine Fist Sect elder. This fog was blocking out the signal.

He grasped the condensed fog with his hand and crushed it. The moment it made contact with his holy elemental energy it just crumbled into nothing.

He followed it up with another burst of his golden aura, this time he backed it by a lot more of his cultivation base. The bright energies spread through the area reaching about 100 meters in diameter. The mist was forced back or more likely the energies were destroyed due to the holy elementals.

The moment the area was cleared up he looked back to his teleportation beacon. With the fog slightly dissipated he couldn’t feel a connection going through. He decided to fly up while dispersing the fog some more. With enough altitude, a signal started to finally go through.

It was too early to summon help for now but he used this chance to send his wife a quick message that he was inside.

Getting more people in here would be troublesome now. This mist was robbing people of their vital energies, he was only fine due to his unique cultivation method. No one from the nascent soul elders had a holy element to their cultivation method. They might be susceptible to this mist if they stayed too long in it. There were ways to help them out with it, but they would need to prepare some contingencies.

‘I should probably wait.’

Zhang Dong decided to wait for now. He didn’t need backup just yet and if he summoned help now the nascent soul elders in question could run out of spiritual energy. If that happened before they actually fought the monster and its minions it would be disastrous.

He floated back up and inspected the mist free area. The residual divine energy seemed to be keeping the fog back for now but he could feel it slowly closing in.

‘This sect practices divine arts, they should have some kind of defensive formation utilizing it…’

He believed that these cultivators were still alive. The reason that the teleportation beacon wasn’t working was because of this mist. Even with a protective formation in place, the signal wasn’t still reaching him. This meant that the fog was probably still covering it from the top. If it was a dome-shaped barrier it all made sense.

The ground shook as he jumped upwards and headed inside of the Divine Sect Territory. He spread out his senses in all directions while examining the situation. There could have been survivors out here that could answer some questions.

He traveled further in, the mist continued to get thicker but he was unaffected by it. It looked more like it was trying to evade him instead.

After some time he finally came across a living being. It wasn’t a human though but a beast, after further examining it he noticed something.

Frenzied Axe Beak [ Qi Condensation 5th stage ]

It was a bird-like beast. It looked similar to an ostrich with sharp taloned feet and a wedge-shaped beak. The most interesting part of the name was the prefix, the monster was in a frenzied state. This brought him back to the past when he first came across monsters like this.

‘It’s the same as that time…’

He spread out his senses into the surroundings and also glanced at his map while flying forward. There were more animals in the area and they were just wandering around without a purpose.

All of them had similar statuses after examination, it was clear that his favorite squid faced monster was involved. Just like in the past the monster was gathering other living beings and gaining strength. This mist that was all around the land was probably another step in its evolution.

‘The more of these it absorbs the stronger it will become, I must hurry…’

He needed to get to that city as fast as he could. He had no idea where those ruins were exactly and even with his speed it would probably take him days or even weeks to pinpoint the location on his own.

Zhang Dong took off into the air, flying high above the clouds and even getting above the mist. Everywhere he looked it was covered in white, it was as if a giant thick cloud was placed on the ground like a large white fuzzy blanket.

His plan was to continue right towards his destination, getting the Divine Fist Sect’s input and someone to guide him towards the ruins where the monster slumbered. Before that could happen though he finally came across his first human survivors.

They looked like regular people, they weren’t wearing any sect robes which probably meant that they were just commoners. Normally a person in Zhang Dong’s situation would see the bigger picture and leave them to their own fate. He would be wasting time and spiritual energy in helping here.

He wasn’t your usual senior though. He knew well that his emotions always got the better of him which caused a lot of trouble to him and the people he wanted to protect. But this was just how he was, if he saw someone in need and he was able to do something about it, he would.

The people he was looking at were a group of five. It looked like a family with two kids and a grandparent. The father was in front of them getting attacked by those frenzied birds he saw earlier. They all were weak cultivators at the Qi condensation level and the beast outnumbered them three to one. If he didn’t aid them, death or corruption was awaiting them.

He could see that they were wearing masks over their faces probably in hopes of not getting affected by this mist. They were still on their feet so these masks had to be working to some extent. He could also detect faint divine energy coming off from those, there was more to them that met the eye.

Zhang Dong finally sprung to action, doing it just in time. The man that was protecting the women and children was about to get clawed and pecked to death by those fearsome birds.

He was much stronger than those beasts, with a wave of his hand he just made them stop in their tracks entirely. It was as if time had stopped for everyone here. His golden energies dispersed the white mist from the area letting the folks here breathe in relief.

The people could barely speak as they saw their family member that was almost killed float up into the air. His wounds were healing themselves on their own in real-time. He was then dropped to his feet right in front of his wife by Zhang Dong.

He turned around to the immobile monsters and with a tiny motion of his finger made them explode into nothingness. They were all safe but he could see the fear in their eyes. The monster birds were replaced with an unknown cultivator that was many times stronger than anything here.

“Don’t worry I’m not going to hurt you, I just wanted to ask you, good people, a few questions.”

He spoke up first without waiting for them to reply. There were a few things he wanted to ask about before going any further.

“Y-yes senior! Whatever you wish! If there is anything this junior could do to repay this favor he will!”

The father started bowing instantly and his family members followed suit. He already felt stiffened by the tone they were addressing him with but this was just how people treated scary nascent soul elders like him, with unshaken respect.

“Relax, I’m here to help. Can you tell me when this mist started to appear and how are you resisting its effects with those masks…”

“The mist…”

The man gave out a sigh and stood up straight while looking out into the distance. He could notice that this elder in front of him was something special. He was even keeping this fog at bay with his cultivation.

“Great senior it happened about a week ago, it appeared out of nowhere in our cities and started to slowly sap our energies away….”

The man gave Zhang Dong the recap. The fog appeared unannounced and invaded their lands, at first they didn’t make much of it. They thought that it was only the weather playing tricks on them. Soon they discovered that it wasn’t the truth and they were slowly getting their spiritual energy sucked away.

The more energy they lost the thicker this mist became. Somehow this mist was growing while draining these people of their energies. After a few days, frenzied beast attacks started happening and the village these five lived in was overrun.

“And the masks? I can feel faint divine energies coming from it…”

Zhang Dong asked while the man looked back at his family. His wife gave him a nod and he finally removed his mask. On the mask, Zhang Dong could spot a flower petal, not really large but it was giving off a holy light.

“It’s a special flower that grows in these lands, it is able to slightly filter the air. With it we can move through the mist but not for too long…”

Zhang Dong identified the petal the moment he saw it. It was a type of spiritual sunflower growing in this world, this did explain how they were able to move through it without passing out.

He rubbed his chin in thought but before he could ask another question one of the children dropped down to her knees and started shouting out.

“Please save us senior!”

The young girl started sobbing while her family members tried to make her stop. From their perspective this elder here had done enough already, asking for more would be shameful. It could also get them all in trouble.

‘I was afraid that this would happen…’

He looked at the girl that was about the age of twelve, her face covered in snot and tiers.

Chapter 252

Zhang Dong was criminally susceptible to the cries of women, even worse if it were children involved. This all due to him becoming a father himself. It would be more reasonable to leave these people here and continue towards the main location of the Divine Fist Sect.

He might lose a lot of time if he started helping everyone along the way. The problem was that it could cost people's lives. Even now if he didn’t intervene here five lives would have been extinguished. If he let something like this happen when being in close range of helping here, he would hate himself later on.

This was something that he had started and now he needed to see it through to the end. In his head, he now was responsible for these five people. He would need to see it through to the end, he would also be able to gain some more information after checking out their village.

“Is it here?”

“Y-yes great senior, just a bit further.”

The family head said while looking down. The five of the people that Zhang Dong saved were surrounded by a bubble of golden energy. They were flying through the air at astonishing speeds. They were quite baffled by this display of might as they had never seen a cultivator of his caliber before.

Zhang Dong had asked about their circumstances. The five had escaped from the village together after some frenzied beasts attacked it. The people in it took out quite a bit but they were overrun by the constant beast tide.

They believed that there still were people there as their village grew out of those special sunflowers. The fog wasn’t able to penetrate past those fields and some people supposedly fled towards them.

“You were speaking the truth, I can sense some people in that direction…”

He arrived at the spot where the village was and could see widespread destruction. The buildings were mostly made from wood which didn’t pose much of a problem for the enraged beasts. With the cultivation boosts, they were getting from the frenzied state it was even easier.

He could feel a large gathering of people in one particular building. The house wasn’t big but there were at least 30 people in it. Outside of it, there was a field with those sunflowers. These spiritual plants were giving off a faint divine aura, even this was apparently enough to force the mist away.

‘The mist isn’t penetrating further… no wait… it is moving slightly…’

With the help of his enhanced senses, he could tell that fog was inching further in. It was in millimeters but it was advancing. Probably in a couple of days, it would seep all the way into the field. He could also tell that the plants were slowly dying, they were not enough to combat this demonic miasma.

He pointed his finger down from the air while concentrating. The people from the side looked with interest as an electrical discharge was visible at his digit’s tip.

Soon a bolt of golden lightning shot out. It traveled with immense speed and connected with one of the beasts below. The monster exploded into dust the moment the bolt of lightning made contact with it.

The lightning didn’t just stop there, no it traveled on to the next creature closest to it. In a matter of moments the lightning starter arcing from monster to monster taking out each one in the vicinity of the village.

“Incredible…”

“Such might…”

The family of Qi Condensation cultivators couldn’t believe what they were seeing. The mass of monsters that had caused them so much trouble was dead in a couple of seconds. This master had taken them out with just one attack. It seemed as easy as breathing to him, truly unfathomable might.

“That’s all of them.”

He nodded while the people behind him had their jaws down. While they were coming to terms with his show of strength, he decided to land on that field of sunflowers. The people in the farmhouse peeked out and could tell that a master had come. One of them moved outside while the rest remained inside.

“Honorable Senior have you arrived to aid us?”

He clasped his hands while looking past Zhang Dong and clearly saw the family of five that he knew.

“Something like that, I don’t have much time. I will get to the bottom of this but for now, you will have to stay here and wait.”

Zhang Dong spoke out while the old man moved his head down, he looked a bit saddened after hearing what he had to say. He probably hoped that this mysterious elder would somehow aid them in this time of need.

“Don’t worry, you will be safe here...just wait a moment…”

He flew up into the sky and pointed both of his hands down while having his index fingers extended. His hands started moving at an astonishing speed, the people below could only see them blurring around. No one was sure what he was doing but not like they were brave enough to speak up.
He was drawing lines into the earth below, strange symbols were being placed around the farm. He was drawing a formation while using the divine sunflower plants as a power source. After a moment it was all finished the formation sprung into action and pushed the mist away even further.

The village that was covered by the thick miasma was being slowly washed clean from it. Zhang Dong flew down, he took out a pill from his spatial ring and threw it at the sunflower field. He made a crushing motion with his fist which made the pill explode into many small particles. These seeped into the ground and nourished it, in a matter of seconds the plants grew twice in size while radiating, even more, divine power.

“T-this is…”

“I have placed a defensive formation around your village, it will use this field as the core. The demonic miasma won’t seep into it for the time being and the weaker demons will stay away.”

The village people would be safe against the mist and probably most of the monsters lurking outside. With the nourishing pill that he inserted into the soil, the sunflowers should last for a couple of weeks. He thought that he would have things resolved by that time.

“Well, then I must be on my way.”

He was about to go. He felt like he had done enough and the people here would be safe enough with this defensive formation. Before he could leave though, one of the villagers called out with tears in their eyes.

“Please wait senior!”

It was a young man in his twenties, his cultivation was a bit higher than the rest of the people here. The others looked at him with surprise, probably still afraid of Zhang Dong’s motives but at this point, they were willing to put their trust in him. With that they let the man speak without being frightened that Zhang Dong would take it as being rude.

“M-my wife… she has been affected by the strange fog there are also others…”

“Affected by the fog?”

He looked to the farmhouse with narrowed eyes. He had felt for life signatures but didn’t really go into it further. He inspected the insides once more but this time doing a more thorough search.

“This is…”

They were humans in there but he could feel something else, something was hiding inside of them. It was giving off a strange aura very similar to the frenzied monsters outside.

“Bring them all outside!”

He gave out the order while the villagers nodded and scrambled inside the house to bring out the affected people. The people started being brought outside, he could tell by one look that something was wrong. For one thing, they were all tied up and their mouths were even gagged.

There were four people affected, after peeking at their status with his system he could clearly see that they all had the ‘frenzied’ status. Without wasting much time he waved his hand to bring one of the bound people over.

It was the wife of the man that brought his attention to them. He didn’t remove the bindings for now while he started the examination. The people saw him walking around the floating woman while sometimes poking her body with his index finger.

“Hm… interesting…”

Zhang Dong had done extensive research in healing. It had been five years since the war was over so he had ample time. It wouldn’t be a stretch to consider him one of the best healers in the whole empire. Along with his extensive book knowledge, he had a high cultivation realm. Having a doctor or a healer reach his stage was truly rare.

“I see what the problem is… Okay everyone please stand back.”

Everyone backed away as he ordered, the only one that wasn’t going back that far was the woman’s husband. He could understand the sentiment so he didn’t say anything about it.

With a flick of a wrist, multiple silver needles shot out from his spatial ring. With another flic, the bindings were removed along with the gag. The moment that came off the woman’s maddened incoherent screams could be heard.

The people gasped slightly worried that the woman would attack someone. She wasn’t able to move though, even though the ropes were gone her whole body couldn’t move. Zhang Dong was keeping her in check with his immense spiritual energy.

The silver needles flew forward guided by him towards specific points in the woman’s body. In a matter of seconds, she looked like a pincushion. His golden energies seeped into her body soon afterward which made her shine brightly.

There was almost an immediate reaction to this treatment. The woman’s eyes bulged out and she opened her mouth wide. A thick dark mist cloud shot out from it, followed by something wicked.

Zhang Dong knew what it was as he had spotted this thing in the woman’s body. He used his holy energies to force this thing outside.

“No, you don’t!’

A specially prepared needle that was larger than the rest shot upwards. A strange high pitched sound was heard by the people. They all looked up, their eyes bulged in surprise at what they saw.

It was some kind of strange worm similar to a leech. It had no eyes but many long thin tendrils that were flailing around in all directions. The creature’s body soon crumbled into dust after getting pierced by Zhang Dong’s needle.

The woman’s body was then gently guided to the ground, her pale complexion becoming rosier after the treatment.

During the examination, he noticed some kind of bug inside the woman. The small long noodle-like appendages connected directly to her brain. The creature had taken over her body in this way. The treatment forced the strange creature to escape while the holy energies nursed her body back to health without causing brain damage.

This wasn’t an easy thing to do, one misstep and the patient could be put in a vegetable state. Luckily Zhang Dong was a proficient doctor who had treated many patients through all these years already.

“She should be fine, the creature has left her body but it might take some time before she wakes up. Now I’ll take care of the rest. There could be some side effects like short term memory loss. ”

There were three more patients and he couldn’t do this too fast as there was a probability of harming them. The more entrenched in the nervous system the creatures were the harder it became to pry them away.

‘If I had the time I could make pills to simulate this healing process. I should probably capture one of these things as a sample.’

He gave out a sigh and made the other affected by the parasitic monster float over towards him. There was no time to wait, he needed to get to the source before it was too late.

Chapter 253

All of the villagers bowed down before him as if he was some kind of divine being. He had healed their sick and even set up a small defensive formation to keep them safe from harm. In their hearts, he was already an unfathomable being worthy of worship and devotion.

When he was about to remove himself from this village one of the elders spoke up. It was an old man that used to be the village head before this all happened.

“P-please honorable senior, grace us with your name, we will be sure to repay this favor in the future!”

The man’s eyes were sparkling with devotion and Zhang Dong could already tell that he was in full worshiping mode. This happened from time to time when he pulled off stunts like this so he was used to playing the part.

“There is no need to know my name… but if you ever come across someone from the United Element Sect or one of their allies, please give them aid. Now I bid you farewell.”

He left on that note. Maybe in the future, these people could repay him by helping one of his sect members. The world was vast and even these people could end up entangled with his sect. One of the young ones could grow up to be a powerful master that aids them in the time of need.

‘Think I’ve read too many novels…’

He chuckled to himself while flying away as the scenario that he just thought about sounded like your generic fantasy setting. A mysterious master saves a village, someone from it then sets out on a grand adventure to find this benefactor and then they meet up many years later.

‘Karma is a thing here, so getting a lot of it might be a good idea. As long as it isn’t bad karma…’

He continued with his journey, the village was like a tiny dot without any mist around it now. He could only hope that the people living there would be fine from now on.

There were many other villages along the way towards the main city the Divine Fist Sect was stationed. He couldn’t make a stop at each one of them, he would spend days clearing this mist himself like this.

‘I need help... ‘

Zhang Dong realized that doing this alone would only cause more casualties to happen. He could very well see himself going from village to village, city to city, and helping people out by placing formations against the mist.

This would be like putting a bandaid on a severed leg. The true source of this miasma was elsewhere and even if he visited every single city in this region nothing would be solved. The fog would probably increase in its intensity and cause the lesser formations to crumble.

He activated his secret technique, the Embodiment of the Thunder God saw the light of day again. His entire body was covered with lightning bolts and his muscles expanded.

The increase in holy energies in the area caused this mist to vanish almost instantly as he propelled himself forward. What was left behind was a hundred-meter wide tunnel, golden arcs of lightning crackling inside of it as he flew forward.

It pained him but he decided to turn a blind eye to the people in the immediate area he was in. He saw the bigger picture but this would probably cause some of the people here to be lost. He would need to live with this decision but in the long run, it would save more lives, at least that is what he was telling himself while gritting his teeth.

He shut off his senses from the surroundings, knowing well that if he felt someone in need calling out that he would stop in his tracks and intervene. The fastest way of solving this problem was by taking it out at the root.

While flying forward he activated his system window. He needed to send a message to his wife and sect. Their help would be needed soon. He previously thought that he would be fighting the monster at the location it was recuperating. A mistake was made, the mist was an unexpected variable with which he would be needing aid from his people.

“Liena I need you to do something…”

After sending it he pushed his cultivation to its limit and propelled himself towards his destination. Everything blurred and lightning crackled as he booked it. With this speed, he was finally able to arrive at his destination, the Divine Fist Sect’s main location.

He stopped while looking at the waypoint on his system map. His glowing lightning form subsided and he let out a sigh. He had gone through quite a bit of his spiritual energy to arrive here this fast. Even though his body was already past the old human limitations he was still sweating.

‘This doesn’t look good either…’

He was floating a couple of kilometers away from the main sect site. Below him was a peculiar sight though. Many monsters and beasts were slowly walking towards where the sect was located. There were all types of beasts and monstrosities down there, even ones that were previously humans.

All of them were heading in one direction and that was a sect covered in a defensive formation. It was just like he had presumed, the sect was still there but it wasn’t quite untouched.

The city he was seeing here was built into some kind of giant rocky formation. It was as if the whole place was placed in a hole after a meteorite hit. The middle spot was slightly elevated and that was also where the main castle-like structure was. There was a large tower standing tall, he could even feel powerful divine energies coming off from it.

The rest of the city was below ground level and it was surrounded from all sides by natural rocky walls. He could see that the people living here had inserted their own structures into those natural walls. There were two giant towers constructed with a main gate in the middle. It looked like this city only had one main entrance.

The structures had the usual eastern fantasy vibe to them. There were giant pagodas and buildings with slanted roofs everywhere and there was a staggering amount of them. The whole area where these structures were was surrounded by a faint golden barrier that exuded divine energies.

These energies were similar to his own holy elemental but they were of lesser quality. They were from a lesser dao of the divine which took its might from the greater dao that he was still learning.

‘That divine aura is faint… it’s not going to last more than a day unless they recharge it somehow…’

He wasn’t sure how things looked on the inside but from his standpoint, it was looking grim. There were millions of monsters going towards this defensive formation and at the front, he could even see them slamming their bodies into it.

The mist was everywhere, its concentration was higher than the one back in the village he saved. This meant that he was probably a lot closer to the source.

Zhang Dong had arrived here in a flashy way so the monsters and the people in the city were very much aware of his presence. It didn’t take long for some of the beasts that had flying capabilities to say hello.

“Not so fast ugly face…”

A monster that looked like a pterodactyl approached him. The most characteristic part besides the long beak and the webbed wings were the mass of tentacles sticking out of its head. They had clearly pierced this creature’s brain and were now in charge of its motor functions.

It was quite large, the size of a truck. It opened its large beak to reveal razor-sharp teeth and even more tentacles. It had chosen its opponent poorly though as before it could reach Zhang Dong it found itself cut into a thousand tiny pieces by his blade.

The monster wasn’t alone, there were many similar ones right behind it with more odd-looking companions. Some he recognized as altered flying beasts, there was even one that looked like a phoenix just instead of the fire it was made from more black tentacles.

There were many opponents but none of them was above the core formation level. They weren’t his match and after a couple of swings of his blade, they were turned into sashimi. Their body parts landed down below to only be devoured by the mass of monsters on the ground.

Some of the beasts even fused with the body parts that he had sliced apart. They created new fused monstrosities that looked like they were straight out of a horror flick.

Zhang Dong was like a light bulb in the dark, the monsters that had previously focused on the Divine Fist Sect’s defenses quickly turned around. They focused on the person in the sky and tried to devour him. Luckily for him, they had only numbers on their side.

He flew towards the city at a moderate pace while taking out anything that got in range of his blade. With his sword heart, nothing could stand in his way. The beasts and creatures on the ground clamored, the tentacles from their bodies extending upwards but when they got close to his radiant aura they crumbled into dust.

The people inside the city could clearly see him approaching slowly. He also made sure that he was flashy in his movement that they would take notice.

Zhang Dong had a bit of a flashback to the old times. To the time he aided his clan members during the fight against the other clans. This had a very similar feeling to it, but this time around he didn’t need to be careful he could just force his way in without any reservation.

………………………….

“W-who is that person? The beasts stand no chance and he can move in that demonic mist without a problem!”

A Divine Sect elder that was standing on one of the watchtowers said while looking at Zhang Dong flying over. A disciple had already been dispatched to alert the grand elder who was the only nascent soul elder capable of fighting.

Fang Heng was this person, he was Fang Meili’s grandfather that Zhang Dong had rescued not so long ago. He appeared at the watchtower next to the core formation elder that was responsible here. Even before getting a report, he shouted out so that everyone here could hear him.

“Lower the power to the formation and open a path for Senior Dong!”

The man looked tired and had bags under his eyes. He was also a lot thinner than the last time Zhang Dong had seen him. He thought that all hope was lost and that no help would be coming but now there was some light at the end of the tunnel.

“Well? What are you waiting for!”

He barked out the order once more as the sect elders weren’t sure about going through with this. They knew that opening up the barrier would weaken it exponentially. There would be no next time after that and the monsters would invade the city. Their elder knew this man though and he was exuding a tremendous amount of divine spiritual energy, he looked like an ally.

A small human size hole opened up for Zhang Dong who promptly sliced up the remaining flying enemies and dove inside. The people that greeted him started bowing but before they could finish and before Fang Heng could greet him, Zhang Dong waved his hand for them to stop.

“Yeah, yeah… honorable senior this… esteemed elder that. Stop wasting time and show me the way to your grand defensive formation, we have some work to do!”

He said in a commanding voice while descending down. It was time to bring his sect members over and take the fight to these monsters.

Chapter 254

Fang Heng looked at the white-haired man that was walking in front of him. This was the person that had aided his granddaughter in the banquet. He didn’t expect to see him here of all places.

He had received a device to set up a teleportation gate with him but it wasn’t working. When he and some of his sect members examined it further they found out the problem. It was this blasted mist. It was somehow blocking out the signal from traveling further.

There was a proposition of carrying it above clouds but that would put many lives at risk. There were many monsters outside the protective formation that would instantly swarm them. He was the only nascent cultivator there that would be able to contend with these beasts.

His allies were mostly at lower realms and these creatures outnumbered them one to a hundred. They had no way of knowing if that plan would even work. Even if they got this beacon high enough for the signal to go through. There was no guarantee that the man that gave him it would appear instantly.

They had abandoned this idea, taking a more passive approach while waiting. They were hopeful that this mist would clear up with time but instead it was only getting thicker.

“So, the mist appeared even before you returned?”

Fang Heng’s thoughts were interrupted as Zhang Dong spoke up to ask him a question.

“Yes senior, it began going through the lands about the same time we arrived at the banquet. It wasn’t as bad as this when I arrived here... but it has been getting worse with time passing…”

Zhang Dong nodded while rubbing his chin.

“So it started after you forced that monster back into its lair… it might have changed strategies. How long has this attack been going on for?”

Fang Heng nodded as Zhang Dong pointed this out. This was also what he and the people from his sect deducted. With the mist, the beasts outside, and even the humans were all corrupted by something. If the monster was intelligent it would try to take care of their enemies with the help of its minions, it was a basic strategy.

“It started with my return, with each day the monsters get stronger and our defensive formation weakens. These beings are susceptible to our divine arts but there are just too many. If this continues the array won’t last for more than a few days...”

Fang Heng replied while moving his head down in distraught. He hasn’t been able to sleep for days and was slowly reaching the end of his rope. But after seeing Zhang Dong in action he was feeling invigorated. The power that he showed outside was immense, he took out a quarter of the monsters outside just by himself while slowly approaching. With him around Heng was feeling hopeful once more.

“First let me look at your grand formation, I must strengthen it. This miasma is blocking out my teleportation treasures, I need to seek aid from my sect members. This is not something I can take care of myself.”

Zhang Dong proclaimed, the people next to him were surprised that someone of his status was so humble. He actually was willing to say that he wasn’t able to take care of this situation even with the immense amount of power that he wielded.

He was led towards the large castle structure in the middle of the meteor impact. It had a giant tower right in the middle that looked like a lighthouse. There was a bright yellow light shining from within it. The light slowly moved clockwise in a circular pattern while illuminating the whole sect.

This was one of the treasures that the Divine Fist Sect was proud of. It was a holy stone that radiated divine Qi, it was placed in the middle of a massive formation and it was powering it. The only problem was that the light was slowly dimming, with each spin the brightness dwindled by a small fraction.

The two nascent soul elders headed up towards this lighthouse. Fang Heng was skeptical about what Zhang Dong could do but he did possess one of the purest divine auras that he had ever seen. It was even above their sect leader and also above any of the hidden council members.

Those were also down to only three, they were all resting in the middle of this lighthouse. Sleeping in a self-induced coma as they had almost given up their lives to fight against that monstrosity.

“Interesting…”

Zhang Dong looked at the tennis ball-sized gem inside of this ‘lighthouse’. It looked like a yellow diamond and was giving off a strong divine aura. It was similar to his own but wasn’t quite there when it came to purity. It was also running low on spiritual energy, luckily for the Divine Fist Sect, he had looked into spiritual battery technology.

With a slight wave of the wrist, his spatial ring was activated and three small cubes appeared. Fang Heng looked with interest at the items Zhang Dong produced. These items were the size of a regular rubix cube, they were silver and shiny. Their surface was covered with strange runic patterns that the older elder had no way of discerning.

Zhang Dong didn’t want to waste time. He moved his hand forward and with the help of his cultivation base the cubes floated towards the shiny gem. The cubes formed a triangle around its target while gently floating around it.

With a snap of his finger, the treasures that were used for storing vast amounts of spiritual energy were activated. Thanks to the large spirit vein running under his sect Zhang Dong was able to produce these items. They were lesser versions of the cubes that he discovered previously in his travels.

Fang Heng’s eyes opened wide as he saw Zhang Dong performing some kind of strange hand movements. As he did small arcs of electricity started shooting out of those small cubes. First, they connected to each other via those electrical passages.

The three cubes started floating faster and faster while the arcs of electricity connected them together. With a bit of time those bolts of energy connected with the gem in the middle. It started out slowly but soon enough the lighthouse treasure started radiating bright light.

There was something off, Fang Heng felt that the energy that this treasure was giving off was vastly greater than what it was previously capable of. The faint yellow light was also changing into a deeper color, it looked more akin to Zhang Dong’s aura that was pure gold.

A strange buzzing sound filled the entire lighthouse as the cubes started spinning faster than a plane’s propeller. This was followed by an explosion of energy that caused the light to burst in all directions.

The people from the sect that were waiting outside the tower were hearing all of this while standing outside. This caused them to look up high at the strange phenomenon.

“W-what is that?”

They were baffled by what was happening, they were all old men and women that had spent all of their life here. This beacon of light had stood there illuminating their lives since they were children.

After that cultivator from the United Element Sect had entered it changed. Instead of the faint yellow light that they were used to, they were greeted with a deeper golden color that illuminated their sect brighter than before.

The protective shield that was close to flickering out of existence was invigorated almost instantly. The shield expanded in scope while pushing the outside monsters back. The ones that were the closest started burning up. It was as if the holy light was burning these demons to cinders, angry at their unholy existence.

“I’ll have to apologize for what I’m about to do, but this is necessary for now…”

“Huh?”

Fang Heng wasn’t sure what to expect but he saw Zhang Dong cracking his fist together. Then he pulled it back while gathering his spiritual energy into it. It was clear to him that he was winding up for a punch. Before he could stop him or ask about what he was aiming at the fist was thrown toward the ceiling.

A large boom reverberated throughout the whole sect area and the people below were stupefied even more. Their holy beacon of light, the divine lighthouse of legends that was their sect's symbol had its top blown right off. They dodged to the side while the white marble rocks crumbled down below.

The moment the tower’s ceiling was opened the light shot up through it. This was Zhang Dong’s aim. He needed this holy light that he empowered with a support array and his battery cubes to go higher. To reach the skies and to part the clouds along with this miasma that was blocking out the signal to his teleportation beacon.

So it did, the burst of light caused the protective formation to expand even further than before. The monsters that were circling above them in the hopes to attack were quickly turned to grilled tentacle meat.

Zhang Dong shouted out while moving his hand forward. He wasn’t done yet, there wasn’t quite enough power flowing into this divine treasure. There was also a little problem with the whole procedure, the gem started to crack, it was unable to handle so much spiritual energy at one go.

Fang Heng also saw this, sweat appearing on his forehead as he didn’t know what he should do. He wasn’t someone that was versed in holy treasures, nor was he a craftsman. Besides cultivation, he had no other passions so this was above him. He looked to the white-haired man that was exuding an even brighter glow than this whole lighthouse. It was up to him to take care of this, if he failed a battle against a horde of monsters was waiting for them.

Zhang Dong utilized all of his knowledge that he had gained in the last five years to mend this fissure. The gem was nothing more than a source of power that converted spiritual energy into divine might. But due to the abrupt rise in this spiritual energy, it was being overloaded, he just needed to streamline the process for it to stabilize.

It was simple in theory but he was rushing which caused him to actually blunder. If he had done it slower the gem would have probably not cracked at all. He now needed to aid it with his own cultivation base. Luckily the healing energies that he possessed would work on this item as well, after a couple of moments the cracks that were previously there started mending themselves back.

The whole formation churned with astonishing power as it finally stabilized itself. The whole Divine Fist Sect was bathed in golden light. The disciples, elders, and even the animals here quickly noticed the change in the divine aura that was now many times purer. Some of the people could even feel their wounds being mended by just being closer to the tower of light.

“T-this is… so pure… such a refined saintly glow… how is this possible?”

Fang Heng had to cover his eyes for a moment as the glow was even too bright for him. He could feel invigorated by just being in the presence of this enhanced holy formation. He could even tell that some of his old bottlenecks were getting cleared up. Old doors that remained shut for ages were getting forced to open and he knew that if he stayed here to cultivate he might even reach the late stage.

“Phew...I mean... It went just as planned, now I should be able to call my sect members!”

Zhang Dong quickly corrected himself while trying to appear as the unfathomable senior that everyone saw him as. The formation was in full swing now, what remained was to get his people over here and go kick some monster ass.

Chapter 255

Zhang Liena was walking through one of the corridors in her mansion. It had been about a week since her son was born. Normally it would take at least a month to get back to full health. With the technology that her husband supplied the sect with the time required went down dramatically.

She was just returning from one of the better sect doctors. The man didn’t hold a candle to her husband but he was the next best thing. She was given the seal of approval, now was the time to get ready to move out. Her husband had sent her a message that he had arrived at the Divine Fist Sect headquarters and that he would be setting up a teleportation gate.

He also sent another message that worried her. Previously the plan was for only the nascent soul elders to move out. Now on the other hand she was supposed to bring over more people. He gave her instructions to take the formation masters as well as the healers that were proficient with holy energies.

Zhang Dong had set up various branches of his own original dao. There were special sections that trained people in his advanced heavenly lightning skills. The other one was for his healing dao with the holy spiritual energy. Even with those two created there was no one who was proficient in both as him. Even his two current disciples had a hard time in adding a second dao to their repertoire.

Both of them tried with limited success, Liena even let her younger sister try one of them out but she failed miserably with both. Nuana her sister was handed the wind cultivation method that she herself was cultivating instead. She already knew that Zhang Dong was the person that made him and not his so-called master, Wei Hung.

While she continued to walk she thought back to the time the two got married. She had been quite eager to be accepted as Zhang Dong’s bride. Who wouldn’t be? He was a young nascent soul master, any woman in her position would have given herself to someone like him. He was handsome, strong, and still young with a bright future ahead. There wasn’t really anyone that could match him in his age bracket.

She might have gone through with the wedding with superficial reasoning. At that time she thought that she was in love, there was a sense of longing to be together with that man. In time she realized that it wasn’t that easy.

It was more due to her upbringing that this sense of wanting originated. He was just the perfect partner for any young lady at her age. He was just the right business choice with the best future prospect out of them all.

She came to a stop and glanced to the side. There she could see her young daughter running around along with some of the maids, her grandfather was also there. Liena started smiling as her little boy was also out there. He was sleeping in a special protective crib that would keep him warm even in cold weather.

‘That might have been then… but now I see that the choice was the only right one.’

After some time passed she noticed that her stone-faced husband wasn’t quite the man that she thought he was. The word that she would describe him the most would be ‘quirky’. He would put up a facade to keep people out but after it melted, his true character surfaced.

Zhang Dong the Patriarch that everyone loved was just a face that he used. In reality, he was very awkward and even shy. He had trouble in expressing his emotions at first but the two had crossed that bridge with time.

Even now Liena remembered one of the times that he prepared a surprise for her. It was exactly a year after they got married. He called it an ‘anniversary’, it was quite the novel experience. There was a surprise dinner party with only the two of them at a faraway location. A nice moonlight dinner with just the two of them. The way that he blushed that time was something that she would remember fondly to this day.

‘Think it was since then…’

“Matriarch Liena, we are ready for your inspection. Lord Qiang has been informed and he will be arriving shortly.”

Her train of thought got interrupted after she arrived at her destination. This was a hidden gathering room with enough space for over a thousand people to fit in. This would be also close to the number of sect brothers and sisters that would be attending in this expedition.

“Ah yes, tell him to hurry up, we can’t have the Patriarch wait after he activates the teleportation gate.”

She covered her face with one of her battle fans while speaking. These weapons were brand new and of the heaven grading, specially made by her husband. It was also one of the anniversary gifts that he had offered her.

Actually, after the two had started doing these anniversary events the sect people picked up on the trend. It started to be popular for couples to do things such as this. Both of them would give each other some kind of gift each year.

This left Liena in a bit of a bind. She wasn’t that good at making items and could only spend spirit stones on buying them from other people. She tried making up that gap in other fields that her husband greatly appreciated.

She blushed a bit after thinking about that last part. The person that called out to her was still there but couldn’t see her face that was behind that large jade green fan. She decided to move forward to inspect her troops.

She could see many people in various robes. There were about a hundred sect elders here that were above the core formation level. After five years of cultivating most of the elders that were stuck at the foundation establishment realm made a breakthrough. With the spirit vein in place and Zhang Dong’s improved cultivation manuals, everyone soared.

The United Element Sect was slowly making up for the time. They now had a similar number of core formation seniors to similar-sized sects. With the better cultivation methods, they were also of higher quality.

“Yes, like that. Please make sure to form a line towards the teleportation gate, the moment the Patriarch activates the beacon we will move through. We aren’t sure what will be on the other side so be ready for battle!”

There was a large teleportation gate in the middle of this room. It was connected to the beacons that Zhang Dong had with him. The sect members clasped their hands and nodded.

The people that were gathered here were composed mostly of core and inner disciples and also elders. They were the backbone of the new generation that was still developing, within time some of them were primed to reach the nascent soul level.

“Did someone say battle?”

Liena looked to the side and spotted a large red-haired man flying over. She covered half of her face with her fan while looking him over.

This was Huo Qiang, the other founding member besides her and Zhang Dong. He was wearing a tight-fitting black shirt that showed off his pecks. His thick arms were covered by intricate looking ruby gauntlets, their thickness only made the man’s arms look larger.

She still didn’t like Qiang all that much. The man was self-centered and haughty, he was of the mindset that fighting was the end all be all. Liena also disliked the fact that he had a large harem of ladies stashed away in his estate. Her husband was different, he was monogamous, something rarely seen in this world of cultivation.

“You finally graced us with your presence, Qiang?”

Qiang smirked while looking at Liena. Both of them started staring at each other while the disciples and other elders sweated at the sidelines. Everyone here knew that these two didn’t see eye to eye. The only person who could actually control them wasn’t here so they were afraid that a fight might break out.

“Are those wrinkles that I see?”

“What did you say? Did your brain shrink even more?”

Qiang laughed out while throwing a small jab at Liena. She on the other hand quickly retailed with a few chosen words. The people around them started backing away even more, sweat covered their foreheads instantly. Luckily for them, there were two people present that could diffuse the situation.

“Please Aunt and Uncle calm down, you are scaring the other disciples.”

A person moved between the two. He had a similar look to the fabled Patriarch. His hair was pure white and he was very dashing. His name was Zhang Liu and he was Zhang Dong’s disciple.

“Yes, why don’t we drink some tea before Master opens up the teleportation gate?”

The second one was a white-haired maiden. She was the most beautiful woman in the sect from the junior generation. Her name was Zhang Xue and she was also Zhang Dong’s disciple. A bit further away was another young woman, this one had golden hair, her name was Fang Meili.

Liena turned her head to the side while giving out a sound of discomfort with her mouth. Qiang on the other hand shrugged as if this was something that he was already used to and didn’t care about.

She looked at the blond girl at the side and then back to Zhang Xue that was with her. She knew that her husband brought over a lady from the city that he had come from. The girl looked to be close to twenty years of age and was quite the beauty. Liena was out of commission for a week so she didn’t have the time to meet her.

Some people even started spreading rumors that she was a concubine that Zhang Dong brought over. This was something that her husband wouldn’t do. She was quite confident about this, even more after she examined the girl in front of her. Fang Meili’s lacked a set of assets that would make her husband interested in her. It would be highly unlikely for her husband to be attracted to this girl that was a bit too skinny for his tastes.

“This is cousin Meili, Master invited her into the sect, she is a relative from grandfather's side…”

Zhang Xue moved her head a bit to the side while blushing. By just mentioning Zhang Jin everyone in here knew how this Meili was related to everyone.

“Is that so,... You have my condolences.”

Liena nodded while rolling her eyes. She had no idea how her husband was related to ‘that thing’. How one person’s desires could take over reasoning like that baffled this Matriarch greatly. She was really glad that her husband didn’t do these sorts of things when he went away. If he was like Qiang or Jin there would be quite a bit of babies running around the premises already.

Meili looked at Liena with a strange look on her face. The girl wasn’t sure why but whenever this Zhang Jin was mentioned people tended to look away. She herself had evaded meeting her ancestor from the other side of the family. Somehow Zhang Xue had always evaded questions about him whenever she prodded for answers.

Everyone was ready for departure and just in time as Liena received a message from her husband. Following it the gate received the coordinates for its activation. It was time to depart and show off the skills of the United Element Sect.

Chapter 256

Zhang Dong had gotten the lighthouse running up again. The holy light filled the entire city and bathed its citizens with healing energies. These were much purer than the divine ones that they were used to. The people that were stuck in lower cultivation realms could feel themselves advancing by just being in the presence of this energy.

He had destroyed the roof of this tower but the people here didn’t care. They were looking at Zhang Dong with worship in their eyes and he knew it. This was the usual way people in this world reacted when someone above them helped them on their cultivation journey. They were probably already considering him half a teacher by this point.

This wasn’t why he was here though, the miasma was cleared up. It was time to call over his people to this place.

“Edler Heng, I need a wide plot of land to set up the teleportation array…”

“Elder Heng?”

Zhang Dong called out twice while Fang Heng spaced out. The old man was still looking at the dazzling golden gem in the middle of the lighthouse. He was also staring at the big hole in the ceiling.

“Ah? Yes, excuse me for my rudeness Senior.”

The old man shook his head around while he gathered his thoughts. Zhang Dong gave him some time to relax as he knew that what he did here was unprecedented.

“Please follow me, We have already prepared an area.”

The two nascent soul masters finally descended from the tower. Both of them flew down and into an open field. The ground was pure white marble and he could see a large fountain right in the middle. There were various statues here and there but most of it was just open space. It was in front of the large lighthouse and probably just a spot for people to gather or look at it.

“Yes, this will do. After I set up the teleportation gate please guide me to your sect elders, I might be able to heal them. It would be best if we had more people helping our cause.”

Zhang Dong wanted to examine the people that went against the upgraded version of his old enemy. Supposedly the sect leader was one of the survivors. All of them practiced some form of divine arts so they would come in handy in the coming battle.

Elder Heng nodded and quickly passed on the information to some of his sect members. They would prepare everything as well as clear up the rubble from the partially destroyed divine lighthouse.

“That would be reassuring, the sect leader and the other elders are beneath this lighthouse. With the new divine energies filling it they might recover much faster, Senior Dong. If you wish to see them, I will guide you myself.”
“Good, let us begin then. This won’t take long.”

Zhang Dong pulled out the teleportation beacon that he had brought over from home. If it was him he could use the system to teleport to such a device but it wouldn’t be that easy for his sect members to do the same. He needed to create a teleportation array here along with a teleportation gate. It would need to be connected to the one at his sect ground and only then would his troops be able to come here.

He waved his hand, his spatial ring was activated once more and a large metallic box dropped down to the ground. It looked like a wide platform, it seemed quite heavy as the floor buckled under the pressure creating some cracks.

Other people from the Divine Fist Sect gathered around. Everyone was curious about what this man was capable of. After what he did to their tower they were taking notes, it was like looking at a hidden master giving them pointers.

After the strange piece of metal was placed Zhang Dong reached out with his hand. He pushed out a faint amount of spiritual energy while pointing at it. As it seeped into the piece of metal the people around here could hear faint crackling noises.

The large piece of metal started moving into action. First, more runes appeared on it before it started changing shape. The metal started unfolding itself and in a short time, a round object that looked like a giant halo appeared before them. At the base, it still had a metallic platform on which it was balancing its weight.

Zhang Dong took out the cube-shaped teleportation beacon and threw it towards this halo. The cube floated towards it and embedded itself into the base where there was a small square spot for it. The moment the bacon was attached to this gate a humming sound was heard.

The inside of it started to slowly fill up with blue spiritual energy. It looked like water was coming together out of the outermost parts of this empty halo. Slowly but surely the energies connected with each other, it looked like an ocean that was rippling with waves.

The teleportation gate was now in place. The shiny parts that made out the edges continued to glow with strange runes. These magical symbols continuously changed shapes until settling into a static pattern. When they did the gate churned with power and the unruly waves started calming down till they looked like a surface of a lake.

Before signaling his people to come through the game Zhang dong turned to look at Fang Heng before speaking up.

“I will signal my sect members to go through the gate, is that fine with you?”

Fang Heng just nodded at the question. Zhang Dong posed it as a courtesy, he was bringing over his people here and more or less taking things over. This would normally be a hit to the face of any sect. No one liked when other forces got involved and they now had to listen to them. This was an emergency situation, Fang Heng was just grateful that his sect had a fighting chance now.

“If you wish to send other members of your family away from here they can go through the gate. They will arrive in my lands and be safe even if the monster isn’t contained.”

Fang Heng rubbed his chin while hearing Zhang Dong talk. Having an option to evacuate the non-combatants was something that they could use. The problem was that if he announced it now, some of the sect members might panic and try to force themselves into the teleportation portal.

“You have my thanks senior, I will bring it up with the other elders and we will decide on it with haste.”

Within a moment’s notice, people started walking through the teleportation gate that he created. The first person that appeared through it was a large muscular man with red hair. Zhang Dong expected his wife to be the first one through but he also knew that it would be Qiang’s style to muscle his way through as a prank.

“Greetings brother, I heard there would be many monsters to fight?”

He walked through with a big grin on his face while exuding plasma energy. Zhang Dong could feel that his sect brother was close to pushing through the early stage and the people here also took note. The moment he stepped through they backed away in fright, Qiang was not hiding any of that energy away which put some strain on the cultivators here.

“Hey stop that, we are guests.”

Zhang Dong’s lower lip moved downwards slightly as he waved his hand around to disperse the oppressive nascent soul aura from seeping through. This made the others relax somewhat.

“Is that idiot causing trouble already?”

The next person to walk through the gate was a beautiful woman. She couldn’t be considered a jade beauty by this world’s standards, her looks were quite more unorthodox. It was his lovely wife all dressed up in a light green robe that went well with her wind elemental esthetic.

Zhang Dong’s eyes moved from his flaming friend over to his wife. He hadn’t seen her for a week and even back home she was bedridden. Seeing her this lively brought a smile to his face, this smile quickly faded though as he needed to keep up his stone-faced senior persona.

This didn’t go unnoticed by the tanned beauty. She moved one of her green fans closer to her face to cover a smile of her own. She wanted to move towards her husband and give him a hug but she knew that this wasn’t the time or place to show affection. She knew that this was serious as her husband did explain the whole situation back home.
“It’s nice to see you, are you feeling well?”

Zhang Dong asked while walking towards his wife with an outstretched hand. He did it to help her go down from the platform. It was kind of a strange thing to see, someone helping a nascent soul master walk down a platform. He still wanted to be courteous towards her, slightly worried that she didn’t fully recover after giving birth.

“You don’t need to worry my husband, I have eaten all the spirit medicine that you left me. You should stop worrying about small things. Think we had some lowly beasts to slay?”

“Yeah, where are they? I’m itching for a fight.”

Qiang proclaimed from the side while cracking his large fist. It was already covered in red energy as he was ready to let loose some of that pent up rage.

“They are outside this protective formation, take some of the elders with you. There are a lot of them you might need some help. Also, try not to harm the possessed humans, we might be able to cure them, use our sect members for this task.”

Zhang Dong replied while snapping out of it, looking at his wife brought his mind back home. He remembered that this was no time for such things. They needed to take care of those monsters outside and then go to those ruins, the main enemy was waiting there.

While the three original elders from the United Element Sect talked more people started walking through the portal. Zhang Liu was next, followed by Zhang Xue and Fang Meili. Everyone moved by rank and after the nascent soul masters, Xue and Liu had the most prestige. They were young core formation disciples of the sect leader. There were also other people from the clans walking with them, they looked similar to Qiang by their looks.

The moment Fang Meili walked out her grandfather Fang Heng’s eyes bulged out. He was not expecting to see her here.

“Meili’er what are you doing here?”

“Grandfather!?”

The blond girl jumped up with join and quickly ran towards her grandfather. She gave him a big hug while the old man placed his hand on her head with a mixed expression. The young girl started sobbing, the rest of the United Element Sect members just moved to the side as they started coming in.

There were a lot of them using that teleportation gate. They were wearing similar robes to the ones Zhang Dong had created all those years for the secret ground expedition. The biggest difference was that they were color-coded by rank, which meant that most of them were dark violet.

After everyone was inside the gate was turned off to not waste the spiritual energy. Gates like this were very power-hungry and the further a person had to travel the more Qi they drained. With everyone here the plan could finally continue, there were about one thousand sect members here with a hundred of them being core formation experts.

“Everyone listen up. We have all gathered here to aid our friends from the Divine Fist Sect in their time of need. We need to cleanse these lands from these despicable demonic beings! There is one problem, the monsters that are outside are only a diversion, the true evil demon lies further away…”

Zhang Dong started speaking to his people. It was time to organize his troops. Huo Qiang would be responsible for clearing out the immediate threat of the monsters outside. He on the other hand with the sect members that were versed in healing arts would try to help out the remaining nascent soul elders from the Divine Fist Sect.

It was time to bring the fight to the demonic beings.

Chapter 257

Huo Qiang smashed both of his large fists together. After these five years, he had grown a nice red beard to go with his crimson hair that was now longer as well. He was getting ready to jump out of the protective formation along with some of his sect brothers. There was also a particular group of youngsters among them, each one with similar crimson hair as Qiang.

“Father, the barrier will be opening soon.”

“Great, are you and the boys ready?”

Huo Qiang was grinding wide while looking behind him. There were about ten youths that looked similar to each other in one way or another. At the front stood Huo Kong that was looking like a younger version of his father already. The others behind him were his brothers that Huo Qiang had sired.

They were all at the core formation level all of them were at the early stage. Kong was the furthest one in and the closest to reaching the middle stage. With the United Element Sect’s new techniques and ample spiritual resources, people that were core members could rise up their rank rather quickly.

“I’ll be taking care of most of them, try not to get in my way when we are out there!”

He grinned while his body started shining in crimson. He started flying upwards toward the protective barrier. Now when it was empowered there was no fear of it closing. Qiang just needed to wait a moment for the Divine Fist Sect elders to open a path for him. When they did the United Element Sect would show these monsters their might.

The youths looked at their father flying into the distance. They knew that it was wise to not be too close to their pops. He liked to go wild, he had a hard time containing his power and when someone sparred with him they ended up injured in one way or the other. The only person that they knew that could contend with him was Zhang Dong.

Even though he was the number two of the sect, they were still very proud to be his kids. But due to the fact that there were a lot of them here, some family infighting was inevitable. Huo Qiang had a similar outlook about relationships as Zhang Jin. He didn’t have as many wives or kids as the old man, still there were over a hundred of them.

Every child wanted to be on top then they could inherit the family head title. There were also kids from side families and now new sect members that could affect the power dynamics of their clan. The group here wanted to prove themselves to their father, if they were useful they were hoping for rewards such as status.

“Don’t think you will be on top forever, brother…”

One of the red-haired youths stuck his chin up while looking at Huo Kong.

“You can try little brother, but we both know who the superior one is!”

Huo Kong replied while smirking at the other youth. He could see that the moment he did the younger brother’s forehead started showing quite the bulging vein. The redness in his face wasn’t something that he wouldn’t notice either.

“You just wait! I’ll be sure to kill more monsters than you do. Do you dare to make a wager with me if you are that confident!”

Huo Kong raised his eyebrow at the callout. This younger brother of his had quite a mouth to him but he also had some skills to back it up. He wasn’t far behind Kong in cultivation but he always managed to be a step ahead so he wouldn’t fear making a wager.

“What do you want to wager? Spirit herbs? Spirit stones?”

“No, those are plentiful and easy to come by… We will wager Fairy Xue!”

Huo Kong almost tripped over as the large smirk covering his face turned upside down. He was clearly having trouble processing what this younger brother was talking about.

“F-fairy Xue?... w-what do you mean Kueng?”

The younger brother was called Huo Kueng smirked while looking to the side. There she was in the distance, Zhang Xue. She was in the process of walking together with her master Zhang Dong. She and a group of sect members were following the Patriarch into the lighthouse to check up on the comatosed Divine Fist Sect elders.

Huo Kong noticed this and he also looked, their conversation continued but in whispers as the red-haired youth started getting bashful.

“How dare you propose a wager over Sister Xue!”

He also started getting angry, his face showing a similar bulging vein on his forehead as his brothers did earlier. Huo Kueng was the one smirking now as he knew his older brother’s weak point.

“What are you afraid that you would lose? I thought you were confident in your skills, brother Kong?”

The other brothers looked at these two fighting. They were interested in where this would lead to and if Zhang Xue was on the line even they were considering taking part in the wager.

“Afraid? Me?... never! What is the wager about exactly? Tell me now!”

Huo Kong was easily irritated just like his father, he also didn’t think that he would lose to his younger brother. Kueng on the other hand straightened himself out and started listing the rules of this wager.

“It’s simple brother, whoever wins will be the one to go ask for Fairy Xue’s company in the coming yearly sect festival. The one that loses will not interfere and promise not to bother Fairy Xue for a year! How is that, do you dare take this wager or are you too scared to accept it!”

Huo Kueng pointed with his finger at Huo Kong that was starting to fume. His short temper was clearly getting to him.

“If I accept this bet… how will we determine the winner? Will we count how many monsters we kill?”

Huo Kong was skeptical, how would they even go about this? Would someone be following after them and doing the counting, he couldn’t really trust his younger brother to not cheat if he didn’t have someone trustworthy performing the task.

“No, remember what the Patriarch said about the people. We are to carry them over here to our healers. The one that carries over the most will win. Our doctors were tasked to write down the number of infected, they will do the counting for us.”

The younger brother smirked as if he was the smartest person around. To Huo Kong this would fix the issue of cheating, the doctors would be marking down who carried who over for future reference so that no people get lost.

There was one small problem with this, Kong didn’t feel like it was very ethical to make a wager where people's lives are involved. Someone might die if any of the youths were too overzealous in their rescuing.

It didn’t sit too well with him to use these people's lives during a bet. Before he could decline this offer he heard a high-pitched voice from the side. He recognized who it belonged to almost instantly due to how childlike it sounded.

“What are you idiots doing? If the Senior Sister hears about this you will be punished!”

The group of brothers turned to the side. The voice sounded cute and sweet yet annoyed, it clearly belonged to someone of the female gender. What they saw was quite the small looking girl with an overdeveloped chest and light pink hair. The skin tone and all-around style was similar to their sect’s Matriarch but her demeanor was quite different.

“Nuana?”

Huo Kong called out while the rage inside of him started to subside. This girl was Zhang Liena’s younger sister and where she was Zhang Liu was probably not far away. It didn’t take him long to notice the white-haired man standing a bit behind her, looking at him with an awkward expression.

“Stay out of this sister Nuana, this is between us brothers!”

Kueng was quick to stop the girl from talking. All of these youths here were from the same generation so they didn’t consider the Matriarch’s young sister above them. They were the sons of the number 2 person in the whole sect. In their eyes they might be even above them, they would be close in prestige to Zhang Dong’s own children.

Even though Zhang Dong wanted to be done with the bloodline system. The people of this world weren’t willing to abandon it just yet. Even Zhang Xue and Liu, who were Zhang Dong’s disciples, weren't that closely related by blood. He was only a distant uncle while these youths were direct descendants of a grand elder.

But in the end, it also depended on how close the given person was to the elder in power. Zhang Dong wasn’t that great in asserting the pecking order. He evaded the struggles of the inner members of the sect along with the politics involved. He mostly kept to himself and let others take care of things like inner disputes. Even now he was long gone and not here, the junior members would have to clear things out amongst themselves.

“Between you? This isn’t a picnic you fools, I’m going to tell my elder brother about this! You all will be sorry!”

Nuana was part of the family now, she referred to Zhang Dong as ‘elder brother’. This was quite different from calling him ‘senior brother’. It was more intimate and showed a closer relationship between the two involved parties.

The group for red-haired youths instantly shrunk back in fear when they heard that. The small girl was angrily pointing her finger at them while shouting. If she brought this up with the sect leader it could bring them trouble. There also was a chance that he wouldn’t care but would they be willing to anger that man?

“Hah.”

Zhang Liu that was to the side finally decided to come over after hearing the commotion. He gave out a sigh while pushing Nuana to the side with his hand.

“Stop with your nonsense all of you, can’t you see that Elder Qiang is already leaving the barrier? The other elders are also working, we from the junior generation can’t fall behind!”

Huo Qiang and his younger brother turned to the side and could see their father powering up. His aura spiked while his soul beast was summoned, the path forward was now open and he was starting to attack.

The older members from the sect that was also at the core formation level sprung to action as well. Almost all of them formed battle formations that took on the forms of various serpents and dragons. They looked similar to the old Zhang Clan formations but their quality and strength was far greater.

“Now stop playing around all of you!”

Zhang Liu’s expression shifted into one of contempt as his aura exploded forward. He was the top fighter of his generation and everyone knew that. He didn’t intend to fight these people, instead, he quickly jumped onto his flying sword and propelled himself towards the opening.

Huo Qiang’s sons looked slightly dejected. Getting shouted at by Zhang Dong’s disciple was quite the hit to their face. He was also the brother of Zhang Xue that they all were aiming for which could cause some problems in the future if they tried courting her.

“W-wait Senior Brother Liu, I’ll aid you!”

“M-me too!”

The brothers pulled out their own flying swords and gave chase. Huo Kong and his brother glared at each other before also taking off.

“We will resolve this later.”

“Yes, we will…”

Everyone from the United Element Sect that was strong enough to face these monsters was now outside the barrier. Everyone here was greeted by millions of strange creatures, they all looked horrifying. They were also burning up due to the high amounts of plasma Huo Qiang’s Ifrit soul beast was now discharging towards them.

“Leave the big ones to me, you all just save the people!”

Huo Qiang gave his order while punching forward, his fiery fists causing widespread destruction and turning the monsters to ashes in just fractions of a second.

Chapter 258

Zhang Dong looked at Huo Qiang fly away towards the monsters. The little conversation that his sons and his disciples had evaded him as he was busy going towards the bottom of the light-tower. His wife wasn’t here with him as she remained outside to aid Qiang if anything out of the ordinary appeared outside.

There were no nascent soul monsters out there yet but that didn’t mean that ones wouldn’t come to be. He knew how these tentacle beings operated. He only hoped that some of the affected humans that were out there could be saved.

“Here's a sample of one of those demon spawns, analyse it.”

He gave the monster worm that he extracted from one of the villagers to his best healer. The man’s name was Huo Fu, an oddball from the Huo clan.

This man looked quite different from all the other muscle men that were born in that clan. He was quite short and lanky, his hair was messy and he didn’t look like the other warriors from that clan.

Zhang Dong had discovered his high intelligence and talent for making remedies after having everyone scanned by his scanner. This happened years before the sect examination and was done to bring the people with talent to the forefront.

This man had no knack for the teachings of his own clan, the element that he was best suited for was also the exact opposite which was water. After this discovery, he was given the correct teachings and he proved himself as one of the best pill and potion makers from the new sect. Now, Zhang Dong relied on him to perform certain tasks, examining a monster like this would fit Huo Fu’s expertise quite well.

“This is…”

The man looked at the bottle with the monster inside. The worm was wiggling around and its thin tendrils lashed out at anyone that it could detect.

“Such a magnificent sample… as expected of the Patriarch!”

The man’s eyes bulged out wide, he was looking at this horrifying monster as if it was a Christmas gift that Zhang Dong handed down to him. He looked to the side where some other sect members in similar robes to him were.

“Quickly, set up the portable lab, we must analyze this specimen with haste!”

He bowed to Zhang Dong while going outside. About twenty of the foundation establishment elders went along with him as they were part of his research team. He himself didn’t have time to work on the cure so he would leave it to this man. He was hoping that they could develop a remedy for the people and save them.

“This way Senior Dong.”

Fang Heng called out to Zhang Dong as the two descended down below the lighthouse. There were no stairs here, probably so that anyone below the core formation level wouldn’t be able to come here.

The descent was quite dramatic but he could feel that the holy energies from above were being pushed towards this area.

‘Are those plants?... they are similar to the ones that were back in that village…’

He expected to see something different. Instead of some kind of extensive healing array formation, he saw a green meadow with many large sunflowers. These sunflowers were the size of trees and they were giving out divine energies. These energies were far greater than what the smaller sunflowers were able to output.

The next interesting discovery was where these three surviving nascent soul elders were. They were directly in the center of those giant plants, their bodies were bandaged up almost fully with only their heads being outside. They were just lying there in the center of the large sunflower while the bandages somehow aided them in absorbing the divine energy.

He could discern this with his eyes. The gentle holy like energy was slowly flowing inside of their bodies and nourishing them. He could also sense something else, an evil demonic energy signature below.

“Evil Qi?”

He called out, which prompted Fang Heng to look at him with astonishment.

“So you can tell Senior Dong? Yes, the elders were affected by that creature’s corrupt evil energy. We were able to halt the corruption with the help of the specially crafted wrappings made from special divine silk. It was made from the cocoon of the holy moonlight moth.”

Zhang Dong tried to ignore the long-winded explanation. In short, these were special bandages that were good at holding back demonic energies. He examined the three bodies with his system, what he saw was two old men and one old woman at their death bed.

The strongest person was at the late stage of the nascent soul. Zhang Dong could feel that there was something wrong. This elders realm was declining, it was closer to the middle stage now and still decreasing. Even with the healing energies in place these people were slowly deteriorating, with time they would probably perish. The increase in the holy energies of the lighthouse was probably slowing down the process even further but it still wasn’t enough.

“Yes, let me examine them first.”

Zhang Dong got to work, he focused on the sect leader as it seemed that he took the brunt of the attack. The demonic energies on his body were even seeping through those wrappings and giving them a darker coloring.

His needle healing technique was utilized first. Fang Heng and the other people in the room stayed quiet while he got to work. They all watched as the pointy silver needles pushed themselves into the Divine Fist Sect leader’s body. He was sure to aim for all the correct pressure points to nourish his body back to health.

The technique produced a lot of golden light as it went to work. After a few moments, he could see the man’s eyes quivering but they didn’t open. Even after adding more energy, he remained in the comma and the demonic energies only slightly subsided.

“The corrupt energies have been in his body for too long, it won’t be that easy to get them out of his system…”

“S-senior is there nothing that you can do?”

Fang Heng called out from the side while his forehead perspired with sweat. He was clearly distraught after seeing Zhang Dong’s healing technique fail.

“There is a way, it's just going to take some time to prepare and…”

Zhang Dong paused at the end while rubbing his chin as he didn’t finish the sentence, this prompted Heng to ask about it.

“And?”

“Ah nothing, we need to prepare a pill, please get everything ready.”

Zhang Dong shook it off while glancing at his sect members that were also there. They were ready to do his biddings and started pulling out various pill making items along with a big cauldron that they placed in the middle.

“Set up the formation!”

Fang Heng stopped asking after the whole United Element Sect personnel started working. Some of them were putting various herbs into the large cauldron while others were drawing strange symbols on the ground below.

Fang Heng moved to the side while trying not to bother anyone. He could feel that his Patriarch’s spirit was slightly invigorated after Zhang Dong treated him with his healing technique. If he said that it was possible then he would put his trust in him, not like he had much to lose at this point.

“Okay everyone, get in your positions we will be going with variation Zeta 6C this time around.”

Everyone from the United Element Sect nodded while Zhang Dong moved into the middle. He started floating directly above the large cauldron that was already at the boiling point. There were thirty other members of the healer unit with him. They would aid him in making this special medicine.
They wouldn’t add much to the finished product but would allow him to push it past a certain threshold. Even improving the medicine by 1% would be enough to decide life or death.

The formation churned with power and everything in this area started glowing in gold. The large sunflowers started reacting and the faint yellow light that they were exuding change into a deeper color.

Zhang Dong started tossing various herbs into the cauldron without using his hands. Those were clasped together and making various hand seals. He was also performing some chants in a language that some of the people here wouldn’t understand.

While the restorative pill was being produced noises from the outside reached here. Everyone could hear explosions and strange wails, this was probably Huo Qiang at work as the monster eradication outside started taking place.

The rumbling outside was a bit distracting but the experienced team of alchemists and healers was able to stay calm. In time a pill started to take form, it radiated massive amounts of holy energy. When it was completed it caused an illusory image of a golden dragon to appear and roar. This was a sign of this remedy's qualities reaching close to the maximum of the heaven grade.

“It’s finished…”

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh of relief. Even for him making such a pill wasn’t easy. Without the help of his team of healers, the pill would have probably dropped a small realm in quality.

He looked at it, the pill was golden and a bit longer in an oval shape. It was about the size of his thumb but was more uniform without any blemishes. It looked as if it was made from pure shiny gold instead of various herbs.

“S-senior this is?”

Fang Heng moved closer after the process was done. His eyes were bulging wide after seeing the item before him. His cultivation instincts were telling him to grab this pill and flee, if he could swallow it he would probably reach the late stage instantly. He held his desires back as he knew that other things were at stake. He also didn’t think he could wrestle it off Zhang Dong’s hands even if he wanted to.

“Good… now we need to give it to your sect leader… could you do the honors, Elder Heng?”

The old man was surprised by the request that was given. But he wasn’t one to refuse, even holding this pill in his hand could be very beneficial.

The pill floated into his hand, Zhang Dong then moved over to the sunflower where the Divine Sect Patriarch was. He used his telekinetic like technique to move the old man’s body up. He was gently turned around and then placed in a strange position.

“Senior?”
Fang Heng asked while looking down at his sect leader. His body was leaning forward and the thing he could see was his posterior protruding his way.

“Uh… you see, the demonic energies are far too great so swallowing the pill normally wouldn’t be advised. We must apply it to your Patriarch’s… uh… rear…opening”

Zhang Dong rubbed his neck while slowly moving the bandages out of the way. Fang Heng looked at the pill in his hand and then at the wrinkly bare man butt that was presented to him.

“Y-you mean?”

“Yes, this is a suppository. Please apply it gently ah, give Elder Heng some lubricant.”

Zhang Dong replied while calling to his sect members that brought over a jar with a transparent gel-like substance. The pill was then dipped in it to allow for a more gentle experience.

“Ready when you are Elder Heng, please hurry your sect leader’s life depends on it!”

Zhang Dong gave the man a thumbs up while flying to the side. The old man with the pill covered in lubricant started sweating. He was now looking at a respected pillar of his sect his bare bottom exposed before him. After a moment he steeled his resolve as he realized that this was a matter of life and death.

“Forgive me Patriarch but it has to be done!”

“GAHHHHHhhhh….”

A strange sound of a screaming man was soon heard by the people that were keeping guard outside the lighthouse. Some of them recognized those shouts as the voice of their beloved leader. What really happened down below would be kept secret; the true way of how the Patriarch was healed would remain a mystery for centuries to come.

Chapter 259

Zhang Dong turned his head to the side as he didn’t really want to see the ‘booty play’ between two old men. The moment the ‘task’ was done the sect leader from the Divine Fist Sect was cured almost instantly. His loud shout of ‘gratitude’ could be heard by everyone here. The truth about this day would be kept hidden due to the old man’s embarrassment.

“Let me help him contain the energies inside of his body!”

Zhang Dong shouted out, he placed his hand on the old sect leader’s head and brought his screams to a stop. He would have done this sooner but he was a bit surprised at the instantaneous scream. The suppository was more effective than he expected, if he knew that the medicine was this potent then he might have just given it to him the normal way. Now it was best not to mention this fact to this person.

With his aid, the bandaged up old man started lighting up like a Christmas tree. The wrappings that were around him burst as they weren’t able to contain this degree of Qi. This left the sect leader nice and naked, the doctors from the United Element Sect didn’t care much but the sect members from the Divine Fist Sect that were there started looking away. They were having a hard time seeing their leader getting treated like that. First was the suppository and now he was all bare before them.

“Almost there!”

He shouted while controlling the golden energies in the patient’s body. After his naked form came to light the patches of black demonic energy were seen. They were shrinking away as the golden energy touched them. The holy Qi was successfully killing off the evil qi that was inside this man’s body, soon enough none of it was left behind. The man was fully healed and even looked a bit younger than he did before. His skin wasn’t as wrinkly and color returned to his face.

“It’s done!”

Zhang Dong waved his hand and brought over some white cloth to cover this naked grandpa. He then floated him down to the ground where his own sect members could take care of him. The two other patients weren’t as affected by the evil Qi as the sect leader. He could probably heal them by making one more pill and split it between the two.

He got to work on it along with his sect members. While he and they were concentrating Fang Heng moved over to his sect leader and started calling out to him.

“Sect leader are you awake? Sect leader Wuying?”

He could see him looking much better than before. His complexion had improved, the healing pill had worked wonders. In time the sect leader that was named Mao Wuying started waking up. His eyes quivered a bit but soon enough he could see Heng’s wrinkled up face looking down at him.

“Elder Heng?”

“Oh thank the heavens, you are alive sect leader!”

The old man smiled, with the sect leader alive and then the other two elders he wasn’t the only nascent soul elder left. With them around, this situation could be salvaged somewhat. They still had a strong base of operations with a powerful defensive barrier that was now reinforced. Now after defeating that monster they would be able to wait and slowly recover. With four nascent soul masters on their side, that would be a possibility.

“What happened… I feel strange…”

The old man looked close to sixty, he had a full beard and gray hair to match it. His face was round and he looked like a friendly fellow. He looked confused and disoriented, he was also grasping his rear while rubbing it. Something back there wasn’t right, the pill had melted during the healing process but the feeling it leftover still lingered.

“I-I feel like I have lost something… something precious… uh…”

The man rubbed his head while trying to grasp the situation. He recalled the last things he remembered. He and his sect members activated the grand formation and used up their trump card to drive a menacing monster back. He then succumbed to the wounds along with the backlash of activating that old relic. Then he woke up with a headache and an even larger ache in his backside.

“Elder Heng please give me an explanation…, why am I naked and who are those people?”

Mao Wuying gathered himself to his feet while holding the white cloth around his body. He could see Zhang Dong not that far away producing another pill for healing. He could feel that the white-haired man wasn’t anyone simple.

“Let me explain, sect leader. That man is the Patriarch of the United Element Sect, I met him at the annual banquet after you and the other elders went into a coma I…”

While the pill creation and healing process continued Fang Heng started explaining what happened. He gave his sect leader a short version of the events that happened as there wasn’t enough time to go into much detail. He painted Zhang Dong and his sect in a good light. They were their saviors and would probably need to get rewarded in some way.

Heng filled Wuying in on the information while the two watched Zhang Dong heal the other two elders. This time around the pill was inserted into their mouths which was enough to cure them both. These elders were at the middle stage of the nascent soul level. The sect leader was at the lower end of the late stage but now with this healing pill in their bodies, they could push their cultivation to the next level. That is if they survived the coming days to do so.

“Elder Yun!, Elder Xinyi!”

Heng called out while being ecstatic. He wasn’t alone anymore, he had his sect leader back with him along with two other elders that were at the same middle stage as he was. With them around they would be able to somehow survive through this. While those two were waking up, the sect leader Wuying took this chance to converse with Zhang Dong. The two Patriarchs looked at each other, the older one was a bit reserved while the younger one felt more awkward than anything.

“If what elder Heng says is true, then you have my gratitude Patriarch of the United Element Sect.”

The man clasped his hands and did a little bow. After feeling out Zhang Dong he noticed that the man’s divine aura was far greater than his. This was enough for him, holy energies were a good gauge for character. Someone that was evil and conniving would never be able to cultivate a Dao like that.

“No need to thank me, we just find ourselves against a common enemy. The creature that attacked your sect is an old foe that I had battled before. From what I’ve heard it is much stronger than when I last faced it. Could you disclose any information about your battle to me?”

Wuying was a bit surprised at this but it would make sense for someone with such a divine Dao to hunt demonic beings.

“Anyone that is an enemy of that demonic creature is an ally to this sect, I will tell you what I know but first let us go out!”

The man had been given a replacement robe and the other two elders were already conversing with Fang Heng. He would bring them up to speed while everyone else floated up to see what was happening around the sect grounds.

Wuying was surprised instantly after getting out of the lighthouse underground. The first thing was the increase in the divine might of their tower, it was many times stronger than what he could remember. Then the divine protective barrier was also fully charged and exuding even more power than before.

‘BLAM’

His attention was then pulled to a faraway explosion. In the distance, he could see some kind of strange red demon with horns. It was giving out the fluctuations of a nascent soul beast at the early stage. It was burning up the flying monsters around the city barrier in droves. After further inspection, he realized that it was a soul best and its owner wasn’t far behind.

This man was a bit further away throwing giant plasma covered fist. Each time his punch descended thousands of corrupt beings fell. The only thing that remained was their ashes along with the man’s boisterous laugh.

“Are you done?”

Zhang Liena moved out from the side, she glided towards her husband that was next to Mao Wuying.

“Yes, this is Elder Mao Wuying. He is the Divine Fist Sects Patriarch. There are also two other elders that I managed to heal.”

Liena nodded at the old man that was standing next to her husband while also giving him a formal hand-clasp and bowing combo. After they got acquainted it was time to move out. With so many nascent soul masters out here there was no reason to leave these monsters all up to Qiang.

“Elder Wuying I propose we clear up these demonic beings. We must then attack the creature at its lair before it’s too late. This monster uses the beings it corrupts to further its cultivation realm. If we leave it to its own devices it will swallow up these lands and no one will be able to stop it.”

This was Zhang Dong’s biggest fear. The monster leveled up by absorbing others, it was similar to how his old system worked. If he still had that then the beast wouldn’t pose a problem. He could probably farm all these monsters that it made and strengthen himself further.

This was impossible now, he would need to do it the old fashioned way by cultivating diligently. There was also the option of absorbing vast quantities of spiritual energy and adding that to his cultivation but that process was quite wasteful.

“Yes, I agree.”

Wuying wasn’t fully recovered just yet but he was more than enough to battle these monsters. Three nascent soul masters were added to their little army. All of them soon took off towards the protective barrier to get outside.

Zhang Dong looked around after getting out. The numbers had dwindled slightly but there were still a lot of those monsters around. The mist was getting pushed back by the radiations of the protective array which allowed even the core formation cultivators to move around freely. He could actually see Zhang Liu and Xue apprehending some people that were affected by the strange tentacle slugs.

Various colorful nascent soul ranked attacks descended down on the battlefield. Liena called forth her storm phoenix, Zhang Dong utilized his golden dragon to aid in the fight as well. His soul beast was able to discharge holy lightning passively which caused the mist to vanish wherever it went.

The three nascent soul elders from the Divine Fist Sect were a bit weakened. They couldn’t quite aid by summoning their soul beasts to battle but they could act as backline support. They pelted the monsters with ranged attacks from a safe distance, the beast started to fall like flies.

The monsters had no way of resisting the combined might of six nascent soul experts. Within a day’s time, they had managed to clean up the evil beings. The efforts to heal the affected humans would continue for a while. The most important thing on their agenda was going towards the ruins where the monster slumbered, it was finally time to bring the fight to it.

Chapter 260

The fog around the Divine Fist Sect was slowly clearing up. It didn’t fully go away but instead cleared up in a one-kilometer wide radius. When the cultivators standing on the walls tried to look beyond that they would only see the thick mist. If they listened closely they would also hear the strange shrieks of the monsters that lurked within it.

Down on the ground, the rescue initiative was in full swing. With the combined powers of all the nascent powerhouses, the beasts had been slain in a short amount of time. Some of the affected humans that weren’t too far gone were apprehended. They were now being kept in quarantine while the divine healers from both sects tried their utmost best in getting them under control.

The people from the Divine Fist Sect had a lot of their own members succumbing to the infection so they were motivated in getting their sect brothers and sisters a cure. With the live specimens that Zhang Dong caught and with Huo Fu’s medical expertise, a cure was being developed. A cure that didn’t require a nascent soul master versed in holy healing.

“I must thank you on behalf of this sect.”

Mao Wuying along with the other three nascent soul elders clasped their hands while standing opposite to the three grand elders from the United Element Sect. Huo Qiang just smirked while Zhang Dong nodded weakly.

“I’m glad that we could save some people but this isn’t quite over. The problem still remains, this mist is proof.”

He looked into the distance where the miasma was still lingering. The protective formation that was enhanced by him was keeping the fog away for now. With it pushed back the monsters wouldn’t be able to approach the sect ground.

Zhang Dong found it strange that this version of his old foe needed this mist. When he first came to this world there wasn’t such a requirement. The frenzied monsters could freely move through the lands but they weren’t as strong as the ones here. He could only attribute this to the monster being weakened or the starting area being some kind of special case.

“Elder Heng informed me that you have faced off against this monster before?”

Wuying asked while looking to Zhang Dong who nodded at the question.

“Yes, but back then it was much weaker. Only at the core formation level. It wasn’t that strong and it could only boast high regenerative capabilities. By the way, Elder Heng described it, it is probably the same demonic beast but it had probably advanced further. I fear that I underestimated its regenerative capabilities and it somehow survived our last encounter…”

Zhang Dong replied while wondering if this was actually the same version of the Cthulhu that he fought twice already. It could have been another one that laid dormant for one reason or another. If it was the one he previously met he hoped that with the current holy Dao that he possessed he would be able to deliver a finishing blow. By the looks of things, this version was susceptible to divine and holy energies. The mist that wasn’t able to penetrate here and the monsters that started burning up when they got closer to these divine energies were proof.

“Aye, the way this monster draws energy from other beings would explain how it could have gotten stronger in such a short period of time... First let me explain what happened on that day.”

Mao Wuying added his two cents, the story was close to what Fang Heng had reported. The sect leader only shone some light on how exactly the relic worked that they used. That item wouldn’t help them much though as it had crumbled to dust after activation.

From what the elder explained the item was a holy sword that was at the highest grade that a heavenly item could reach. It was also just a hilt with most of the blade broken.

“Some of the divine blade’s shards might still be in the monster's body. This might be just my guess but the creature should have trouble healing itself with our divine item inside of its body.”

This made a lot of sense, the Cthulhu that he knew was a creature that could heal itself from any wound. He had to disintegrate it into small particles to get rid of it both times. Even then it might have been the same one and survived.

It should have been able to mend itself from a wound like that. It looked like the divine energies that were inside that damaged blade proved more deadly to the beast. It had to even flee and send its underlings instead of attacking by itself.

“That does make a lot of sense. We will move towards the ruins where you found the monster, I must ask you to lend me a guide.”

“Of course United Sect Patriarch, we will aid you however we can…. but…”

Mao Wuying looked behind himself with a troubled look, Zhang Dong kind of knew why this old man was hesitating. His sect was now in shambles and they were down to four nascent soul masters. Even the lesser sects that were at the banquet had more manpower than they had now.

The man probably wanted to prioritize his own people and fighting that demonic creature might not be on his agenda. He was probably thinking about abandoning this city and seeking refuge elsewhere. If Zhang Dong told him to jump into the portal into his lands he would probably take him up on the offer instantly.

“I’ll guide them, sect leader!”

The one to step forward was Fang Heng, the man that he was most familiar with. He was a powerful nascent soul powerhouse so it would be nice to have him along for the ride. The other nascent soul elders didn’t trust him just yet. This was understandable as he just barged into this city not that long ago.
The fact that he was saving them without asking for anything in return was already raising some eyebrows. This wasn’t something a cultivator in Zhang Dong’s position would do for free. They could understand it if this creature had something like an immortal treasure but it looked like he was just killing it to save lives.

Was he a saint or was there some other reason that he was doing this? The people from the Divine Fist Sect were skeptical but they couldn’t really do much about it. They weren’t in the position to complain nor could they ask the other sect about their true motives.

“Are you sure Elder Heng? We could let another elder from the information pavilion do it instead? ”

Wuying wasn’t really keen on having one of his remaining nascent soul elders being the guide. He would rather use one of the core formation sect members instead. They were a bit more disposable. He wasn’t sure how this undertaking would work out and he had to look at the bigger picture here. Losing someone like Elder Heng would be a big blow to the sect’s future.

“I understand sect leader but our sect has a debt to repay to this man. I would like to aid him in this crisis, it is the least I can do.”

The old sect leader looked into Heng’s eyes and could see that the man had made a decision. It would be impossible to change it now as he knew that look well.

“I see that you have made up your mind Elder Heng…”

Zhang Dong stayed to the side and waited for the two old men to make up their minds. He didn’t care that much about who would guide him there but it would be better if it was Heng doing it. The man owed him one and was also a strong nascent soul cultivator that practiced divine arts. He would probably be a nice addition to his fighting force against the demonic beings.

“Are you finished?”

“Yes Senior Dong, I will guide you towards the ruins. I just have one more favor to ask of you…”

“Is it about Meili?”

Fang Heng nodded at the question. Zhang Dong knew more or less what the man wanted to ask about so he just spoke up first so that they wouldn’t beat around the bush for too long.

“If you are worried about her well being, don’t worry. We will open the gate and if you wish she and more of your family members can leave towards my sect. They will be safe there.”

Fang Heng just clasped his hands as a sign of gratitude. Zhang Dong and he discussed some things before the old man went away to inform his family. He and Meili would have some catching up to do.

The girl was hanging out with Zhang Xue in the background and the two were in the middle of contending with some red-haired youths. He recognized one of them at least, they all looked similar to his sect brother Qiang.

While the evacuation and healing were underway Zhang Liena moved over to Zhang Dong.

“Little Xue has it tough, the spawns of that idiot are always swarming around her.”

It looked like Liena wanted to go over there and deliver a few smacks with her fans to those boys. Zhang Dong just smiled before moving over to his wife to calm her down.

“Xue can take care of herself, they wouldn’t dare to do anything drastic, probably wouldn’t even be able to. Our little Xue is quite strong.”

Liena moved a bit closer, bumping her shoulder into Zhang Dong’s chest while the two looked at the youths messing around. They could see Liena’s younger sister moving into action and shouting at the young males. Liu was hanging in the background, Zhang Dong knew that the youth had given up on the notion that he would ever get rid of Nuana by this point.

Probably the fact that she was the little sister of the woman his master was married to only made it more difficult for him to deny her advances. He wasn’t one to interfere in their relationship as it wasn’t really his problem. He also got a chuckle out of how the little girl was overzealous and always seemed to cause chaos around her.

After a moment he looked to his own wife but before he could move his hand around her waist a sect member walked over to make a report.

“Sir, the gate is ready for activation. We are just waiting for your order. The preparations for departure are also underway, we should be ready within the hour. ”

He had to move away from his wife that turned away to the side, one emerald fan covering her face so that the interrupting sect member wouldn’t see the frown on her face. Zhang Dong was a bit worried about this sect member's future by how his wife was looking at him. He knew that she wouldn’t do anything drastic but he might find himself cleaning the beast stables, for a prolonged period of time.

“Begin the evacuation but keep it organized, we can’t have people panicking.”

He knew that some people would want to escape as quickly as they possibly could. Getting surrounded by strange mist and flesh-eating tentacle monsters would do that to you. Order had to be kept though and children came first, the adults would be last.

After wrapping things up here they would depart. More backup would be coming after the gate was opened in the form of his favorite battleship. It wouldn’t be able to fit through the gate on its own but with the spatial technology that this world had it wouldn’t have to. With it around, he could safely take more of his sect members to those ruins.

Chapter 261

The people from the Divine Fist Sect were all looking up into the sky. There they saw a massive flying ship made from iron. It dwarfed their own two flying vessels that were stationed next to it.

This ship had appeared out of nowhere after the United Element’s Sect had activated the teleportation gate again. A large group of cultivators arrived in a unique looking getup. One older man stuck out like a sore thumb with the strange cap and militaristic coat that he was wearing.

The ship was summoned up into the sky soon after and most of the people that arrived were stationed on it. The rest were just people that were bringing over some resources from the main sect like healing herbs and materials that had the holy or divine element to them.

Some of the cultivators from the Divine Fist Sect had decided to evacuate while most of them made the decision to remain here. They would wait for the word to arrive from their elder Heng. He and some other cultivators were going to investigate the ruins that started it all. It was believed that the monster that attacked them was probably lurking there and biding its time to recover.

It was agreed that Zhang Dong, Huo Qiang, and Zhang Liena would all travel towards that monster-infested location. They would take the ship and some of the core formation elders. With the two ships from the Divine Fist Sect would trek along. They would all remain close together and offer some covering fire if needed.

“Is everything ready?”

Zhang Dong asked while standing on the main deck with his hands crossed over one another. With him were Huo Qiang and his wife, the person he was calling out was the ship’s captain.

“Yes Sir, the Argonaut 1 is ready to depart.”

“Good, let us go, time is of the essence.”

The captain saluted his Patriarch and headed towards the ship's inner part. The three nascent soul elders watched the man depart together.

“What do you think?”

Zhang Dong posed the question to Qiang while the captain vanished behind a door.

“About the beasts? They weren’t anything special, the youngsters could probably clear them out themselves.”

The muscular red-headed man just shrugged as he didn’t seem very alert. It looked like he wasn’t taking any of this seriously. The monsters that he faced were all below the nascent soul level so he based their strength on that fact alone.

“Could you use that tiny brain of yours once in a while? Do you think my husband would arrange all of this if this mission wasn’t of the utmost importance?”

Zhang Liena scoffed while looking at Huo Qiang, Zhang Dong just stood to the side while trying not to break his poker face.

In reality, he wasn’t sure how strong the monster was now. It could very well have regressed in cultivation after getting hit by the Divine Fist Sect’s artifact. It would be a bit embarrassing if that was the case. It was better to be prepared though, it would be fine if they came over-prepared than the other way around.

“I sure hope not! I didn’t come all the way here to fight a weak demonic beast!”

Qiang lamented the thought of not getting to fight a strong monster. He was at a stage of his life that fighting weak core formation beasts wasn’t all that fun. The only joy left in his life was fighting with nascent soul level opponents but with their sect not being in conflict with anyone for a long time proved to be boring.

“I worry about your children, is only fighting in that rice-sized brain of yours?”

“At least all of my brain didn’t go to my chest!”

Huo Qiang was quick to fire back while pointing at Liena’s overdeveloped chest. It had gotten even larger than before due to the recent birth.

The pink-haired woman moved her emerald battle fans to cover that area while glaring at Qiang. Zhang Dong just wanted to facepalm as he just couldn’t get these two into one room for more than a minute.

They just constantly fought with each other, he feared leaving the sect for more than a few days. When Liena was pregnant she didn’t bump into Qiang that much so it was fine. But from now on he expected her to be more active, things might get dicey from now on.

He just feared that people from the Qiang faction and Liena’s side would start getting pulled into this mess. Yes, those existed even in his sect, each grand elder had their own people. They all had heightened status and would react to their grand elder’s mood swings in one way or the other.

“How impudent! You dare?”

Liena moved into a fighting position while Qiang smirked at the challenge. He was already itching for a fight. The problem was the bad timing and the place. Zhang Dong couldn’t have the two duke it out on his brand new ship. Luckily he knew how to get his wife to back away and forget all about it.

“W-what are you?”

It was a simple maneuver, he just moved in closer and lifted the woman up into his hands. The tactical princess carry was implemented and it was successful. Liena started squirming around in his arms for a moment or two but soon enough she had calmed herself down. The rage from her face had subsided and it was replaced with a blush.

“There, have you calmed yourself down, my wife?”

Liena just nodded while grumbling a bit, he could hear Qiang giving out a ‘Tch’ sound from the side. He had lost a sparring match which he was probably saddened by.

“And you Qiang, stop angering Liena, or the next time we spar I’ll be sure to give your pride and joy a good smack.”

Zhang Dong made a fist with his hand and glanced down. Qiang followed this gaze, he noticed that Zhang Dong was staring at his family jewels. This made him shrink back in a quick response while covering the thing between his legs with both his hands.

“You wouldn’t, senior brother… I still need that.”

“You sure? Think you had used it more than enough, maybe you should try living like a monk.”

After throwing a few jabs of his own he started walking away. Liena looked over her husband’s shoulder while being carried away and stuck her tongue out while lowering one of her lower eyelids down. This was the very same gesture she performed when Zhang Dong saw her all these years ago.

“It’s not fair, brother Dong always takes Liena’s side…”

Qiang pouted a bit but Zhang Dong wasn’t there to see it as he was already walking away. He moved towards his personal cabin with Liena in his arms. This caused the woman to fidget even more as a lot of sect members could see this show of affection. This only showed that the sect leader and his wife had a good relationship. The sect members didn’t have much to gossip about as this fact was already known by many.

“You know that he is annoying you on purpose, you are like a little sister to him.”

Zhang Dong placed Liena down on a couch after walking into his personal cabin. It looked quite cozy in here and the two would be able to relax here for the time being. The door would actually open only for him and no one else. Even if Qiang came or his disciples the doors would be closed until he allowed entrance.

“I know.... but I just can’t stand his face… that condescending face… Can’t we banish him from the main sect? It was so peaceful when he was ordered to patrol the borders.”

Liena asked with sparkles in her eyes. She was giving Zhang Dong the puppy eye treatment but he didn’t really want to abuse his sect leader position for squabbles between his wife and best friend.
“You know I can’t do that. Don’t want our children to copy things like that in the future…”

Zhang Dong was afraid to bring up a ‘Young Master type’ in the future. He was now a father; he didn’t want his children to have a stick up their butt. If they saw him abuse his power left and right they would think themselves above other people. Liena still had the old mindset of might made right, she wouldn’t be opposed to using her husband's position to her favor. He was slowly trying to change that side of her but it was a slow process.

“You are too lenient with him, his father also isn’t showing enough respect…”

Before Liena could go on a tangent about honor and prestige she found Zhang Dong’s finger up against her lip.

“Let’s not argue, we have other things to worry about for now.”

He sat down next to her on that couch but soon moved into one of his favorite positions. It was one that he preferred when he was alone with his wife. That was by placing his head onto her thighs, with this he had a nice view along with a soft spot to rest his head-on.

“Sometimes I forget how much of a child this husband of mine is…”

Liena gave out a sigh while petting Zhang Dong on the head with her hand. She could only smile down at the man that was rubbing his cheek against her thighs. When Zhang Dong did this she always wondered where the powerful sect leader she married had gone to.

“You’re the only one I can show this side, so be grateful to this great leader of yours!”

“Yes, I am very much grateful, my great leader.”

She petted his head one more time before feeling Zhang Dong’s hands wandering to certain places that they shouldn’t. The ship ride would take a day so the two had some time to kill. Zhang Dong was feeling stressed out by the whole demonic being debacle so his wife would have to help him out with that...

While the United Element Sect Matriarch and Patriarch were having a steamy encounter the rest of the cultivators were preparing to take off. The ship was now slowly moving through the protective barrier. The two smaller ships that the Divine Fist Sect had were moving behind it with Fang Heng on one of them.

Soon the argonaut moved to the back as it had to follow these ships towards the ruins. The people left behind in the city would have to wait with anticipation for their return. The gate with the path back to the United Element’s Sect would remain there for the time being. If the monsters from the mist were to breach the improved array everyone would have a way to evacuate.

Some people that were convinced that this sect was already done for had taken Zhang Dong’s sect up on the offer already. Most of the cultivators remained in place though, they believed that staying with their own till the bitter end was the correct thing to do.

“What do you think about this, sect leader?

Mao Wuying was hovering above the sect grounds with the other two nascent soul survivors. They looked at the ships vanishing into the mist, the grayish fog engulfed the large flying vessels till there was nothing left to see.

“We all faced that monster together… Prepare everything, when the time arrives we must be ready to leave…”

Chapter 262

Zhang Dong opened up his eyes and could see a uniform ceiling made from steel. There were various small gem light orbs embedded in it that shone in a dim yellow light. He rolled over to the side, what he witnessed was the sleeping face of his lovely wife right next to him.

He just remained there, not moving while staring at the wife of his children. She still placed importance on her face, the makeup that she wore only got more intricate with the years. He had tried to tell her that it was fine to go with a more ‘natural’ look. Whenever he mentioned that he could feel the daggers stabbing into him from her menacing stare.

He moved his hand over to her cheek, with the back of his hand he caressed it. He could feel Liena’s breath on his skin and she started to wiggle around. Before he could wake her up, he heard someone call out from the side.

“Patriarch, we will be arriving at our destination within an hour’s time.”

The voice was a bit choppy, it was coming from a console from the side that was connected to the Argonauts control room. He recognized the voice, it was the ship’s captain doing his report. This abrupt call out also caused his wife to finally wake up.

“Is that so, I’ll be with you in a moment.”

Zhang Dong called out to the disembodied voice of the ship’s captain while sitting up. He was still in bed, the only thing covering his naked body the silky bed sheets.

“We should get ready and prepare for battle.”

Liena rubbed her sleepy eyes for a moment, she could see Zhang Dong standing up and grabbing his robe that was on the side. The two started to redress themselves while looking at the mirror at the side.

Zhang Dong checked if he had all of his spatial rings present along with the weapons that he usually used. While doing this Zhang Liena moved over and straightened up his robe along with his disheveled hair.

“Give me a moment, I need to freshen up.”

“You look fine...Uh… nevermind.”

She gave him that face again so he decided to just let her redo her makeup. Something like that could take from a couple of minutes to even an hour. After leaving the room he headed to the ship's operating room where all the important people should be gathered.

“Greetings Patriarch!”

“Welcome Master.”

His two disciples were here as well but they were missing a certain Huo Qiang.

‘He never liked this type of gathering, he is probably on the bridge getting prepared for the coming battle.’

He nodded at the people that were greeting him while moving further inside. He remembered everyone in this room all thanks to his almost perfect memory. Being a cultivator at his level brought some perks with them. Knowing their faces was the only thing that he did, what their private lives looked like was something he wasn’t interested in. There was a certain barrier that wouldn’t be crossed.

He was the Patriarch and they were under him, having a personal relationship with them would be quite hard. The people here treated him like some kind of king, some even close to a divine being. They would perform any task he would give them. What they wanted in return was prestige and a chance for improving their cultivation. Everyone was aiming for the very top here, they all wished to ascend to immortality in one way or another.

“How does it look, Captain? Are there any dangers ahead of us?”

Zhang Dong asked while sitting down, he had a special seat prepared for just his use. All the other people were standing up straight not daring to do anything out of place in front of the sect leader.

“Reporting to the Patriarch! The trip has been smooth, the monsters that lurk in the fog are unable to pierce through our barrier. There were fewer of them left than we expected. We believe that most of the monsters from these lands were slain during the defense of the Divine Fist Sect.”

Zhang Dong rubbed his chin while listening. Apparently, the monster’s numbers weren’t unlimited. There were swarms of them back there, it was possible that the army was now thinned out.

“Mmm, prepare for battle either way. Even though the monsters aren’t appearing now, they could be lurking at the ruins to defend their master.”

It would be a good idea for the beast to pull back its armies to its lair. He wasn’t sure if the monster had a direct connection with its minions. After most of them were killed by him and his elders it would be smart for the demonic being to bunker up. They would probably experience heavy resistance at these ruins when they arrived.

“Is the radar picking them up?”

“This mist is blocking our devices, we can’t pierce through them beyond a kilometer. I’m afraid we will only know if the beasts are waiting for us after we arrive at our destination, my lord.”

He nodded while looking at the screen. There were a few red dots here and there which represented some flying monsters. There weren’t that many around, whenever they flew by the monsters would try to attack them. But they would disintegrate into particles whenever they slammed themselves into the Argonauts shield.
There were two large green dots in front of his ship which represented the two ships from the Divine Fist Sect. They had guided them towards this area, even in the mist, their navigators were able to traverse their land without a hitch. They weren’t going that fast but within a day they were not close to the previously found ruins.

Zhang Dong found it a bit strange that these ruins were only found recently. They weren’t that far away from the main sect city. They also weren’t in a particularly dangerous area from what he had heard.

“We will approach slowly, it would be unwise to rush in without any information. Make sure that everyone is ready for combat!”

He gave his orders while observing the indication on the big screen. He spread his senses outside and kept a close eye on everything. There were approaching the supposed lair of the monster, the first thing he noticed was the noise. The closer they got the fewer sounds he could hear.

During their approach just a few minutes ago he could hear the wails of strange monstrosities in the distance. There were even sounds of them slamming into their protective barrier but now, there was nothing. It was as if there was nothing here, the wind had even stopped howling.

‘Something isn’t right....’

“The wind… something is affecting it.”

He looked to the side, Zhang Liena was standing there back in her attire. She was the person most versed in the Dao of the wind so she noticed that something wasn’t right. Their eyes met for a moment and he nodded, it was time to go outside.

“Captain, remain vigilant. I and grand elder Liena will depart for the ship deck to examine the situation.”

It was time to leave and go outside. The two removed themselves from the room, Liu and Xue moved behind them while Nuana also approached from the side. The kids had joined them on this expedition but they were here more as observers. With the nascent soul masters around the core formation cultivators would only get in the way.

These youths at the core formation level could still aid the Argonaut with their cultivation. They could and would be stationed by the ship’s side cannons. There were many of those and they were constructed in a way that a cultivator could boost the cannon’s power with their own cultivation base.

“Finally you are out, the fun is about to start!”

Huo Qiang was sitting right at the tip of the ship’s deck. He was looking out into the cloudy void that was this mist. The two smaller ships in front of them were giving out light of their own. They were still hard to spot with the naked eye as the ships kept a large distance from each other.

“Fun huh? I hope that fun won’t be very deadly.”

Zhang Dong replied with a shrug while moving towards Huo Qiang and the tip of the ship. He tried to spread out his senses beyond this fog but it was quite good at blocking his internal sonar. He decided to use his system’s map function afterward but as before it was getting jammed.

He didn’t like where this was going, whenever his system was affected by anything it didn’t bode anything good. He was going to face off against a monster that he believed was brought with him to this world along with his system. By who and why was still unknown to him.

Zhang Dong hopped that he could shed some light on this mystery by taking the beast out. He had yet to encounter any more of those strange cube treasures that he had absorbed on two occasions. The person that appeared that one time was also suspicious. Was that person an ally or an enemy? It could just be a ploy of the being that brought him here.

He was scared that he was now some kind of plaything of a god-like existence. It could be a person at the immortal level of strength or even far beyond that. From what he knew there were no immortals left in this world at least none that were active. One could be hiding somewhere but not like anyone at the nascent soul level would be able to sense a cultivator of that prestige.

The silence continued for a few moments, the only thing that could be heard was the humming sound of the Argonaut’s engines. The silence was brought to an abrupt stop as one of the Divine Fist Sect’s ships went up in flames.

It was the one that was the furthest away from them. Zhang Dong could faintly see something large and slimy piercing this flying vessel from below. It looked like a giant trunk of a tree with many branches that were strangely moving around.

“Enemy Attack!”

The alarm sounded on the ship, the thumping steps of many cultivators were heard in the surroundings as everyone took off running. The side cannons sprung into action as everyone that was in one tried to focus on the enemy.

The two grand elders including the Patriarch from the United Element Sect reacted as well. They all focused their energies on the exploding ship, they weren’t attacking the strange ‘tree’ but trying to pluck the Divine Fist Sect cultivators that were falling down after the explosion.

Elder Heng who was responsible for their safety was also there. With the four powerful cultivators working together most of the ship’s crew was safely evacuated to the other two ships.
“Finally I was tired of waiting, it’s our turn now!”

Huo Qiang shouted out while pointing out with his finger towards the strange tree that was hard to see due to the mist.

The tip of Qiang’s finger started glowing in a deep crimson. Particles of red light converged onto the tip before a red beam of plasma shot forward. In a fraction of a second, it connected with the thing that pierced the ship.

“GUOHHH.”

A monstrous wail of pain was heard by everyone present after the attack connected. The mist was forcefully parted by Qiang’s attack to reveal the enemy’s true form. Instead of a large tree what they saw was a mass of flesh. The branches were just smaller squiggly tentacle appendages, on each of them a toothy mouth which was now screeching in pain after a large hole was blown open in the thick tentacle trunk.

“Everyone, Attack!”

The order was given, the large ship composed of spirit metal lit up brightly as its cannons started firing, the battle had finally started.

Chapter 263

A mist covered sky lit up in bright red after a large explosion. The source of this eruption was a large flying ship with sails. It was pierced by a monstrous appendage that was able to take it out in one attack.

This thing looked quite bizarre, dark in coloring, and made out of flesh. From it, a myriad of squiggly tentacles was wiggling around. Each one of them covered in mouths, these mouths weren’t uniform in design. They were a mix of beasts and humanoid creatures alike, the teeth on them looked to belong to carnivores as well as to herbivores.

The shrieks of a thousand creatures were heard from those flailing tentacles. Their cries were soon erased by a red beam of molten plasma. It connected with the thick dark tower of flesh and caused it to burn up. The tentacles attached to it went up in flames along with it while screaming in a high pitched wail.

“How’s that?”

“Qiang watch out, below you!”

Huo Qiang who was up in the air and also the first one to attack looked down. He was quick to react by dodging to the side as another large spire of flesh tried devouring him from below. This one actually looked more like a giant worm with a toothy mouth but it also had a lot of those slimy tendrils coming out of it.

“The mist is a lot thicker in this part...Captain, activate the formation!”

Zhang Dong called out while also moving down from the Argonaut. It was time to get his hands dirty and to help out his sect brother that was getting swarmed by some strange tentacle monsters. Zhang Liena wasn’t far behind as all of the nascent soul masters sprung into action. The other cultivators remained on the ship that was equipped to protect them.

The ship that went down belonged to the Divine Fist Sect. Fang Heng the man responsible for them was on the other ship but he was now hovering above it. There was enough time to evacuate the core formation elders onto the other flying vessel before the skyscraper-sized monster flesh trees got them.

Thanks to The Argonaut what they were facing would soon come to light. The large metallic ships' large array formation started glowing bright gold. Runic symbols started appearing on the bubbly like barrier before it started expanding outwardly.

Within a matter of moments, the whole ship lit up in a bright golden hue. It started pulsating with energy that was shooting outwardly in a burst of bright light. This continued for a time while causing the miasma around the area to get pushed back forcefully.

Finally, everything was appearing before them, the fog was clearing up. The people that were looking at the ship's screen and the ones that were outside to witness everything started gasping. What they saw was truly appalling, a sight that they didn’t expect to ever see.

Where everyone expected to see ruins or some sign of a city that was here, they witnessed flesh. Everything was covered in a layer of meat, squiggly living one to be exact.

What used to be the ground or the ruins were covered in a mountain of flesh. Tentacle-like appendages were protruding out of everything, strange mouths, eyes, even ears and noses were attached to that flesh. It was like out of a horror flick where some kind of alien monster had fused with every living being that it came across.

“What is all of this…”

Zhang Dong had to do a double-take over everything. He wasn’t sure what he was looking at, was this mass of flesh the Cthulhu monster that he was supposed to be facing? He tried examining everything with his system but it showed corrupt numbers and question marks over everything. Even it had trouble identifying what this thing was and he had a sinking suspicion as to why.

“This thing… it's made up of thousands… no millions of living beings... It has somehow fused with them together... “

He detected vast amounts of demonic qi coming from the creature below. It was on different wavelengths that brought him to his conclusion of it being composed of various living creatures, humans included.

The ship continued to send out waves of divine energy into the distance which helped in keeping the mist at bay. The tentacle mass below wasn’t all too happy about this fact and started thrashing its tower sized tendrils at the unwelcome guests. Luckily for Zhang Dong and his people, their ship was quite mobile and this monster below wasn’t the speedy kind, evading its attacks was manageable.

The Argonaut wouldn’t be taking a passive stance in this battle. The crew inside was ready and waiting. The ship was equipped with large spirit cannons that were powered by the ship's engine. Their power could be further boosted by the person using them. The order to attack was given long ago and the people were quite trigger happy.

A rain of various colorful projectiles descended from the sky. It was as if shooting stars were descending from above. These energy attacks collided with the screeching monster below, tearing into it while it tried to defend itself with its massive body of squiggly flesh. The sight wasn’t pretty as the moment the monster's body was pierced dark blood and pungent smell followed.

This wasn’t the only enemy that was waiting for them. There was a myriad of flying monsters separate from it coming their way. They were quite strong at the pinnacle of core formation and able to move even without the mist surrounding the area around them.

Zhang Dong looked at the monsters but he didn’t join the battle yet. The other three nascent soul elders had joined with the flying ships to support them but he was still looking around. There was something off about this whole place. The flesh monster did give off nascent soul fluctuations of energy but it wasn’t that strong.

The only thing it had going for it was its size. It didn’t look like it would be able to handle all of them, which would make this an easy victory for their side. From his experience when things looked too good to be true, most of the time they were. That is also why he remained vigilant while scanning for other enemies.

“What is that…”

It wasn’t long since the mist cleared out but now he noticed something. In the distance there was a strange structure, it was still composed of flesh and part of this monster. It looked like three arches coming together into one spot. At the spot that they connected was some kind of fleshy rope that dangled around.

It connected to a spherical object, due to the explosions it was swinging around. From it, he detected a strange energy signature. He focused more, listening in as he had a suspicion that this thing wasn’t anything simple.

“Is that a… heartbeat?”

Zhang Dong was quite far away from those flesh arches but he could tell that they were the size of 100 meter tall towers. The thing that was hanging down from it was close to their size but much wider, the more he looked at it the more it appeared to be some kind of egg covered in a fleshy membrane.

“Fuck… it’s in there…Qiang, Liena, help me out!”

Zhang Dong pointed at the egg-like object in the distance while trying to get his ally's attention. He didn’t like the way that thing looked and if his suspicion was correct it would be best to get rid of that thing as soon as they could.

The two were having their own battles in the distance but they were quick to react to his summons. Liena and Qiang looked to where Zhang Dong was pointing to. They could see the strange fleshy structure with a strange dangling egg in the middle. Even they could tell that there was something not right with that thing.

“What is that evil aura…”

Liena gasped.

“Could it be?”

Qiang narrowed his eyes while looking into the distance.

Zhang Dong just nodded while pointing out with his hand, his soul beast was summoned behind him and roared out. The other two didn’t wait long before summoning their own beasts. The red Ifrit radiated massive plasma energy while the Storm Phoenix brought storm clouds over.

The three moved their hands out while pointing their palms at the egg-shaped mass of flesh. Energy started gathering a few meters away from where they were standing as the three grand elders concentrated for a combined attack.

Green, red and gold energies started mixing with one another. The combined might of the three nascent soul elders caused everything to tremble around them. While the three were charging up, the mass of flesh below reacted.

It seemed like the monster wouldn’t just allow the humans to continue with their attack without retaliating. Soon various massive tentacles traveled towards them, on the tips giant mouths with teeth set on devouring the three young grand elders.

The three soul beasts that were hovering around the trio from the United Element’s sect wouldn’t just remain passive for this to happen. The massive beasts gave out a roar while charging towards the incoming tentacles. Their own mouth opened up wide and each one released a burst of energy that looked like an elemental breath attack.

Those masses of flesh weren’t strong enough to resist this burst of energy and started to crumble. This didn’t stop new ones to appear for a continuing surge of monster flesh. These tentacles reformed themselves almost as fast as they were burned up, showing off how good at regenerating themselves they were.

Luckily the three soul-beasts were capable enough to overwhelm the regenerative abilities of this being. This gave enough time for the three elders to gather their nascent soul energies in one spot.

It started from a tiny fingertip-sized orb in the center. It gave out a burst of energy while expanding into something the size of a basketball. The three types of energies were combining into one which made it look like a taijitu.

Soon the three were finished with concentrating and a massive torrent of spiritual energy was released. It looked like a massive beam of light that was composed of three dragons. They all shot towards the strange-looking egg while circling around themselves. They converged into one three colored dragon before connecting with their target, the explosion sent shockwaves into the surrounding causing the flying ships to buckle under pressure.

The cultivators that were lighting up the sky with cannon fire stopped with their attacks. They all looked to the distance where the three grand elders sent their attack towards. What remained there was a mushroom cloud and dust, probably anything that was there was incinerated into nothingness. Any parts of that flesh monster that connected to that spot were crumbling into dark dust.

“Was that it?”

Huo Qiang called out while crossing his muscular hands together, his tone indicating his disappointment.

“Let us hope so, I don’t want to remain in this evil place for much longer.”

Liena replied while fanning herself a bit. Zhang Dong didn’t chime in as he just squinted and looked into the distance. Then his eyes jolted open wide while he bolted for his wife. Liena gave out a surprised yelp while getting pulled to the side by Zhang Dong. A fraction of a second later a giant black beam of light shot towards where the three grand elders were standing.

A massive howl could be heard from the spot the three fired their combined attack. That was also the spot from where the dark beam of evil energy shot from. The dust started to slowly settle revealing a huge monster lurking within.

Chapter 264

The monster had a vaguely anthropoid outline, but with an octopus-like head whose face was a mass of feelers that some would call tentacles. Its body was covered in scales while also having a rubbery looking body texture to it. It had a somewhat humanoid shape, two legs with two arms, its hand and feet had prodigious claws. Behind it was a set of long webbed narrow wings that looked more like a decoration than a functional appendage meant for flight.

Quasi-thulhu [ Nascent Soul Great Circle ]

Zhang Dong looked at this creature, it looked almost exactly like the other two creatures he had faced. The biggest difference was its size, it was well over a 100 meters. It had probably burst from that egg sack that they fired upon. It was very surprising that it had survived, its regenerative abilities were probably further enhanced than before. Then he had to take its cultivation realm into account, with a nascent soul this creature would even live if its physical body perished.

‘This isn’t going to be easy…’

Zhang Dong bit his bottom lip while the monster started at him. There were some superficial wounds from the attack that it took but they were quickly healing in real-time. Before he could think up another strategy a certain overzealous friend of his shouted out from the side.

“So this is this beast? I’ll take care of it!”

Huo Qiang slammed his fists together while they glowed in a crimson hue. Various runic patterns appeared on the armor gauntlets that he was wearing. His soul beast howled out along with its master as both of them charged towards the massive monster.

“That idiot…”

Zhang Dong wasn’t fast enough to stop his battle happy ally and had to watch as he charged forward. He could only follow him after also powering up. His body gave out a golden sheen before he burst towards the dark green being, Zhang Liena close behind him with her Storm Phoenix soul-beast with her.

The pair of husband and wife looked at each other while nodding. Instead of following behind their overzealous red-haired friend, they decided to flank the monster from the sides. Dong moved to the right side while Liena took the left one. The plan was to do a pincer attack while the beast was contenting with Huo Qiang.

This Quasi-thulhu didn’t seem that perturbed by the previous attack that it received. It wasn’t moving at all, its face tentacles squiggled around while its yellow eyes scanned the surroundings. The three nascent soul cultivators that were flying towards it looked like small flies, their soul beasts were slightly larger but they didn’t look like they would stand a chance against this massive creature.

Size wasn’t everything in this world though, a larger frame brought more power with it but it also reduced mobility. It would probably be easy to hit this monster but would it be enough to bring it down to its knees? Huo Qiang was now charging up an attack to test his mettle.

Huo Qiang moved his fist back while flying forward on a collision course with the Quasi-thulhu’s massive squid face. His body was surrounded by red plasma energy, most of it was flowing right into that huge fist of his. the Plasma Ifrit was right behind his master, his body was mirroring this punching motion as both of them flew forward.

Qiang’s spiritual energy exploded causing widespread destruction. Storm-like winds were caused by the eruption of speed and power. Anyone that was witnessing this attack gulped hard while stopping in their tracks to stare.

The powered-up fist was finally thrown forward, the Ifrit that looked like it was standing behind its master was somehow absorbed into this fiery attack. Its whole body was sucked into a chaotic mass of spiritual energy that collided with the unmoving monster’s face.

A massive discharge of fire-based energies occurred. The flying ships that were in the distance started rocking back and forth as even they were affected by the eruption of plasma.

This wasn’t the end of it as Zhang Dong and Liena closed in from the sides as well. Both of them were ready to produce their own version of this attack.

Liena motioned towards the monster’s side with her emerald fan. The bird made of lightning and wind energies gave out a screech before turning into a mass of spiritual energy. It descended on its target in the form of a giant thunder filled twister. The tornado slammed into the monster's side while spinning around and burrowing itself deeply into its flesh, trying to tear it to bits.

Zhang Dong was the last one to produce an attack. He held two of his fingers toward the enemy while holding his hand in a sort of gun shape. It didn’t take much time for his fingers to glow in a bright golden color. A bolt of golden energy shot out, arcs of electricity were surrounding it as it traveled at a speed that couldn’t be followed by a regular person’s eyes.

A thunderous noise filled the whole area as three of those nascent soul level attacks collided with the monster. Each of them hit one after another before causing a massive explosion of spiritual energy.

Zhang Dong and Feng Liena moved back a bit while floating in the air. The discharge of their attacks caused another cloud of smoke to form. Even with their enhanced senses, it was hard to tell what was happening inside. They needed to wait for the chaotic energies to disperse before knowing if the monster was affected by their attacks.

They were sure of one thing though, the beast didn’t doge at all and took the brunt force of their attacks. Those attacks were at a level of a late stage nascent soul cultivator. Someone like Zhan Jie that Zhang Dong faced previously would be dead three times over if he was hit by all three of those attacks.
It took more time for the smoke to clear up. Huo Qiang floated back as well while grimacing. He had his hands crossed over one another with his chest puffed out. On his face a slight frown of annoyance.

“Senior brother, why did you interfere? Now the monster is dead!”

Zhang Dong’s brows quivered as he heard his junior brother boasting around. He didn’t know this creature too well so he wasn’t understanding the gravity of the situation. When the smoke was slowly clearing away the truth was revealed.

Quasi-thulhu was just standing there but it was missing part of its head. Part of it had been blown off right through. One of its yellow eyes was missing while black blood oozed out from the wound. Huo Qiang could see right through this hole to the other side, the hit looked like it punched right through the creature’s brain.

On the sides where Zhang Dong and Liena attacked there were visible holes as well. The creature was missing its massive arms that had fallen down to the ground. For all intents and purposes, the squid monster looked to be defeated. It wasn’t moving much and the only thing coming out of it was black blood.

Before everyone could rejoice, the mass of flesh that was all around this area started getting feisty. It was fighting against the two flying ships with all its might but its huge size proved to be a weakness. It just couldn’t land a clean hit on any of those floating vessels now after the moment of surprise was gone.

While the three grand elders were looking at the unmoving monster the mountain of flesh started retreating towards them. Zhang Dong was the first one to spot this anomaly which caused him to back away while alerting his wife.

“Something is wrong, get back!”

Huo Qiang was the only one unconvinced, to him the battle was already won so he just looked around while floating. Liena listened to the advice of Zhang Dong and backed away while protecting herself with a shield made of green spiritual energy.

The surrounding area that was mostly composed of the fused being of flesh started getting sucked up. This caused the destroyed ground to be visible as the being made up of flesh started to get smaller. While this was happening the squid-faced monster started moving around.

The giant gaping hole that was made through its brain started mending itself. Tiny tendrils started squiggling around and transforming themselves into new flesh while connecting broken ones.

The destroyed arms turned into fleshy tentacles as well while moving themselves back into place. The whole process didn’t take that long and Zhang Dong along with his companions could only watch with surprise as the huge monster mended itself back. It only took about fifteen seconds for the beast to be back at full health. There were no visible outside wounds to the monster and it also didn’t seem to have used up much spiritual energy to perform this task.

This wasn’t quite the end of the spectacle happening here. The previously formless mass of flesh, mouths, and tentacles started transforming. Two large spires of meat appeared right next to where Quasi-thulhu was standing. They started taking form, with time the two transformed into grotesque monsters of their own with now a visible cultivation level that put them at the nascent soul late stage level of power.

Their forms weren’t much better than their friend’s. The two were smaller than Quasi-cthulhu but not by much. One was a giant floating eye with many appendages coming out of its bulbous body. Some of them looked like ordinary tentacles, some like human or ape-like arms. Some looked like insectoid appendages with sickle blades like a mantis would have.

The second one had a taur-like look to it. The lower half of its body looked like it belonged to some kind of four-legged beast with large talons on its feet. The top part was a bit more humanoid with a torso and four arms. Its head was mostly just teeth and a giant mouth with no eyes. Its eyes were placed on the shoulder part of the more humanoid section of its body.

Zhang Dong tried identifying these monsters with his system window but what he was getting was corrupt letters and numbers.

!@&$@#SDF21# [ Late Stage ]

&$@#^#GD^& #!%^SD [ Late Stage ]

He could at least see their power levels but he could feel that the two monsters were at the very top of that ranking. If he compared them to the Dark Palm Sect Patriarch that he fought they would come up on top without much of a problem.

Quasi-thulhu gave out a massive angry shout that caused the sound waves to push everyone back even the nascent soul fighters weren’t safe from it. Everyone protected themselves with their own skills while backing away. Even Huo Qiang’s haughty attitude had changed after seeing the other two monsters appear.

“Gather up everyone, This isn’t a fight we can continue without a strategy!”

Zhang Dong sent a message to the ship’s captain to aim for the floating eyeball of a monster. They would need to split their fighters between these huge demonic beings. The plan of surrounding the boss of the two had failed. Now they had to contend with other enemies that were almost as strong as the main one.

“Let me aid you!”

Fang Heng finally showed up while the ship with his sect members retreated behind the Argonaut.

“Glad to have you on board…”

Zhang Dong frowned a bit while looking at the large monster in front of him. His body started radiating energy while expanding in size.

Chapter 265

...5...10...25...65...85...100...110… meters, Zhang Dong’s old Avatar form finally saw being used today. He matched the Cthulhu look alike in size but he was still half a head shorter than it was. It didn’t seem like this massive monster would be easily killed with its regenerative capabilities. It also looked to be on the more sluggish side which made this form more useful in this fight.

This new Avatar form technique was a bit different than the old one. For one thing, it utilized Zhang Dong’s soul-beast giving him less energy based qualities. He looked more like a golden statue covered with scales, lightning bolts and electric arcs were shooting off his whole body just as before.

His body refining skill also came into play here. He had already pushed it further than his Qi cultivation at this point. Making heavenly grade items was something that he was already proficient in.

This left him able to absorb them through the years, he was still restricted to the late stage as the resources were limited. Getting to the great circle stage would just bankrupt his entire sect. It was also not feasible due to a bottleneck that didn’t exist with the previous versions of this body refining technique.

Now he actually needed to absorb a higher grade of item each time he moved a small realm up. This posed a big problem as there were no weapons that he could craft that would be of the very height of heaven grade. He lacked both the skills, knowledge, and resources to push through that threshold. Any tiny mistake would cause the weapons he made to degrade. This process needed perfection, this he could only achieve with time and crafting experience.

Zhang Dong’s new and improved Avatar form took three of his aspects and combined them into one. With it, he lost some maneuverability and he couldn’t use most of his weapons. This form’s biggest attribute was its resistance and sheer power. He didn’t take the time to name it properly, he also didn’t have anyone to pass it onto either. This was a technique that he customized for his special constitution. Passing it on to his disciples wasn’t possible as they lacked his metal-like body refining technique.

The Cthulhu look-alike finally became active, after getting hit multiple times without retaliating it was time for it to strike. Black miasma surrounded its body, it looked thick and was even dribbling down to the ground. The moment a droplet of this dark-green liquid fell down it burned a hole right through the hard rock.

The monster opened up its large mouth to gather energy. Particles of dark qi were condensed into a smaller point right in the middle of that tentacled face. Luckily Zhang Dong remembered this type of attack as he had seen it once before when he was fighting this creature in his demon hunter disguise.

He was quick to throw an uppercut to that squiggly chin. It connected at about the same time that the monster fired off its attack. This caused another explosion to detonate, right inside the monster's toothy mouth. The dark rays of energy shined through to the outside, anything they touched died instantly. Plants wilted, rocks shattered into dust and even the small particles were affected.
Zhang Dong’s face that was in his avatar form was unmoving but in reality, he was trying not to show the amount of pain that he was in. It was only one punch but his whole fist felt like it had punched through a cactus. It felt like a million tiny needles were inserted into his knuckles at the same time. His only explanation was this black miasma that the creature was covered with. It was similar to acid and caused an excruciating amount of pain.

He couldn’t stop now though, he needed to follow this momentum. After the uppercut followed a straight punch to the exact same spot. The monster’s face caved in fully and it was pushed back. It looked like Zhang Dong had the advantage, the monster was getting pummeled by his giant form.

The people on the ship were all hidden inside and either manning the cannons or ready to repair anything if they got attacked. Before anyone could cheer the monster finally retaliated. While being forced back by the second punch it swung one of its giant arms toward Zhang Dong’s face. He reacted by putting up his guard but he was still pushed back.

The massive claws dug into his forearm that was used for defending. They ripped through his giant golden form causing dark-colored claw marks. The poison that was on the tips of those claws seeped in while Zhang Dong retreated in pain. His forearm that had a deep golden hue started turning black.

He wanted to scream but managed to hold it in. He grasped his injured arm and started injecting golden energy into it. With some time the evil Qi was pushed back and he recovered. The same was true for the monster, its head that was missing was now fully reformed and it looked just fine. It shouted out once more while charging another mouth beam, this time around Zhang Dong wasn’t close enough to interrupt this attack.

While Zhang Dong found himself in a pickle he noticed that his wife and Fang Heng was behind him. They were in the middle of their own battle facing off against the monstrous centaur looking deformity. If he dodged to the side there was a possibility of the two being hit. The beam that this monster could shoot off was quite wide and was also very toxic. He was somewhat protected by his holy Dao. His companions on the other hand would not be able to recover as easily as he could if they got hit.

He decided to take it head-on. He covered his face with his arms in a protective position while focusing. Before the monster fired off its dastardly beam he started gathering his holy energies. His body began shining once more and a thin layer of golden lightning energy gathered around his arms that he was using for blocking.

There wasn’t quite enough time for him to produce a proper quality shield but it would have to be enough. The torrent of evil energy condensed around that squidly mouth of the Cthulhu analog creature. It shot towards Zhang Dong’s upper body which was a stroke of luck for him as that was the spot that he was defending the most.

When the beam impacted a loud thundering sound was heard. His entire body was shrouded in black energy and anyone or anything that was in close proximity was pushed back. Zhang Liena, Huo Qiang, and even the Argonaut weren’t able to hold themselves in place. The two monstrosities that they were fighting were affected as well, both of them tumbled back while actually receiving some residual damage from their boss’ attack.

“Senior Brother!?”

“Zhang Dong!”

Both Liena and Qiang shouted out as they both saw what transpired. A similar mushroom cloud was produced in the spot that Zhang Dong was standing. Both of them wanted to jump in to aid in his battle but before they could act the two monsters they were fighting resumed their attacks.

Quasi-thulhu howled in a strange way, it was as if it was laughing. After the smoke had cleared the golden form of Zhang Dong could finally be spotted. It was a lot less shiny than before, his forearms that he used for blocking were brownish-green. It looked as if he was being affected by the corrosive properties of this attack. Even he wasn’t able to fully resist it.

But he would have to, he didn’t think his allies would do much against this monster. If he canceled out his avatar form at this moment, there was a danger of succumbing to this poison. He was many times stronger in this form than without it, even with it fully activated he was receiving damage over time.

‘How am I supposed to kill this thing… Should I try the pulsar technique? But that technique takes forever to charge…’

The only techniques that were plausible against this thing took an ample amount of time to perform. He could try doing it like last time with his swordsmanship but this monster was much bigger than before. Cutting it up into tiny cubes before disintegrating it would not be possible. It would probably out regenerate those strikes and he had to be careful of its offensive capabilities as well.

After receiving a simple claw strike and a simple Qi discharge his fighting capabilities had already dropped. He was losing copious amounts of Qi while healing himself as this demonic spiritual energy was draining him of his own healing powers.

The beast wouldn’t give him much time to strategize as it lunged forward. Its webbed wings spread wide while it growled. Those tentacles on its face squiggled around as it opened its mouth.

Zhang Dong had one advantage over this monster. He actually knew how to fight, this beast obviously was only good at overpowering its opponents. The attacks it used were easy to read and rudimentary. It was telegraphing all of its strikes, the way it moved it body made it easy for Zhang Dong to read its intentions.

Quasi-thulhu went for quite the tactic as it attempted a bear hug. It was probably aiming to grab its opponent and then deliver a murderous bite. Zhang Dong was quick to react by stepping to the side, when the monster flew past him, he delivered a palm strike to the side of the monster’s scaly body.

If this being had human anatomy then the blow would probably be a crippling one. It would at least take the air out of its lungs but instead, it only made it angrier. Quasi-thulhu shouted out while quickly generating dark energy on its claws. It aimed for Zhang Dong’s head but he was already able to read this move. He bobbed his head to the side and managed to slide his hand in right over for a counter punch.

This blow sent shockwaves into the surrounding area. If a core formation cultivator was flying unprotected around this battle he would find himself blowing up into small bloody meat chunks. The spiritual energies that these two were producing were just far too massive for any normal person to stomach. Even Huo Qiang and Zhang Liena needed to move away from the two giants.

It looked like the United Element Sect’s Patriarch had everything under control. He was dancing around this monster delivering blow after blow. Each time his kick or punch connected part of the monster’s body exploded. The problem was that afterward it mended itself back to its previous state.

Zhang Dong was slowly losing out, if this fight continued for too long he knew that he would run out of stamina. He was still only someone at the middle stage of the nascent soul realm. He was fighting an opponent two small realms above him. Even with his better cultivation method, he would tire out before it and he wasn’t as proficient at healing himself as his opponent.

‘Shit… what should I do…’

He dodged another blow while delivering a massive energy-filled palm strike to the monster's back. He injected his lightning energy along with his holy qi into the spot he hit making it explode. But when he was pulling his hand away it was already mending itself back into place.

Then he saw it, before the wound closed itself fully there was something he noticed. It was tiny compared to the monster and him but it was there. It was an item that he was familiar with why it was in the creature's body was unknown.

“Why is that there… did this thing absorb it… or is it powering itself through it…”

His eyes shone a bit as he quickly thought up another plan, with this new discovery he might stand a chance.

Chapter 266

The monster roared at Zhang Dong that looked like a giant electrified golden statue. Both of them were now in a contest of strength with their fingers interlocking. No one was giving their enemy an inch but also neither of them was able to move. The creature and the cultivator seemed equally matched in strength at least for now.

After a moment Zhang Dong’s golden fingers started changing in color, they shifted into an unhealthy looking dark green. The monster’s evil energy was seeping into his hands while expanding like tiny spiderwebs. Before this corruption could continue the monster received a swift strike to its nether regions.

It was kind of odd to see the monster’s face convulse in pain after receiving this strike. The tentacles that were on its face weren’t the only dangly bits that this Cthulhu possessed. It had apparently some humanoid traits with some common weaknesses with this being one of them.

The monster’s grip loosened up after the swift smack to its more squishy lower organs. Thanks to this Zhang Dong could move his hands back while also delivering a swift palm strike to the beast’s chest. This strike caused a large shockwave to travel far and wide, causing even more destruction to the whole area.

‘Where is it… I’m sure it’s in there… I need to take it out…’

Zhang Dong was looking at the hole that he blasted into the monster’s chest with his palm strike. It took a few moments for it to close up but this was enough time for him to spot a tiny metallic object inside that opening. It was something he was familiar with and also something that he was looking for all these years.

It looked like a regular cube, similar to the ones he found in that secret ground and below the area where he was teleported into this world. It looked slightly different, it was pitch black and radiating a strange menacing demonic energy. The previous ones that he encountered weren’t like that. They mostly had regular spirit energy stored in them and acted as some kind of batteries or storage devices.

Somehow this device that was connected to him arriving in this world was inside that monster. Was this ruins a spot that a previous person that was spirited away arrived at? Maybe this thing was their tutorial monster, maybe they perished during it and it was left here to its own devices?

There were a lot of these scenarios going through Zhang Dong’s head right now. How it got there wasn’t that important but how this could help him in defeating this monster was.

He knew that these cubes stored a massive amount of spiritual energy in them. During the fight with the old Pride Demon all those years ago he was able to raise his cultivation level to a new height thanks to it.

This cube looked corrupt by the monster’s demonic energies. Zhang Dong had a suspicion that it was using this cube as a power source. The one he found below his initial summoning spot had a lot more energy in it than the one at the sacred grounds.

There was probably another spirit vein down here, or there was one at least. It was possible that the monster somehow fused with it after suffering injuries from the Divine Fist Sect relic weapon. How and why wasn’t important but now he had constructed a plan of action, there was some hope.

He only needed to get that tiny thing out of the creature’s body. The problem was that he had tried blasting several holes in this Cthulhu monster but the cube wasn’t there. He had used his spiritual sense to focus on it. This thing was moving around the monster’s body at a random pattern.

Whenever he tried getting to it, it shifted to another spot and got away. The monster was also quite resistant, even though he was blowing chunks out of it, most of his energy was consumed during this task.

After the initial strike, the cube dived back into the monster’s body to another part of it while the wound was mended. This had continued for several minutes, he was now slowly running out of stamina. The previous test of strength was proof enough, he was weakening.

Huo Qiang and Zhang Liena were further away. Fang Heng and the Argonaut were supporting those two from a distance. The ship was constantly firing its many cannons while moving around in the air. The nascent soul cultivator performed his own ranged attacks that utilized his Divine Dao.

The two monster helpers weren’t easy foes though. They had similar healing capabilities to their master. They weren’t as strong as the foes Zhang Dong was fighting but they were also battling against weaker opponents. Both sides were at a stalemate for the time being but the biggest problem was the main demonic being that was facing off against Zhang Dong.

It was much stronger than anyone here and Zhang Dong was barely contending with it. Was it not for his battle sense he would have gone down for the count a long time ago. A direct hit from the monster’s massive fists or claws would be enough to topple the golden giant. In his smaller form, he would not be strong enough to deliver enough damage to the monster.

He also contemplated trying to invade the monster’s body in his regular size to get to the cube but gave up on that idea quite fast. The monster was a shapeshifter and it could consume other people into its body. If he entered its insides he would probably find himself attacked by the inner organs, consumed in a matter of seconds by the demonic energy that was at the great circle of the nascent soul level. He was just not strong enough to resist them in his regular form.

For now, he decided to focus on the cube. That thing looked like it might be responsible for this creature’s might. If it was fueling it, after its removal it should drop to a weaker state, maybe even revert to the core formation level. If it was that weak he would be able to crush it between his fingertips.

So he tried again, this time around he used some of his reserves to activate another improved version of his old technique. He clasped his hands together, this combined with his golden form made him look like a giant Buddhist statue that was praying.

His body started to shine brightly, golden lightning bolts started shooting out of his back into the surroundings. A sound of shifting metal could be heard as his body started to change. A new set of arms erupted from his body. Those arms appeared right below his shoulders, soon another set of arms sprung out making him look as if he had six of them now.

Each of those arms opened up their hands while blue energy gathered. Soon each one was holding a sword made from lightning energy. This was one of his original techniques that he was sent to this world with, the Thunderlight sword. He had trained it up to perfection throughout the years as well as brought it towards the nascent soul level of strength.

With the six swords in hand, he charged towards the massive opponent that was already healed up. The monster didn’t just stand there as it blasted him with more demonic energy. He had to force his way through it while defending himself with the swords but when he got in range the slicing started.

He was like a machine, the plasma-induced swords started chopping Quasi-thulhu’s body into small pieces. His swordsmanship expertise showed as the body was carved up. His gaze was focused not on the damage he was doing but at the moving treasure inside the monster. He constantly tried hitting it with this thunderlight sword but each time he swung down the tiny object moved to another section of the monster's body.

The only thing he could do was to follow its movements while chopping parts of the monster up. The less body there was to travel through the easier it would be for him to get it. Time was of the essence as he knew that he wouldn’t be able to keep this up for long. The monster’s arms, legs, and even head were now falling down to the ground but he still wasn’t finished. Soon most of its torso was coming apart which left the small cube not much space to maneuver.

‘Damn I can’t hold it…’

The thunder swords started sizzling out of existence. His spiritual energy was almost drained now but he wasn’t giving up just yet. He moved his arms towards the part of the monster’s body that had the cube in it. All six of them were plunged inside of this demonic being but the moment they did Zhang Dong could feel that something was wrong.

When he sunk his hands into the monster he didn’t feel much resistance but he couldn’t stop now. With his six hands still there, he managed to force the cube into a corner, and finally his giant digits managed to grasp it in place.

The moment they did though, he felt a massive jolt of fear run through his body. With all his might he started pulling, his hand that was holding the small object jerked back but he was unable to remove it from the monster’s oversized body.

Then it happened, the sliced up parts started moving back towards the chopped up body. Zhang Dong’s multiple hands started vanishing which left him with two of his original ones. One was deeply stuck in the monster’s body while he was using the other one to try and push himself back to freedom.

Before he knew it he was getting pulled inside of the monster’s body. The corrupt cube was stuck in there with his whole fist around it. He just couldn’t yank himself free from the monster’s clutches. No matter how much he pushed, pulled, or even discharged his golden lightning into this demonic being it wasn’t budging an inch.

He could feel the monster slowly absorbing his body. His golden form started corroding into a brownish color. Dark cracks started forming on his hands and face as he started to show signs of breaking. If he didn’t get out of here he would certainly get consumed by this monster.

‘I… I can’t…’

He found himself unable to budge from his spot, canceling out of his transformation to get smaller was being blocked. The monster’s demonic Qi was somehow affecting his state. Activating the system’s teleportation function was also not working, things looked dire.

Zhang Dong looked around hoping to find something that could aid him. His gaze landed on the Argonaut that wasn’t that far off. It was bombarding the large eyeball along with Huo Qiang that looked somewhat beat up.

He steeled his resolve and sent a quick message to the ship’s captain. The man in question was sitting in his large chair as he received a red prompt on his monitor. There was a clear order there, the man grimaced but would comply with the Patriarch’s edict.

The man stood up from his seat which brought attention to him. He remained silent without uttering a word while looking out to the large screen. On it, he could see the golden giant wrestling with the monster. With each passing moment the golden glow was dimming, this made him realize why the Patriarch gave him such an order.

“The order has been given, activate the Gungnir. Aim… aim for the Patriarch!”

Chapter 267

Zhang Dong was grasping the cube with his giant golden hand. He could feel its corruption even without examining it with his system. In his previous encounters, he only needed to touch this type of cube and he would either get a prompt to absorb its power or it would happen automatically. In this current situation, this wasn’t happening, the cube was somehow absorbed into this creature’s structure.

There wasn’t much he could do in this situation. He was slowly getting absorbed into this creature as well, the only reason he wasn’t already dead was his holy dao. It was sufficient in pushing the demonic energies away but it also had its limit. Maybe if he was also in the great circle like this monster then he could overpower this power leech but at his current level, it was impossible.

The only thing he could do now is buy time for his battleship to charge its main cannon. That thing was powerful enough to even kill him when fully energized. He could see the ship slowly moving towards his direction while the front part transformed. The cannon slowly expanded while pointing towards him, in a few seconds the moment of truth would be upon him.

It might have seemed that he was committing suicide by battleship cannons but that wasn’t his plan. The beam of concentrated spiritual energy wasn’t for him but for the cube inside the monster. If it was destroyed he theorized that this monster would suffer a backlash, thus losing most of its cultivation base. Even if he got injured Huo Qiang and Feng Liena would be enough to finish it off in that state.

“What are you doing?”

Before the ship could blast away at him he heard a voice from afar. It belonged to his wife Zhang Liena, her soul-beast was surrounding the centaur looking monster with green cyclones while she on the other hand was flying his way. She had noticed that the ship was powering up and also who it was aiming at.

“Don’t come closer, I’ll be fine.”

He sent her a message while also prompting the ship’s captain to hurry up with charging the cannon.

“Captain, overload the engines, fry the systems if you have to, I can’t hold this thing for long…”

His glowing golden form was slowly flickering. The black miasma was engulfing him from head to toe. The creature’s squid face was in close proximity to his own. Zhang Dong inserted some of his reserves to his forehead to deliver a headbutt to its face. The monster’s head flew backward but this wouldn’t keep it from giving up, it would soon regenerate while trying to swallow him whole.

“You’re not fine at all…”

Liena wasn’t hearing any of it as she transformed into a green beam of light and headed towards Zhang Dong’s position. She was clearly unwilling to just let her husband be blasted by the giant ship’s cannon.

“Stop!”

Her approach was halted though by one of her allies. In front of her was Huo Qiang, he was slightly beaten up from fighting the large eyeball but the monster was now contending with his soul beast. It wouldn’t be held for long though.

“What are you doing, get out of my way Qiang!”

“Senior brother told me to stop you…”

“You…”

Liena looked into the distance, Zhang Dong in his giant form was slowly getting engulfed by a mass of dark green flesh. His golden color was dimming and the ship was almost done with charging up its main cannon. Liena knew that she wouldn’t be able to get Huo Qiang out of the way at least not in time to help her husband. She would still try…

“Get out of my way, or die!”

She took out a certain item from her spatial ring. It looked like an emerald badge with a green phoenix engraving on it. She held it out in front of her and injected it with her spiritual energy to activate it.

“You’re going to use that thing on me?!”

Huo Qiang put up his guard while looking at her. He knew well what the thing she was using was. He backed off while looking at her and his own soul beast that was wrestling with the giant eyeball monster.

Qiang wasn’t sure what he should do, he promised Zhang Dong to stop Liena for her safety and he would carry out that request. He knew very well what his senior brother was doing was very dangerous. He had trust in him, he believed that he would be fine but Liena would need to stay back for his plan to work.

The problem was the item that Liena was holding. It was a special device that was gifted to her by Zhang Dong. Qiang himself was waiting for one of his own but Zhang Dong told him that he would need to wait as there weren’t enough resources to go around just yet.

He put up his guard as he continued to block Liena’s way. The woman’s body started glowing in green color while the emerald badge floated towards her sternum. It attached itself a bit above that ample bosom which after an even shinier glow covered her body.

In a fraction of a second Liena’s body started getting covered by metallic parts. They covered her entirely, from head to toe in a suit of armor. This armor had an intricate streamlined design that complimented Liena’s form. It looked like it was made from some sort of green jade or crystal.

Qiang instantly felt Liena’s cultivation realm shooting up past his own. This secret treasure was similar to the dark armor Zhang Dong had gifted his grandfather all those years ago. It was tailored for his wife and was the only one that he had made. There just weren’t enough resources to go around, he didn’t even have his own version yet.

Soon the transformation was done and Zhang Liena bolted forward. Both of her and Qiang collided in a bout of strength. What normally would be a specialty of this red-haired brute quickly turned around. The green wind energy overwhelmed the red plasma. Huo Qiang got pushed to the side by a strong smack to the face while Liena continued forward.

But the deed was already done, the ship’s main cannon was getting activated. Her orders were ignored as the captain would follow Zhang Dong’s over Liena’s at any given moment.

“No, Stop!”

She cried out while seeing the cannon’s massive spiritual energy cannon fire away. This condensed torrent of Qi was much larger than the one the ship fired off during the battle against the Unlimited Sword Society.

This caused the ship’s main cannon to start melting, the tip of the ship even started to go up in flames as the order was given to overload the engines and fire at over 100%. Going over the limit would allow the cannon to fire off a stronger beam of energy but it would also destroy it in the process.

At this point in time, only half of Zhang Dong’s head and part of his feet were sticking out. He looked like a person that was getting entangled in some dark rubber that had tentacles. The creature was trying to devour him alive but also was having trouble maintaining its humanoid form while doing this.

He could feel the beam approaching, this was the moment to go all out. Zhang Dong gave it his all, with a burst of Qi he dipped into his reserves and the whole monster lit up along with him. He didn’t do this to free himself; at this point, it was far too late for that. No, he only used his last ounce of strength to move his hands forward.

In those hands of his, he had the corrupted cube that was being used to power this beast. The moment the beam of condensed energy was ready to hit, he opened up his palm so that it connected with the cube instead of him or the creature.

A gigantic explosion occurred instantly, everything went white. Liena that was charging forward was sent flying in the opposite direction, even with her armor on that pushed her power output by a small realm up she wasn’t able to hold on.

The ground rumbled, the people on the Argonaut were helplessly trying to control the ship. The alarms were going off everywhere and they were losing altitude. The main cannon was on fire and part of the repair crew was trying to put it off.
“Get the ship under control! What happened to the Patriarch, get the screen running!”

The Ship’s captain barked out orders while the whole room's crew was in a state of confusion. The explosion had seemed to have overloaded some of the spiritual devices. Before the Argonaut got stabilized two people rushed into the command deck.

“What is the meaning of this!”

The first person that had gone in was Zhang Liu, who was followed by Zhang Xue. Both of them looked maddened, why was obvious. They were manning the cannons not long ago but soon they found themselves looking at the main cannon firing at their Master. They weren’t able to do anything about it, so they rushed here to get some answers.

“It was the Patriarch’s orders! Now sit down you two brats, you might be the Patriarch’s disciples but here you have no authority!”

The man slammed his fist down on his chair while glaring back at the young man. Zhang Xue placed her hand on Liu’s shoulder as she tried to calm him down. Not long after the large screen flickered with light.

“We regained the signal Captain…”

They all started at the screen, there was a lot of static on it but slowly it started to clear up. When the dust had settled they were greeted with a surprising sight.

“Where are they?...”

What they saw was perplexing. There was absolutely nothing there, no monster or Zhang Dong anywhere. Instead, they saw a large hole, the strange thing about it was the shape. It was a perfect sphere. It was as if someone took a big chunk out of the ground.

On the outside, Zhang Liena and Huo Qiang were closer to this phenomenon. Both of them could feel the strong spiritual energy coming from the center of that large hole. The two huge monsters that they were fighting against weren’t looking so good either.

The moment the light subsided and the sphere hole was revealed they noticed that the two beasts started crumbling into dust. They could only explain this with the death of the main monster that Zhang Dong was fighting with. The big question was, where did he end up? Was he killed in the explosion along with it? Or did he get out in time? No one was sure but they wouldn’t be leaving this place before they found some clues.

“I… I don’t feel him anywhere…”

Zhang Liena looked around but couldn’t get a read on her husband. She quickly deactivated her emerald armor and looked at her hand. On it was a ring that her husband gave her, it was linked to another one that he had with him. The two rings were linked by a teleportation formation, if she activated it she should have been able to go to her husband.

Her hands trembled a bit but she activated it but to her dismay, nothing had happened. She tried again and again but to no avail, it just wasn’t working.

Huo Qiang dived for that large hole that was formed after the explosion. He lit up the place with his fire but he couldn’t spot anything either. There was nothing there, no monster remains, and no Zhang Dong.

“Where are you, senior brother…”

Chapter 268

“Did you find anything? Any clues?”

An angry-looking Zhang Liena was tapping her foot on the ground. There were some people standing around her, they were looking at that tapping foot. The more it moved the more the ground shook around her.

These people were members of the Argonaut 1 ship crew. The flying vessel had been put out of commission after overloading the main cannon. While repairs were underway the people that were free started searching the area where Zhang Dong had vanished in. It looked as if a chunk of earth was evaporating out of existence. The hole was perfectly circular and over a kilometer in diameter.

A day had already passed since the fight with the gigantic monster and its two companions. The moment the monster vanished along with the sect Patriarch the other two went up in smoke. There was nothing left to tell the tale, the only thing there was the giant hole in the middle of those old ruins that didn’t exist anymore.

“We have examined the explosion site… after a day of searching we couldn’t find any rem…”

The person that was answering was one of the elders that came along on this expedition. The moment he tried to mention Zhang Dong as the ‘remains’ he felt a chill run down his spine. Zhang Liena looked at him with rage-filled eyes and while exuding some killing intent.

“I mean… we couldn’t find any sign of the Patriarch being there. There are also no monster remains, it's as if they evaporated along with this fog.”

The old man sweated while shifting the conversation in a different direction. After the cannon was fired and both the monster and the Patriarch were gone, the mist cleared up.

“We have contacted our sect members that remained at the Divine Fist Sect. It seems that the fog is now gone from these lands. Even the creatures that were inhabiting the infected people seemed to have vanished, as if they were never there, to begin with…”

“Is that so… you may leave…but keep looking!”

Liena waved with her fan and the old man quickly bowed and removed himself from this location. This was just in time for Huo Qiang to appear out of the distance, he emerged from the bottom of the hole that Liena was also in close proximity. He landed next to the Matriarch, a big frown on his face along with furrowed brows could be spotted.

“This is bizarre, there are no traces left of him or the monster. It’s as if the battle never took place.”

He stood next to Liena with his arms crossed over one another while both of them looked to the large perfect sphere hole down below. There were many lights and people moving down there as everyone was ordered to search.

“He lives, I know it… A master of his caliber would leave a trace behind, something… it’s as if..”

“He was teleported away?”

Liena nodded at Qiang’s question. The two were thinking of the same thing, it looked like everything in this hole was just wished out of existence. A regular explosion would have left traces of spiritual energy behind. There would be faint signs of the creature’s and Zhang Dong’s nascent souls, those were much harder to erase. For these two people here it looked as if the whole spot that this detonation occurred was removed from this place.

“My thought exactly… the other possibility would be…”

The two looked down with their faces grim as they didn’t want the other option to be true. This being that Zhang Dong was truly dead either by this explosion or by total eradication of his very being.

“Yes… what will you do? One of us must return back to the sect, I’m sure the Divine Fist Sect will aid us in the search now but we need to keep the news from spreading…”

Huo Qiang asked while moving away, the news of their Patriarch perishing or vanishing in strange circumstances would bring them harm. They were already on a brink of war against the Limitless Sword Society. There was also the Yggdrasil Sect working in the shadows which was another problem they might have to contend with.

“I’ll remain here with some of our sect members, the ship needs to be repaired, I’ll protect it.”

“I’ll return to the sect and bring the news, we will wait for Senior Brother’s return…”

Huo Qiang nodded while moving away, before leaving he was sure to give Liena a small pat on the shoulder. She didn’t react much besides giving him a nod, without Zhang Dong around they would need to keep everything in check.

The biggest problem was the other sects that might try to use Zhang Dong’s absence to their advantage. The next one was the inner members of their own sect, with the most powerful member now gone the power dynamic would be shifting in another direction. Even though these two didn’t want it, their camps were at odds with each other. Zhang Dong was a large sturdy wall between the two which kept anything from escalating but now he was gone.

Liena didn’t look back at Qiang as he floated away. She looked down at her golden ring that she was gifted by her husband. It was one of the most treasured gifts that she received as it was the item that was proof of their betrothal. She was unsure of what had happened to her husband but she dreaded the thought of this ring becoming just a momento.

She took up flight and closed her eyes, her spiritual sense examining everything once more. Liana wasn’t willing to just give up yet, if Zhang Dong was only teleported away then he might be alive, he might also still be battling this evil creature in another part of this world. If she could just get a hint as to where he went, then maybe the masters at the sect would be able to pinpoint his location. For now, she could only continue searching and she would search for as long as she had to….

“Dong’er… where are you…”

…………………………………………

‘Some time earlier.’

Zhang Dong opened his eyes, he wasn’t sure where he was but he was in a heap of trouble. The last thing he remembered doing was positioning the corrupt cube in the line of the spiritual cannon beam. He was sure it was a direct hit but what came next was a blur.

He didn’t feel any pain or that he suffered an injury. When he opened up his eyes he found himself back at his regular size. His avatar form was canceled out but he was alive.

The odd thing was his surroundings consisted of chaotic energy. He found himself floating through some kind of tunnel, the walls of it were composed of strange Qi. He could feel that he was spinning out of control at an immense speed, where he was going and what this strange space was he had no idea.

‘Did that Cthulhu die?’

‘How long have I been in here?’

‘What is this place? How can I get back?’

He started asking himself questions, it was very hard for him to concentrate around here. He tried gathering his spiritual energy to make himself stop from spinning but to no avail. He was like a rock hurled into outer space, his destination unknown.

Zhang Dong could see strange energy torrents, lightning-like energy, and flickering of lights everywhere. This looked like one of those bad drug trips that some people had when overdosing.

The whole experience was making him sick, he was disoriented and had no idea what to do. The more he tried to activate his cultivation to free himself from this place the more his head hurt. It was as if this place wasn’t letting him use his powers at all.

He tried feeling out the Dao around this strange space but the feeling was totally different than to what he was used to. He felt like he was running on an unsupported operating system, any attempts to gather his qi were getting shut down. The only thing he could rely on now was his system, the moment he brought up the screen he saw red.

There were ‘Danger’ and ‘Error’ signs plastered all over this display. It was already hard to tell anything while spinning around but this just made things less bearable. With time and some squinting, he was finally able to see something.
‘Lost world tether? What is that anyway?’

The system was giving him some strange prompts, there were a lot of corrupt text and warning signals littering his display. Finally, he was greeted with a button that he could press, without any other options he begrudgingly pressed it. This prompted the system to give him more corrupt text but some of it was readable.

‘Missing world tether…’

‘Trying to establish a new connection… please wait…’

‘Searching...error… error…’

‘Error… missing tether…’

‘Overwriting commands… looking for a new link… please wait…’

‘Trying to establish a new world tether to user number 80082… error … subject deceased…’

‘... found a new world tether from sector 41067 setting up a new link…’

The error signals and prompts continued to appear for a while. With time something like a new world tether was found. His body started glowing immensely during this process and somehow the spinning motion started to lessen. He found himself stopping in his tracks together with a dinging sound that his system gave him.

‘… new tether added… transferring user to the new sector now...’

The moment that message appeared he felt his whole body jerking toward the energy tube wall. He was now traveling at neck-breaking speeds towards something that looked like pure energy, energy that was far above his cultivation realm. Before he could be fried by it an opening appeared. It was composed of white light and large enough for his body to go through.

The inside of this white light was another energy corridor. This one was much smaller and he couldn’t actually move at all. It felt like he was going down a constrained tube of energy what was on the other side would remain to be seen.

“GAHHHHHHhhhhhh”

With a plop he was finally out, he hit something hard and tumbled forward. The momentum carried him further and further until he hit something hard. His face hit the ground and he sprawled out like a starfish. He couldn’t hear anything or anyone as he just remained face planted on the ground.

“Ow… my head…”

He had a splitting headache, he tried activating his holy energies and they worked. A golden light surrounded his body while healing it. The wounds that he had sustained were slowly vanishing and he also felt like his energy reserves were larger than before.

‘Where am I?... did I absorb some of that cubes power, I think my cultivation is higher…’

He stood up to see where he was, what he saw was not something that he expected.

‘Huh? What is this place?’

There was nothing here besides a small wide pillar that he had hit while tumbling. The rest of this space was filled with nothing but the void. This void wasn’t pitch black, there was a stary sky above him that faintly lit everything up.

He looked around but besides the wide pillar that reached up to his belly button, there was nothing there. Before he could examine this whole place further he felt a jolt of energy. He quickly glanced to the source which was right in the middle of that pillar.

To his surprise, he saw someone appearing out of thin air right in the middle. It looked to be a person but compared to him, the person was quite tiny. It looked to be a young girl in her teens, she was so small that he would be able to squish her with one finger.

The girl looked a bit confused while looking around, with time she looked up and noticed Zhang Dong staring down at her. After opening up her mouth wide along with her eyes she dropped down to her knees and started bowing. Then she finally spoke up.

“Honorable heroic spirit, I Beatrice Hohenberg beseech thee to grand me a contract!”

Zhang Dong just blinked repeatedly while staring down, soon a sound escaped from his mouth.

“Ehhhhh???”

Chapter 269

“Lady Hohenberg?...”

“Lady Beatrice Hohenberg of Dawn Lake, are you paying attention?”

“Huh?”

A young girl jolted awake, her vision blurry. The girl was fifteen years old, she was about 170 cm in height and was noticeable by her long golden hair. This was a trait of the Hohenberg noble house that was given to its true descendants.

“I see that you are with us again, Lady Beatrice. I know today is the day that you get your summoned spirit but please at least try to pay attention.”

The blond-haired girl saw an uptight glass wearing lady looking up to her. They were in a classroom and the person that was speaking to her was one of the teachers at this noble academy. Beatrice blushed a bit while trying to cover her face with a book, the other people in this classroom started laughing and snickering.

“I apologize Miss Enora.”

The lady stuck up her nose a bit high while looking at the other people in the room. Everyone here was of the same age, it was filled with a mix of boys and girls and all of them were wearing uniforms.

Not everyone had the same uniform, some were white and some were black. There was a clear status distinction between the people here. The classroom was built up high similar to how a movie theater was made. The people in the white uniforms were sitting back up high while the ones in the black ones were down below and closer to the blackboard.

Beatrice was someone that was sitting down at the first desk so her sleeping form was hard to miss. The young girl wasn’t able to sleep the whole night as today was a very important event. An event that would decide how her life would play out in the future.

“Good, let me go through today’s ceremony. I’m sure that you are all aware of the utmost importance of this magical ritual that you will go through.”

“You have been practicing for this very occasion.”

The glasses-wearing lady teacher had a small wooden wand in her hand. She waved it around while pointing at the blackboard the moment she did the letters started shifting around. They took the form of some kind of pentagram with a lot of runes.

“You will be brought to a room with this magic circle, be sure to go through the ritual as you have been instructed and place your prepared items at each point. Don’t make any mistakes as you could offend the spirits.”

“If you fail your ceremony your next one will be held next year. I must remind you that the older the summoner is the harder it is for them to connect to the spirit realm. A person that isn’t able to make a contract with a spirit will be deemed a failure at the age of 18 and will have to find a different profession.”’

The teacher continued to talk while Beatrice’s heart skipped a beat at the mention of someone failing. This reminded her of how she wasn’t allowed to fail, if she wasn’t able to procure a strong or even a middle-class spirit contract then the future of her noble house would be put into question.

‘I can’t fail… everyone is counting on me… the main house might revoke our branch family rights if I fail too…’

She was reminded of her older brother who was that unfortunate person. He was three years older and had dropped out after failing to establish a summoner contract. She wasn’t sure what he was doing now, he had left the main house while saying that he would find his own way outside the summoner profession.

This left her as the sole heir to the whole Hohenberg of Dawn Lake family estate. A big burden was dropped on her shoulders and she wasn’t sure if she would be able to succeed. The fear of disappointing her parents had taken root deeply in her mind.

There was a certain prestige that the noble families needed to uphold. She was part of a branch family, the main noble house required them to bring forth a summoner as an heir. Without it, the main family would drop their support and they would be stripped of their noble status. Without it, they wouldn’t be able to afford their estate that was also rented out through the main noble house to them.

In reality, her branch family was nothing more than the property of the main house. They were just dogs kept on a short leash. If a dog lost its teeth and wouldn’t be able to protect its master then it didn’t have a purpose of being. Without a proper summoned spirit she wouldn’t be considered worth the investment. If that happened there would be only one option, a thing that she knew her parents would do.

‘The will probably force me to marry someone... ‘

She shivered at the thought of being forced to marry some older man and having to bear his children. That was mostly what happened to noble ladies with no status and money. They would be sent out to tie the knot with a rich enough noble that would be able to support the failing estate. Her parents would be secure but her life would be in turmoil depending on who she would be left with.

Beatrice looked at the blackboard that was constantly being changed. The teacher went through the procedures again but she had already memorized everything down to a tee. This didn’t mean that she didn’t look at the explanation again. Worrying that she might have forgotten something she continued to pay attention.

The lecture concluded soon and the students had to go outside. She remained seated at her desk with all the other black uniform students. There was a certain class rule here, unless all of the white uniforms left the classroom the lower born weren’t allowed to leave. This sometimes caused her to remain here for up to an hour if some of the noble ladies got too chatty.

She looked up to a certain person, it was a beautiful noble lady with similar blond hair to hers. The two looked a bit similar in one way or the other but this one was clearly of higher status. She was surrounded by other girls and boys in white uniforms and they were chatting away.

“What do you think Lady Isabella will receive?”

“I bet it will be a legendary spirit king like a white dragon!”

“I think a phoenix would fit Lady Isabella much better.”

“Wouldn’t a Sylph be more aligned with that?”

Beatrice listened in while a certain green-haired youth walked over towards Lady Isabella. He was quite handsome and the other people that were chatting took notice. They all moved back slightly, they were clearly making way for this individual that was of higher status than they were.

“Would that be to your liking, your Majesty?”

Isabella smiled at the new arrival and the two started talking. Beatrice turned her head away out of indignation. She knew that the man approaching was one of this country's princes while the blond girl was his fiance. She didn’t want to interact with that girl but this was something impossible as she was someone from the main family. To her, she was nothing more than a servant, a useless one if she wasn’t able to get a fitting summoned spirit.

The high nobles finally decided to move their butts. Beatrice was in Isabella’s camp so she followed behind her. She was the odd person out of this group, mostly her use was in doing troublesome errands. Today was an important day though, so even these nobles were more focused on the summoning ceremony. If they failed their prestige would be put in question even more than hers was.

There was only one chamber to perform this ritual so she needed to wait. First came the more distinguished nobles like the Prince or Isabella. She and some others would need to wait till late at night to get their turn.

She remained outside while waiting for her turn, the people that were from the more pristine noble houses were all able to receive their spirit summons. It was easier to achieve this with some additional items, some summons could be somewhat ‘bought’ over to form a contract.

The lower nobles like her didn’t have enough money for something like that. The items that a person offered during the ritual were a form of tribute to the summoned being. They were there to attract them, more than one spirit could answer your call. The strongest one would then win out over the others and be the one to form a contract.

Time continued to fly and now the youths in the black uniforms were beginning their rituals. Some of them were successful while some failed. With lacking resources, they could only count on their lackluster talent. Soon it was her turn to give it a try, the large doors to the spacious ceremony room opened up and she was left alone there.

She could see the stairs leading up to the summoning platform. The room was dimly lit but rays of light were shining on that platform. In its center was the magical circle that the teacher mentioned before. It had already been used by many other students before, some of the mana used in the ritual was still lingering.

‘Time to place the gifts…’

Beatrice took out the items that she prepared. They had some magic in them that was supposed to lure the spirits here. They were just ordinary magical items, the more costly ones were already used during her brother’s tries. Even with the higher quality ones he was unsuccessful. Even with moderately good items around there was a big chance of failure, she hoped that this wouldn’t be the case for her.

‘Please... let this work…’

She went down to her knees in the center of the magical circle. Her hands were clasped together as she went down into a kneeling position. The magical symbols started lighting up in a deep blue color as the ritual started.

“Ego antiquum spirituum te rogamus, occurre obsecro mihi testimonii…”

She started a long chant that she had remembered thoroughly. There was no stuttering and no hesitation in her voice. This was her one and only chance, failure was not an option. Rays of light shone down on her as she continued praying. Nothing seemed to be happening and she couldn’t feel the presence of any spirits. Normally they would start to appear the moment she finished the chant but even after going through with it once, there was nothing.

There was still some time left in this ritual, the magic circle was active so she started repeating the incantation over and over again. She couldn’t feel anything happening but when she opened her eyes a strange scenery filled her vision.

She wasn’t in the ritual chamber anymore, she was in some kind of dark space. When she looked up she could see a strange unfamiliar sky with many stars. Some of them were moving around, it made it look like rain, a rain of stars.

Then she looked behind her and saw him. There was a giant standing before her, his large glowing eyes focused on her small form. This giant was wearing some strange white robes and his body was covered in some kind of otherworldly golden glow. She could also see arcs of lightning bursting forward from his very being.

‘Is… that a summoned spirit… I never heard of something like this…’

She racked her brain about an answer while slightly panicking. Then it came to her, in one book there was writing that some special spirits could pull their summoners into their own realm. These spirits were considered legendary ones, the ones that had a humanoid shape were also considered even rarer.

She dropped down to her knees and started bowing the moment she realized that this spirit might have been a rare legendary one. Beatrice wasn’t sure why he chose her but this was her big chance, there was a possibility of the ritual failing if the summoned spirit didn’t agree. Thus she assumed the kneeling position and did her best to plead her case.

“Honorable heroic spirit, I Beatrice Hohenberg beseech thee to grand me a contract!”

After she spoke those words an uncomfortable silence was all that greeted her. This was only broken by a strange deep groan that this giant gave out. This only made her plant her face deeper into the ground while pleading more.

“Sorry about that little girl, could you raise your head it’s hard to talk like that…”

The next time the giant spoke up his voice was much softer sounding. She did as instructed and looked up, her body trembling slightly at the giant before her.

“I think you need to explain a few things here…”

The giant spoke up while moving his large face closer, the time for contract negotiations had begun.

Chapter 270

Zhang Dong looked down at the golden-haired girl that looked to be in the middle of her teens. At this moment in time, she was clutching her ears. After his little outburst, her ears were probably ringing. He noticed that his increased size was causing the girl harm so he tried to lower his tone.

The need to lower the amount of energy he was giving out was also a must. He started glowing less but shrinking to her size was not an option apparently. If she was just someone from a tiny race was a possibility. Zhang Dong had a hard time believing that he had turned into a giant by coming to this other world.

“Sorry about that little girl, could you raise your head it’s hard to talk like that. What did you mean by a heroic spirit when you addressed me? What is this about a contract?”

She had clearly given him a title of some sort. This was probably a clue to this predicament, if not he would need to search for answers of his own accord.

“Great Spirit…?”

The girl looked up towards him, he had leaned closer slightly so his giant face along with his glowing eyes were now looking intently at the small girl. Surprisingly the girl didn’t flinch at his colossal sight again, was it bravery or resolve?

“I thank you for answering my call, If the great spirit is willing I would be honored to form a contract…”

He could see her fidget a bit after returning the question with a statement. From the short exchange, he could somehow figure out what this was. The problem was that it didn’t really make much sense, how was he a summoned being? He came from a fantasy-like world of cultivators, so summoners and wizards wouldn’t be really shocking to him.

“You would like to form a contract with me?”

He asked out of curiosity, maybe prooding with questions someone that thought that he was some kind of summoned spirit wasn’t the greatest idea.

“I would be honored, Great spirit!

The answer didn’t give him much, though he didn’t even know how to form this ‘contract’ even if he wanted to oblige. Also signing strange binding contracts with unknown people in an unknown location would probably not be the smartest option.

The space around him felt strange. He could somehow use his cultivation and powers but the energies were different than what he was used to. He could spread his spiritual sense in all directions but he couldn’t feel any other living being here. The girl and he himself were the only two people here. Even then, she felt more like an energy construct or a soul than a real living being.

He wanted to try some other options before asking the girl for further answers. This space felt like some kind of dead-end, the only thing he wanted to do is get back to his sect. After going through all the teleportation treasures and his system options, he still couldn’t find a way out, being stuck here was a very real possibility.

The girl down below remained silent while trying not to fidget while he continued to think.

“G-great spirit? C-could we form a contract? D-didn’t you summon me here to form one, great spirit?”

Zhang Dong looked down at her, one brow raised. The girl really wanted to get this contract deal going but there wasn’t really much in it for him. He would rather decline her request but a sudden new development threw a wrench into his plan.

“Warning… world link fading… need to establish a stronger tether… warning!”

‘What is it now?’

He groaned a bit while looking at his system window that started flickering with warning signs. He could see some kind of new counter that was going down.

World synchronization rate 89%.... 88%...87%...

It started going down and continued without stopping. He started getting some kind of strange feeling in his very soul. Zhang Dong could see that he was somehow getting rejected from this world by something, slowly fading away. He looked at his hands and after the rate dropped below 70% he could see them flickering in and out of existence.

“It is advised for the user to form a contract with the summoner named Beatrice Hohenberg.”

“What the?”

He heard a voice from the side, it sounded like an old text to speech module from an old operating system. He turned to the side to see a wisp of blue light hovering there, this was the thing that just talked.

“Who are you supposed to be?”

“I am the AI companion generated to aid the User number 80082. If the user fails to form a connection with someone from sector number 41067 he will be erased from existence.”

Apparently, the system had gained some kind of sentience or it was just a more elaborate AI program. It was advising him to form a contract with this girl. It sounded that if he didn’t go through with it, it would end in death.

“Is there another way?”

He asked.

“Analysing the question... The User could absorb the person called Beatrice Hohenberg and inhabit her body forcefully. The User would be then recognized as an inhabitant of this sector.”

He looked at the young girl that was still kneeling down. She was looking at him with those big blue eyes, taking over her body was out of the question. He wasn’t an evil spirit that possessed others and he would like to keep it like that.

‘I might not have a choice…’

The counter dropped below 50% and he started to fade away. There didn’t seem to be another option but to take this girl up on the offer and form that contract. He wasn’t sure what that foretold for his future but he had to live. His family was still out there, he needed more time to figure things out. Sticking around a teenage girl for some time didn’t seem like much of a problem.

“Uh… system? AI helper? How do I form a contract with the girl?”

“... sending information to the user… please wait for the data transfer…”

He felt a familiar pain run through his head. It was reminiscent of the jolt he always got when buying techniques from the old system store. In a matter of moments, he had the information in his brain.

‘So that’s how it is… it’s not as bad as I thought it would be…’

The contract wasn’t binding him for life. Thanks to his level of power being far superior to the summoner he was the one with all the decision-making power. He would be able to break it off by his own will if he ever wanted to. If the summoner wasn’t strong enough to keep the summoned spirit at bay in some way, the spirit could leave at any moment. He could even switch hosts if he wanted to.

“Girl...Beatrice was it, I will form a contract with you.”

The girl looked up, her blue eyes went wide with surprise. He wasn’t sure what she was thinking but she looked equally confused and ecstatic. Zhang Dong had gotten the instructions on how to perform this ‘contract’ through this strange ball of light AI. He still wasn’t sure if he could trust that thing and how it even came out.

He had a suspicion that it had something to do with that other cube, he had absorbed it and might have unlocked some new functions. The contract was similar to binding two souls together. They would be connected by a sort of chain and both of them could gain benefits.

The summoned creature would be given energy from the Summoner and fed off of them. The one using the spirit would gain its aid in return, it was mostly a symbiotic relationship. Both of the parties were getting something for it.

After the contract was broken the spirit would return to the so-called spirit realm. It would get to keep any strength that it was given and with time could even evolve into a being of higher power.

Zhang Dong moved his finger out towards Beatrice. It was as large as her whole head but he needed physical contact with his summoner to perform the soul binding procedure.

“Accept it”

The girl shivered slightly while closing her eyes. He gently bumped his finger against her forehead to begin the procedure. A small fraction of his soul transformed into a golden shackle, it flew out towards the girl’s own soul and the two were connected with each other. This process was only possible if both of the parties were willing, if not the weaker one would be quite dead.

He could feel the young girl’s soul getting connected with his own. His soul arts were still lacking but with the system’s help, he was able to perform this strange ritual. The magic this world used was similar to the one of his world but the ‘wavelength’ of mana was slightly different than of Qi that he was used to.

‘That should do it…’

World synchronization rate 43%.... 44%...47%...

The synchronization rate started going up the moment the connection was finalized. Before he could ask the girl more questions he saw her vanish. She just popped like a soap bubble and only faint energy particles remained.

‘Damn, what now… and how should I call you?’

Zhang Dong frowned while looking at the small glowing blue light that was hovering over his shoulder. This thing reminded him of an annoying game element from one of the old games that he played. It was as noisy though and only spoke up when asked a question by him directly.

“This unit’s designation number is 000451200-B08…”

“... B08?... Okay, I’ll just call you Bob. So tell me, Bob, where am I and how do I get out of here?”

He took a seat on the platform the girl appeared on. It was the only thing besides the sea of stars above. While looking around he spread his senses far and wide again, this place was kind of weird. With a bit of prodding he figured something out, this place wasn’t as big as it seemed. The sky above was only an illusion, the wide dark space spread a few kilometers in each direction.

“So Bob, can you explain where I am and how do I get home? Also, what are you and this system…”

The glowing light moved towards him while changing colors. It looked like it was thinking, after a few moments its robotic voice sounded out.

“Insufficient data… must gather more nuclei”

“Nuclei?”

“A nucleus is a concentrated hub of information about a given sector….”

The machine started a long-winded explanation that pointed him back to the cubes as always.

“Wait… if I get more of those cubes, could I get back to my old world? I mean, to my previous sector?”

“Calculating…”

“With an additional nucleus, the probability of establishing a tether to users' original sector is 37%...”

“Oh? How probable is it without one?”

“0,00145%”

“Great…”

Zhang Dong looked around this closed space and was already feeling homesick. The only thing on his mind were his wife and kids. There was the problem with the crazy sect of swordmasters still to be resolved. He was worried that with him not there a war between sects could happen.

“How do I even find one of those cubes if I’m trapped in here?... huh?”

He felt something tugging at him from the inside. He focused on this strange feeling and in a moment could see something strange. He could see a strange ritual chamber through the eyes of someone else. This was clearly the girl that he made the contract with, he was now connected with her. It was a strange sensation of being in two places at once.

“I guess I will have to use this child to help me out… I need to gather more information about this world.”

He rubbed his chin while looking at the girl through her eyes. The blond was looking at a glowing mark on her right hand. He could feel his own energy signature coming off it and it was the sign of a successful summoner contract. He could feel the girl’s joy when she looked at this strange runic symbol.

‘I did it grandfather, I’m a summoner maybe with this…’

He jerked a bit after hearing the girl's voice in his head. Somehow he was able to hear her thoughts but it didn’t seem like she could hear his.

“This will take some time to get used to… think I’ll just observe her for now…”

“Bob can you tell me more about this world…”

He sat down cross-legged in this empty space, he wasn’t sure how long he would be stuck here but he would do anything in his power to return to his family and friends.

Chapter 271

Beatrice opened her eyes, it took a moment for them to focus but soon she could see the room that the summoning ritual had been performed in. She felt a bit out of it, the whole ceremony was unusual. The summoned spirits mostly appeared as phantoms in this very room and then formed the contract. Something like being sucked into a strange dimension and then looking at a titanic giant before her was unprecedented.

She wasn’t sure if it was a dream but when she looked at her right arm she noticed proof of it being true. On it she could spot a certain symbol, it looked like a magic circle with a specific rune in the middle. This was the proof of a contract being made and this magic circle would be used for channeling the summoned spirit's power.

The girl started standing up from the kneeling position that she was in. She felt a bit weakened after the ceremony and also disoriented. It felt like time was moving slower in that dimension and that here not that much had passed. Beatrice grasped her hand that had the summoner symbol on it, it was glowing for now but soon it faded away into her skin leaving it invisible to the eye.

‘I did it…’

She held that right hand close to her chest, it was as if she was giving it a big hug. Before she could finish up with her moment of delight a knock on the door was heard. She turned to the sound, knowing well that it was probably one of the teachers checking up on her. Beatrice remembered that before the spirit summoned her to his dimension she did use up a lot of time. Other people were probably still waiting outside and waiting for their turn.

“I’m coming!”

Her feet shuffled quickly towards the exit, even if the time was close to being up the teachers wouldn’t just barge in on a summoning ceremony. They probably noticed the surge of mana during the spirit binding magic. After it was finished they probably wanted her to hurry up, at least that is what she concluded.

“Lady Beatrice Hohenberg… were you successful…?”

A man in a teacher’s uniform greeted her, he had a large scroll in one hand while in the other a large feather. He was an older gentleman with a beard and a monocle decorated his face. This very monocle gave out a magical light as it was used as an identification device. The man looked at Beatrice’s right hand and could see that she did indeed have the magical insignia.

“I see, Lady Beatrice. Everyone that has passed the ceremony will have two days off. You may return to your family for the time being. I’m sure that you are aware of the next test.”

Beatrice just nodded while the old man scribbled something into that large scroll. She was aware that getting a summoned spirit was just one part of the bigger thing. New classes would be formed after each student got their summon. These summons would be tested in a couple of days and depending on how strong they were they could move up into a higher position. Getting a white student uniform was even possible if someone was able to procure an exceptional spirit.

This was also something that Beatrice had some hopes for, the huge white-haired titan that she saw looked like some kind of special heroic spirit. Why it was interested in her was unknown, the girl didn’t feel like she was exceptional. Her mana capacity was average and her grades were also somewhere in the middle of her class. Her position was also only of a branch family daughter, nothing really out of the ordinary.

“Yes I am aware, I will excuse myself. I need to go see my parents.”

The students that completed the ritual were moving through the side exit as to not bother the ones that were still not done. There was nothing here anymore but as she moved deeper into the school grounds she noticed some sad faces. Not everyone was able to pass this test and would need to try a year later.

The longer it took the harder it was to get a contract, she considered herself very fortunate to be able to do it on the first try. Even more with the gifts reserved for the spirit that were mostly of bad or mediocre quality.

It was already late and most of the campus was silent. This place was called Lestallum’s School Of The Arcane, it was further divided into smaller subsections. She was part of the summoner magic circle that was one of the more influential schools of magic in the kingdom she was in.

Beatrice, like most of the other students, lived in a dormitory. She was now heading towards it, on her mind, there was nothing else than contacting her parents. When they heard the good news they would probably praise her as their position would be secured.

She also hoped that this would stop them from trying to find her any strange marriage partners. As the only child from this family with a new summon, her worth would increase. Maybe she would be able to be the one in control of her life from now on.

While being excited she didn’t even notice that her feet were shuffling quite fast. Beatrice was now running towards her dorm room while her head filled up with various scenarios. She could already imagine being praised and showered by adoration from her parents. But the person that she wanted to impress the most wasn’t among them anymore.

“Isn’t that Lady Beatrice? Why are you in such a hurry?”

“I bet she failed and it running back to her room to cry.”

Her thought process was interrupted by familiar-sounding voices. She looked forward and saw a small group of three girls. All of them were wearing similar black school uniforms like her.

“Lady Adabelle…”

This was someone that she was familiar with. All of them belonged to Lady Isabella’s entourage along with her. Even though they all were theoretically part of the same camp it wasn’t of her choosing. It was something that was decided by their parents, the three here didn’t get along with her that well. Lady Adabelle was quite antagonistic towards her in particular.

“No, I successfully made a contract with a summoned spirit.”

Beatrice clutched her right hand tightly with her left one while slightly glaring at the three. Without Lady Isabella around there was no way of knowing what these three girls would do but she didn’t think that it would get violent.

“A failure like you managed to make a contract?”

“Who are you calling a failure?”

Beatrice glared at the girl next to Adabelle that was sniggering around. She didn’t really want to stay here and get belittled so she decided to just move past the three. Before she could move along one of the girls blocked her path.

“Why are you in such a hurry, why don’t you show us your spirit?”

“Yes, I bet she is just embarrassed that she failed. She probably doesn’t want to show us the proper respect!.”

A person that didn’t manage to summon a spirit was considered inferior to someone that did. Even if they were able to remain in the magical academy they would have to bow before the students that had a contract.

“You will see my spirit when the tests are taking place, now get out of my way!”

The three girls chuckled amongst themselves while continuing to block Beatrice’s way forward.

“How about we do it like this…”

Lady Adabelle moved her hand forward and the back of her hand gave out a greenish glow. A magical circle with a large rune in the middle of it appeared, soon before her, a large snake materialized.

“What are you doing…”

“Just a little test Lady Beatrice, just summon your spirit, otherwise…”

The large snake slithered towards her while hissing. She backed away while looking at it with wide-open eyes, clearly feeling the danger.

“Fighting is forbidden on the school grounds! You will get in trouble!”
The girls just looked at each other and continued to chuckle.

“Summoning a spirit isn’t forbidden~”

The large monstrous snake was moving towards her. Beatrice realized that the three were just trying to egg her on. They were probably trying to scare her and wouldn’t go overboard but the snake spirit was real. It was horrifyingly scary to look at and was moving towards her very slowly.

Beatrice moved her right hand forward, she didn’t have any practice but she knew the theory behind it all. Mana was guided towards her right hand, the magic circle activated quickly and started glowing in bright blue light. This caused the snake to stop in its tracks along with its summoner that was surprised that Beatrice actually had a contract mark on her hand.

“She really made a contract?”

The three girls were surprised but the astonishment on their faces quickly turned into mocking looks of pity.

“Was that it?”

“She couldn’t even summon it?”

“Maybe she doesn’t have enough mana to summon a basic spirit?”

The laughing continued while Beatrice’s face sunk. She looked at the glowing mark on her hand but couldn’t feel that special summon of her reacting in any way. While panicking the snake resumed slithering forward, it was now directly in front of her moving around her legs.

“S-stop this!”

She wiggled around in indignation while the trio laughed but unbeknownst to all of them a fifth person was among them, this being Zhang Dong in his new spirit form.

‘Well, this is an odd feeling…’

He thought to himself while floating right behind Beatrice, no one, not even his summoner, was able to see his true form. When the summoning process started Zhang Dong felt a slight tug. It was as if a small child was trying to pull him closer. The person doing the beckoning was far weaker, this meant that he as a summon didn’t really need to abide by the call.

Zhang Dong did it anyway as curiosity got the best of him. After getting some basic information about this world from the new AI companion he wanted to give this a test. Being able to move around in this new world was something he had to do. Finding more of the cubes would be his most important quest as only those would help him go back to his wife and family.

It was a strange feeling, he followed that tugging sensation and appeared in this world. He was floating right behind his summoner but invisible to her gaze. This was a strange feeling, it was as if he was floating between two worlds. When he tried using his cultivation the world resisted him but there was a small spark of power that he could use. This was coming from the summoning mark that the girl had on her right arm. Through it he felt that it was possible to do something.

The snake started to slowly entangle itself around Beatrice but suddenly it stopped. It wasn’t out of its own volition but instead, there was something else stopping it. Right below the snake's mouth a disembodied hand appeared. It was now holding the summoned creature and lifting it up into the air.

“What is that?”

Beatrice looked at the snake that was being dragged away. She was freed from the bindings before they could be sprung around her body. The hand that was holding the snake spirit looked like the one belonging to the giant that she made a contract with.

The snake was soon seen getting shocked by an electrical discharge before disappearing into thin air. This caused the girl named Adabelle to drop down to her knees. If a summoned creature was forcefully compelled to leave its owner would suffer a backlash. The other two girls looked at the disemboweled hand in fright and quickly helped Adabelle up to her feet.

“This isn’t over!”

One of them said while quickly escaping, Beatrice was surprised by the display as she had never seen those three flee so fast before.

“I see that you have peculiar friends. I guess young master types exist everywhere.”

A voice called out to her, it was coming from the floating hand. It was clearly her summoned spirit speaking. The summoning had worked and it seemed that the spirit was protecting her. Before she could ask a few questions she felt dizzy, the mana in her body was getting drained at a rapid pace and she was having trouble holding on.

“I guess we will have to build up your spirit before you can summon me… you should get some rest.”

The spirit said before the hand vanished into the void, it seemed that Zhang Dong’s new companion would need some training before he would be able to stay in this world for longer....

Chapter 272

Beatrice managed to return to the dorm room. Students with black uniforms were forced to share their space with others. The girl was feeling quite tired after the encounter with the group of girls and after using that summon for the first time her head was still hurting. She felt that she was suffering from drowsiness that came from overstraining herself and drawing out too much mana.

Her roommate looked sloppy as always. It was a short girl from the alchemist circle, due to this the room’s smell was always strange when she came back. The two did get along but the constant threat of explosions and poisonous mists spreading through this room was a thing that she had to live with.

“Hey, Beatrice.”

The girl called out while pouring some green liquid from one beaker into another.

“Hey Marry, I’ll be in my room.”

Even though they shared the same dorm room with each other they both had separate bedrooms. They were still nobles so the ones in charge decided to not make them share bunk beds or be stuck in one small room with each other.

‘Do summon spirits talk that much?’

Beatrice flopped on her bed, she didn’t even feel like taking a bath or calling her family. The summoned spirit that she made a contract with was on her mind. Normally the spirits that magicians summoned weren’t that intelligent.

They mostly followed their master's orders in a robotic way. This one on the other hand was capable of holding a conversation. This meant that that heroic spirit was really rare as only the top shelf ones were intelligent enough to converse with their contractor. There was also another problem, this spirit never told her its name. Normally during the contract, the spirits true name would come to her naturally but instead, there was some kind of conflicting information that didn’t make sense.

‘Maybe I’m not worthy enough to know its true name yet?... I don’t think I can control it well…’

She thought back to the encounter with the snake spirit. When she attempted the summoning it worked but it took some time for her spirit to react. It was as if it only acted when its summoner was in danger but didn’t follow specific instructions. It also left on its own accord when her head started to hurt, without the summoning being canceled by the summoner.

‘I’ll have to visit the library, maybe I can find an answer there…’

Beatrice gave out a yawn while curling up in bed. Due to the stressful nature of this day and lack of sleep the previous day she was really tired. Soon her eyes were closed as she floated off to dreamland. The person she was thinking about on the other hand was wide awake, looking at his ‘contractor’ from his void dimension.

‘Her body can’t take the strain of summoning me into that world, I need to do something about that…’

Zhang Dong was sitting on that column in the middle of the void. Shooting stars were flying down above him but not like he could move towards them. After further examining where he was in, there were a few conclusions that he was able to make.

For one this place was a small pocket dimension, similar to what the Dimensional Regalia was in the beginning. The whole space stretched out for about five kilometers in all directions. When he tried flying forward he ended up at this pillar again, if he tried going towards the shooting stars he would hit an invisible wall that he was unable to break.

It looked like there was nothing to work with here but that wasn't necessarily true. If he concentrated his spiritual energy, there was a way to change the scenery. He tested this out by creating a small patch of grassland, the field was small but this was just a proof of concept. It was as if this place was part of him, part of his soul, just empty and uninhabited for now.

‘I guess I could create a house for myself, for the time being, just sitting on this pillar isn’t very comfortable.’

Before he did any renovating though there were other questions that needed to be answered. Today’s strange event of him being summoned to this world that his contractor Beatrice inhabited. Another question was concerning his ability to move through that other world. It was at least possible if his summoner called him but it was temporary.

The amount of force this young girl could exert on him was minimal, he attributed that to being much stronger than his summoner. If he compared the amount of energy that this girl was able to output, it would be around the lower levels of Qi condensation. With him being now really close to the late stage of the nascent soul there was no way of her forcing him to do anything.

‘She is lucky that I’m not some kind of malicious spirit, I feel that a strong summon would be able to devour their contractor if they really wanted.’

He thought while looking to the side, there a small ball of blue light was floating about.

“Hey Bob, Is there a way of increasing the girl’s spiritual energy? Though I guess they call it mana here.”

He was still getting used to the new AI companion that he received. It came to life after the absorption of the previously corrupted cube. The trust between him and this construct wasn’t quite there yet but there was a use for it. This system wasn’t something that he could wholly trust but without it, he would have still been stuck in that strange energy tunnel.

“I have finished scanning the host named Beatrice, sending data to the user.”

Zhang Dong felt a jolt in his brain again, soon he had a detailed biometric profile of the person that he was inhabiting. The girl even had her own section in the system window from this point on. The blue AI had some other features that it could bring out, a holographic image appeared in front of him after he ordered it to produce it.

“I see… this world has a similar energy source as my spirit energy. Mana huh…”

Mana sounded like something that belonged to a high fantasy world that had elves and gnomes in it. From what he could tell it worked a bit different than Qi from his world.

A cultivator absorbed spiritual energy from the surroundings and nourished various parts of his body to get stronger. There were all kinds of cultivation techniques just as many as the stars in the sky. In the end, a cultivator ended up with an enhanced version of their body and soul. Even without specialized body refining techniques, their body would be transformed, more when a cultivator ascended into a higher realm.

In this world, on the other hand, mana wasn’t absorbed in such a way. At least these summoners or magicians didn’t strengthen their body, they went for the soul instead. Thus they only increased their casting capabilities and mana reserves while the body didn’t change much from what a regular human would be.

‘They can advance their mana faster than a cultivator would but at the same time they remain weaker…’

Zhang Dong wasn’t sure but he figured that there were spells or ways that could enhance one's body. It looked like they were more of a temporary boost than something that prevailed even if the caster was out of mana. A cultivator on the other hand would be left with a certain degree of strength even if they used up all of their Qi. Even more, if they were practicing any body refining techniques like him.

‘I don’t really need to make her body stronger but I need her to have more mana…’

He rubbed his chin while staring at the hologram of Beatrice. He could see all her vitals and statics, due to the contract the system was able to gather all of this data. With it, he was able to analyze how people in this world differed from the old one.

There was a need for more information. The cultivation that he had amassed was for spiritual energy and not mana. The ones concerning a person’s soul arts were a bit more similar to the techniques people used in this world, he still needed more information.

‘Well, she needs to wake up first…’

He looked at the empty void with the patch of green grass that he made. For the time being, he needed to renovate here....

Beatrice woke up with her face on the ground. She had somehow rolled down from her bed and landed straight on the floor. The girl’s original bed back home was much bigger and she was quite the high roller. This wasn’t anything new for the girl, she just climbed back up to her feet and moved towards the bathroom.

Her roommate was not here anymore so she would have it just to herself. The water faucet was activated with an infusion of her mana. She was now staring at the reflection in the mirror while brushing her teeth. The events from yesterday were going through her mind, the only thing indicating that it really happened was the magical tattoo on her right hand.

Thanks to passing the ritual trial she had the day off. The teachers had marked her down and the next round of tests would continue later. For now, she decided to relax in the bath after that it would be time to go home to meet up with her parents.

They were probably expecting her to come back soon, it wasn’t allowed to use magical devices to contact people outside the school. She would need to go to the appropriate place and ask for permission first. But for now, it was time to relax, though while doing this she heard a disembodied voice call out to her…

“Beatrice was it? Could you hurry it up, I would like to gather some information…”

She raised her head while looking around, confusion was clearly on her face. The voice was familiar and soon she remembered who it belonged to.

“Honorable Spirit? Is that you?”

The spirit never told her his name so she still didn’t know how to refer to him.

“Yes, it’s me.”

“How can you be here without being summoned?”

“I’m not really here, I’m just contacting you through our link. Our souls are partially connected but don’t worry, you aren’t in any danger.”

This spirit had quite the soothing manly voice, it reminded her a bit of her late grandfather. For some reason it made her trust in his words, she still needed to clear one thing up.

“Great Spirit, could you give me your name… and tell me why you have chosen me?”

The latter part was more important than the first one. She wasn’t sure why a powerful spirit like this agreed to a contract, there could be some ulterior motives.

“My name you ask? I guess I forgot to mention it...”

There was a moment of silence before the manly voice was heard again.

“Yes, I will tell you my name. The people have already forgotten me but I am the one and only Holy Lightning Emperor, Leigong!”

For some reason, there was a thunderclap sound the moment he disclosed his name. She had never heard of a being of that name before, it also sounded quite fierce. She wouldn't know that this Lightning Emperor only went with this name to sound cooler. He didn’t want to go with the usual thunder god names and chose something closer to his current cultivator disposition instead.

“Respectable Leigong, about my other question?”

“You can drop the honorifics… for the reason I chose you… well… let’s just say that you aren’t ready to know the truth yet…Now, could we go to a place with some books?”

“Books? We have a large library with magic books at his academy… but I’m supposed to go home now...would the book at my home estate be enough?”

“Think that should be fine for now...let us depart, with haste!”

Beatrice just nodded, she wasn’t sure what this spirit named Leigong wanted but he was her summoned spirit. This meant that she needed to cherish it. The books did say that the better relationship that a summoner had with their spirit the stronger it became. So the time came to return home.

Chapter 273

Zhang Dong floated around in his new void dimension. It was looking quite different now after he figured out what this place actually was.

“Should I put more trees here? What do you think, bob?”

He was now standing on a small tropical island with nothing more than the deep clear ocean surrounding him. There was a certain lack of living creatures swimming in that water and it was clear enough to see the bottom.

With a flick of his finger, a set of palm trees with coconuts sprung out from the ground. Soon a nice sturdy hammock was placed between those two and Zhang Dong hopped into it.

“You’re not much of a talker, eh?”

The glowing orb didn’t react to the question as he had hoped for. The place that he was now looking at had changed to fit his vision. He could change it by sheer will as this small pocket dimension was in fact a reflection of his soul. Its size was tied to his cultivation realm, if he managed to reach the late stage it would probably expand further outwards.

“My soul realm eh?”

He glanced to the side and could see his soul beast taking a dip in the warm ocean. He could bring in some fish but they wouldn’t really be real, nothing more than a simple construct.

This was certainly new to him. Apparently, this was something that everyone in the cultivation world and other worlds possessed. It was just hidden deep inside themselves as it was inside of their soul. He was somehow forced inside of this soul world during the whole crossing over worlds fiasco.

Zhang Dong wasn’t sure about the logistics of being here. This was all done by his system that had functions that didn’t make much sense to him. From Bob’s explanation, it seemed that his soul was stuck between this world and the passage he was in previously. This was also the only way through he could survive as somehow souls wouldn’t be erased while existing outside their own world.

He already knew that there were more worlds like the cultivation one that he came from. Something brought him thereafter he clicked that email, the biggest question was why.

By how the system reacted it seemed that people weren’t allowed to travel between these worlds. If they did they would be erased out of existence just like he almost was. The system was given to him by whoever or whatever sent him to the cultivation world but it was broken during the time he almost died.

It looked like the system thought he was dead as his designation number always came up as ‘deceased’ when he was scanned. There was someone else like him who made this possible and he had left that cube behind at the old secret ground that he had been.

This was also the reason that he was somehow trusting this blue orb thing. It was helping him for now, his secret helper was going against the being that created this whole mess. Though he wasn’t sure if that being was malicious in any way, it could have just been playing games. It was giving people strange powers from a mundane world, from a certain standpoint it could be considered a blessing.

He profited from gaining this system. After coming to the cultivation world he gained everything, good looks, status, and power. He managed to turn his lesser than stellar life into something special.

The big question was, what was this being or god expecting to achieve from giving others like him powers and sending them to strange fantasy-like worlds. Would there be some payment waiting to be paid at the end of the journey?

‘Sometimes living in a delusion is bliss…’

After giving out a sigh, his new partner in the form of a blond girl was still in the middle of traveling back home. Surprisingly the people in this world were quite advanced, they looked to be in a sort of renaissance era. Though instead of venturing towards more advanced technology they were investing their time into magic.

Mana was an abundant source of energy that was just filling up the air. It recycles itself whenever a spell is cast so it was hard for it to run out. He knew this thanks to Bob’s help as well as to Beatrice that was happy to answer any of his questions. After being able to hear the girl's thoughts he thought that he might be able to download some information directly from her brain but it wasn’t happening. He would need another way to get more information about this world and this would be done through books.

“Might as well try cultivating here…”

He jumped off his hammock and tossed the coconut that he poked a hole through. It was kind of weird but he was able to feel the sweet taste of the milky liquid inside. He could even make the coconuts taste like an energy drink if he wanted in here.

The weather was calm as he floated up while in the lotus position. Since the whole monster exterminated he wasn’t able to cultivate. He concentrated on this soul realm, there was no way of advancing his regular realm but that wasn’t true for his soul. Now while he was here the access point was at his fingertips.

The clear water that filled this ocean was quite calm and peaceful. Soon there was a change with that, the whole place started to distort and rumble. The soul beast that was Zhang Dong’s dragon looked at its master floating up and glowing in a golden color.

His body started exuding powerful bolts of lightning that shot out in all directions. They collided with something and continued to push against it. This only caused the whole place to shake even more before Zhang Dong stopped his first cultivation attempt. His face was filled with sweat and he was panting.

“It did work… at least a bit…”

The whole locked soul dimension got slightly bigger, he could feel this. He quickly measured how much his cultivation advanced and to his surprise, this form of cultivation was very beneficial. His soul had gotten slightly larger and more powerful, this also pumped up his qi reserves by a tiny amount.

“This feels like it will be better than regular cultivation… with a stronger soul all of my techniques will get more powerful, my soul-beast will also start evolving further…”

He had something to do till his new partner in crime returned home but for now, it was time to cultivate.

Beatrice was now sitting in a carriage, she had gone through all the procedures to leave the magic academy and was now heading home. The teleportation circle that she used was something that she would never get used to. It always made her sick in her stomach and she always needed some time to regain herself.

This was the only way to leave the Lestallum’s School Of The Arcane. It was a very high-class place that was hidden away from prying eyes. It was apparently located on some kind of secluded island, even the students going there weren’t sure where it was. There were various magical illusion barriers and defensive ones around it to keep unwanted visitors away.

Thus anyone that wanted to come and go would have to go through a special teleportation device. Unregistered and unknown people would be stopped before anything could happen. She had transferred close to the city that her parents lived in and where their estate was. Beatrice's full name was Beatrice Hohenberg of Dawn Lake and her family lived close to this very lake.

It had a grand name to it but in reality, there wasn’t much grand about it. Beatrice was now looking out of the carriage window and at this very lake. It had once been a focal point in the kingdom with many magical fish living in it that were a delicacy. But with bad management, the fish that had gathered were thinned out.

‘That happened about the time when grandfather was young…’

Beatrice remembered her grandfather that used to tell her stories. The lake fiasco happened before he was able to take over the estate after his own father. It was quite a hard task to manage it after they lost their main source of income. But due to being a strong summoner, he was able to get help from the main family but now he wasn’t here anymore.

Her father on the other hand couldn’t hold a candle to the late grandfather. Thus their house was in a pinch, the main family was giving them a chance if the new heir turned out to be promising. If not they would probably pull away most of the monetary help.

She was close, all the familiar-looking trees and landmarks were coming into view. The doors to her estate opened up and she was let in to her surprise there were a lot fewer servants than what she remembered.

‘Did some of them quit?’

Their reason for them moving on to a different noble house could be one, they weren’t offering much of a pay. With all the problems and even debt slowly crawling their way, there was no way of paying their servants their proper wages.

“Beatrice!”

“Mother!”

She disembarked from the carriage and was greeted by her mother. The woman was slightly taller with a different shade of hair that looked more brownish than blond. Right behind her was an older gentleman in his 40’s. His hair color was more in line with Beatrice and he had a matching mustache to boot.

“Good to see you but mother…”

The mother-daughter pair continued to hug, all until poor Beatrice felt like she was getting choked out. The older lady finally parted from her child, tears of joy clearly visible in her eyes. Before the two could converse further the father stepped forward, his greeting being far more reserved as he just nodded.

“Beatrice.”

He then glanced at his daughter’s right hand while squinting, the frown on his face changed into a smirk soon enough as he had confirmed it with his own eyes.

“Good, with this our expenses will be secured!”

“Dear…”

The mother jabbed her elbow into the father's side while glaring at him. She then moved over to her daughter and started pulling her away.

“Come, I bet you are tired after your trip, we can talk inside.”

The father gave out a weak cough after getting hit in the stomach. He had to look as his daughter got pulled away into the estate.

“Wait Beatrice… what about the summoned spirit?...”

“We will talk about that after dinner.”

The mother responded with a shout while her husband frowned some more and followed after the two.

‘The mother is fine but the father is a bit…’

Zhang Dong commented as he had broken off his cultivation session the moment the girl arrived at this estate. While the girl moved through the estate he started examining it. The whole building was quite big and expensive-looking but it also was kind of run down. It was obvious that there weren’t enough people here to take care of everything.

The food that the girl was eating at least looked good. It looked like western style cuisine with some unknown meat. From what he knew there were some magical creatures in this world but they didn’t differ much from regular farm animals. This made him wonder if these words were just being copy-pasted from some kind of preset. In his old and cultivation world, similar animals and beasts existed.

‘I should bring up the library before these two decide to go on some kind of spa trip…’

He was kind of lost in the girly talk that this mother and daughter pair was having. The father was a bit to the side and very grumpy looking. It was obvious to Zhang Dong that he only wanted to talk about the summoned spirit. He might even have to make an appearance. He was even contemplating burning off this old man’s mustache for looking this cranky...

Chapter 274

“That’s enough!”

A loud banging sound could be heard that echoed through a large dining room. Beatrice along with her mother looked to the cause of this noise. They saw a rather angry-looking man with a mustache gritting his teeth and staring at them.

“Father, is there a p-problem?”

Beatrice stuttered a bit as she was in the middle of chatting it up with her mother. The older woman had been asking her all sorts of things. Mostly concerning her health and if she was doing well at school. It didn’t seem that she cared that much about her managing to get that summoned spirit. Her father on the other hand was a lot more interested in that fact.

“Yes, we need to talk about your summoning ceremony.”

“Dear! She just returned home, gave Beatrice some time to rest.”

The older woman glared at her husband while getting between her child. She was certainly a doting parent which the fourth hidden person in the room noticed.

“Helena, we don’t have time for such things. You know the importance of having a strong spirit, if it's a low-grade one we will have to think about the arranged marriage.”

“Arranged marriage?”

Beatrice shot up from her seat the moment she heard what her parents were discussing. She could tell from how they were behaving that this ‘arranged marriage’ business was something that was previously discussed. But from her standpoint now with her summoned spirit, she would be exempt from something like that.

“Don’t worry dear... we just talked about it, we haven’t settled on a suitor yet.”

Beatrice’s mother patted her shoulder while continuing to glare at her husband that started this whole thing. Before more nonsense could be spoken another fist collided with the large dining table which caused the tableware to shake around. The two girls quieted down as the man of the house looked quite maddened by the fact that he was being ignored.

“Enough! Beatrice after you are done with eating come meet me out in the yard. We will test your summoned spirit!”

The older gentleman stood up from his seat and moved outside. The only servant that was in the room had to fix the chair that had fallen over. There were also some spilled dishes on the table where that fist landed along with a small hole in the wood.

“Don’t mind your father, he is just… worried about the estate…”

“I know mother…”

After a moment of silence, Beatrice looked to her mother with another question.

“What off older brother? Has he returned?”

The mother just shook her head.

“No, he became an adventurer before we lost contact, he could be in any of the many dungeons…”

While the two women talked Zhang Dong perked up at the mention of dungeons and adventurers. This was one of the staples of the fantasy worlds from more westernized novels. He started wondering if the adventurers had ranks ranging from F to S, maybe even SSS like in those stories that he used to read.

The two continued to talk while he listened in. The supposed brother had apparently gone on to become an adventurer. From what he had gathered there wasn’t anything like a leveling system in this world. There were classes and fantasy-like professions like mages, summoners, and magic knights. They gained their techniques and skills through hard work, there were apparently no shortcuts of killing monsters and gaining free skills and experience points.

It looked like he would soon have a chance to show himself to that noble-looking father. The man looked like he had a stick up his butt and that mustache made him look even more condescending. Though as a father he knew where the man was coming from. He was someone that had the weight of his family on his shoulders.

From what it looked like the man had some degree of magical power in him. Zhang Dong could somewhat feel the danger level by how much mana they were exuding from their souls. It wasn’t that much though, if Beatrice here was at the lower levels of Qi condensation then her father was maybe at the very early foundation establishment stage.

This was akin to an elder from a very small clan back in his world before he arrived there. Someone like that would have no way of starting a big family at most he could hope for an elder’s position in a smaller clan.

The father was also only a Baron, which painted a picture to him. There was a steady hierarchy in this world as in the one that he came from. This was almost the lowest noble title that one could achieve, the only one below it was a knight. Which would put this man as maybe the level of an outer sect elder.

Without a potential heir to the family techniques, it looked to be over. But at least it was fine for Beatrice to take over, though he wasn’t sure about that as he wasn’t planning to stick around for that long.

While he was thinking about the noble power dynamics Beatrice called out to him. She was now heading to the back of the estate. A large yard was back there where the guards and knights were training. With the loss of prestige, some of them were transferred out by the main branch noble house. What remained were mostly inexperienced youths and old knights that were past their prime.

“Um… Holy Lightning Emperor Leigong, are you there?”

He wanted to laugh at the long-winded name that he had given himself but it was better than being called Dong in this Western language-sounding world.

“Of course, where else would I be?”

“Wait… is that the sound of the ocean?”

“Ah…uh... don’t mind the small stuff, how can this Holy Lightning Emperor help you today my child?”

Zhang Dong started coughing while realizing that the ambient sound from his soul dimensions was getting through when the two were talking. With a wave of his hand the waves calmed down and his soul beast also stopped flopping around in the background. He had materialized some fish for the big guy to chase around.

“Would it be okay for me to summon you again?...”

He smiled a bit, the girl was really timid. She felt like a good kid and by being connected to her soul he knew that she had a kind heart. This made it easier for him to help her out but also made things more difficult. First, he needed to get her stronger as without her having a higher mana pool he wouldn’t be able to interact with the world for more than a few minutes.

“You can but… your body can’t handle the strain too well. I won’t be able to stay for long, you must increase your mana reserves with haste…”

This was the most important point, he needed to find a quick way to boost this girl's mana reserves. He had a connection to her soul so there were a few approaches that he could take. Before he could do that he would need to be sure that it wouldn’t harm Beatrice in the slightest. There was also the possibility of something going wrong if he didn’t have the information. For this, he needed to get to that library.

“That’s why you must visit a library and procure all the books that concern magic, anything can be of use, the more the better.”

Beatrice nodded while listening to her summoned spirit talking about the library books again. She didn’t know what he wanted with those, normally a magical being as this should know more about magic than humans. Things like human magical theory wasn’t something other races could even use. Every race and being was slightly different and thus required a totally different approach.

“Of course Honorable Holy Lightning Emperor Leigong.”

Zhang Dong gave out a chuckle while they ventured forward, this girl reminded him a few of his disciples with how much prostrating she was doing. Finally, they arrived at the supposed training area where he saw an old man in a suit of armor standing next to Beatrice’s father.

“I am here, father.”

Beatrice curtsied slightly while holding her long skirt.

“Good. How is that spirit of yours? Can you show it to me?”

The girl evades her father’s gaze while holding her right hand on which her summoner insignia was. Her father had a similar one as she had which was also the proof of being the current family head.

“Ah yes… I can show him to you…”

“Great, before that. Sir Heinrich.”

The old man that was on the side moved forward. He placed himself in front of the young girl with about twenty meters of space between them. Soon the sound of a sword getting unsheathed could be heard.

“Heinrich will test your summoned spirit, you should have learned how to summon it by now, right?”

Beatrice nodded while still clutching her hand together. She had summoned this spirit once before but it was a peculiar one. For one he felt like someone from the older generation that wasn’t taking things very seriously.

Her hand was stretched towards the man in front of her. She infused her mana into it and made the summoner sign glow in a bluish light. The light flickered in a golden hue for a fraction of a second but just like last time, nothing appeared.

“Beatrice? What happened?”

The father looked from the side a bit surprised that there was no spirit there to fight the knight.

“Ah… the spirit is here… he is there father…”

Beatrice pointed toward a barrel in which some old wooden practice swords were stored in. It was close to where they all were standing and blocked part of the view.

“There? But I can’t see anyt… what is that?”

The blond mustache-wearing man leaned forward as he witnessed the form of his daughter’s summoned spirit.

“A boot?...”

It looked to be a white boot that didn’t go further past than the ankle. It looked like it would connect to a leg but it was cut off. The strange summoned spirit started floating around while getting close to the knight.

“Um Father… the honorable spirit says that we can start the test…”

“The spirit told you that?”

The man’s eyes bulged out slightly as the bodiless foot floated towards his armored knight. The old man in the suit of armor was looking at this strange phenomenon as well. The man looked to the baron as he didn’t know what to do.

“Fine… go ahead, Heinrich.”

The old knight looked at the wobbly foot moving his way, it wouldn’t be hard to slice something like that in half. The man felt anger that he was forced to be part of a silly test like this. He was a sworn knight though and had to follow orders.

His sword was raised and its edge was encased in flaming energy. The sooner he took care of this, the sooner he would be able to resume the training of the other guards.

This strange boot reacted to the charge as it flew towards the armored knight. It changed its trajectory and it was now looking like a flying kick was coming towards Heinrich. He reacted by swinging his magic-infused sword at the disembodied body part, soon the two collided with each other.

What was supposed to be an easy victory for the experienced knight captain, turned to shock. Instead of the foot getting cut in two pieces it smashed the knight's sword into tiny pieces. It flew even further and collided with Heinrich’s metal armor sending the experienced warrior tumbling back.

“Impossible!”

Beatrice’s father’s jaw dropped as he looked at the floating foot that soon vanished into tiny mana particles. The armored knight was out cold with a footprint on his armor. It had a strange symbol in the middle that looked like a checkmark. The old man wouldn’t be waking up for a while after this...

Chapter 275

Beatrice was concerned at first after seeing the foot appearing out of the blue. The floating hand made more sense as it could at least grab and punch things. This thing on the other hand was just a floating boot.

To her surprise, the floating body part that was wearing some strange otherworldly boots flew towards the old knight. She knew the old man as a respectful knight that was quite strong, not much weaker than her own father. He would be able to single-handedly take on a monster-infested lair and come out on top.

It was one thing going against Adabelle with her simple snake spirit. The young girl was untested in battle and didn’t know how to use her summon properly. Sir Heinrich on the other hand was a trained knight. He was past his prime but he was still more than able.

This same sessioned knight was now slumped forward while leaning up against a wall. His arms were limp and he was foaming at his mouth.

“Oh sorry about that… I thought he would be able to handle it… I guess this world's strength standards are a bit lower than I anticipated, he was at most at a half step foundation establishment realm...”

She heard her summoned spirit rumble around in her head. Apparently, he was even going easy on Heinrich, she wasn’t sure what that realm was but it looked to be some power measuring system that this spirit of hers had.

“Is he alright? If you have enough mana I could heal him for you.”

“Honorable spirit can use holy magic?”

Beatrice perked up at this revelation. Healing was a secret art that was mostly only possible by devout priests that channeled godly energies. It wasn’t something a regular mage could learn but maybe her spirit knew the lesser nature elemental regenerative arts of healing. Those could be performed by other magicians and shamans but weren’t as potent as the miracles that a priest could perform.

“Yes… I think you don’t really need to summon me for that… could you just walk over towards him and follow my instructions…”

She nodded and quickly moved over to the downed man whose body was twitching around. The sword that he was using had shattered into many tiny pieces as well.

“Beatrice, what are you doing?”

Her father called out from the side as he finally got over the shock of seeing his best knight go down in one hit. He was about to call out to some servants to come help but soon his attention was drawn back to his daughter that placed her hand on the knight’s chest.

The summoning crest on her right hand lit up in a blue light that quickly changed its coloring to a more golden shine. He was an experienced summoner himself and someone that had worked with priests before so he could identify this mana pattern as holy healing light. This gentle light washed over Sir Heinrich that started looking better in a matter of seconds, waking up in a flash.

Soon after performing the healing feat, Beatrice started panting out loudly. She felt a familiar headache which signaled that she was running low on mana. The man was healed but the footprint was still denting his steel armor.

“What kind of spirit did you make a contract with… you need to explain everything to me.”

Beatrice’s father ran up to lend his daughter a shoulder to lean on. Soon the two returned to the house and she was able to rest on a couch. Her mother was already next to her with some mana potions to relieve the head pain. She was quick to explain the situation of meeting the spirit, from how she was pulled into a strange space to his size and to how he was listening to everything they were talking.

“Holy Lightning Emperor Leigong?”

Her father rubbed his chin while trying to remember if there was someone like that named in the past.

“It’s not odd for certain powerful individuals with strong mana to be reborn as heroic spirits…I will have to do more research on that name…”

The man looked at his daughter and placed his hand on her shoulder.

“Listen well Beatrice, I know that you are happy about gaining such a spirit but this could bring unforeseen consequences.”

Beatrice looked up to her father and then to her mother not really sure what he meant by that.

“Consequences? Won’t the estate be secured when the main house from Dragonridge hears about this?”

The father furrowed his brows while looking at the mother and soon he spoke out while explaining everything to her.

“Beatrice, you probably don’t realize why the main house has stayed in power for all of those years.”

“Dear?”

The mother moved in from the side as if trying to stop him from saying more but the man raised his hand to stop her.

“She is a summoner now, one with a powerful spirit dwelling in her. She deserves to know the truth.”

“The truth? The truth about what?”

Beatrice asked while looking between her parents, not really sure where this was going. She came here hoping to only get good news but things didn’t seem to be heading in that direction.

“It’s about your grandfather, his death wasn’t an accident...”

“What?”

She jumped up from her seat, her eyes going wide at the revelation, from where the conversation was going there was only one possibility.

“Did the main house have anything to do with it?”

After a moment of silence, her father nodded.

“Yes,he had gotten problematic to handle for the main house. He was very talented… too talented for his own good…”

Her father disclosed what he knew. Her grandfather was considered to be a powerful summoner, he had managed to nourish his spirit into a dragon after many years of progress. Thus the main house which had the name Hohenberg of Dragonridge, started seeing him as a threat.

Zhang Dong listened in from the side, this whole thing sounded similar to how things were run in his own world. It was a similar situation to how he got too powerful in the Dark Palm Sect’s eyes. The ones in power couldn’t handle the thought of an upstart sect or clan sprouting in their territory.

It was a normal way of living in worlds ruled by the mighty. He wasn’t sure if soul binding magic existed in this world. This side family didn’t have anything like that attached to them, so maybe that was the reason why this grandfather wasn’t turned into a slave. They had to murder him to keep the status quo.

The story wrapped up with the father mentioning that he didn’t know how they did it. His father’s body was sent back to the main house and it was reported that he died fighting some monsters.

“Yes I remember that day…”

Beatrice moved her head down, now she realized why that story sounded strange. Her grandfather was far too mighty to be slain by normal monsters. She was young then as this had happened over five years ago. Since then the estate had been deteriorating slowly.

“But father, we must avenge grandfather! How can we sit still when something like this happens, we must report it to the other ducal houses!”

Beatrice started screaming out in rage. Something like this was unheard of, they were all nobles from the same kingdom. How could a ducal house kill someone from their branch family because they feared his might?

“We will do no such thing, you will do no such thing either! None of this can leave this room!”

“But father!”

Beatrice protested by her mother and started pulling her to the side by the arm.

“Listen to your father, the other ducal houses won’t help us. This is just how things work between the nobles dear…”

“But mother… What about grandfather’s death? How can we leave the perpetrators at large?”

The mother looked into her daughter’s eyes and Beatrice knew well why there would be no repercussions for those murderers. There was no way for them that were at the lower end of the totem pole to go against a Duke household that was the main Hohenberg line.

“You are a smart child, I think you understand the gravity of this situation. Even though that spirit of yours is strong you can’t show off its power… At least not till you are stronger…”

Zhang Dong continued to listen in, he wasn’t sure what he had gotten himself into here. He could somewhat feel Beatrice’s indignation at the fact that her grandfather perished like that. Even though she was nodding and now promising that she would be careful, but on the inside, she was like a powder keg.

The biggest problem was that he was stuck with her and he would probably be the person having to go against any enemies if this young girl decided to act. He would need to keep her out of trouble as letting a child die under his watch would be unheard off.

“Honorable Spirit…”

‘Ah, here it comes…’

The conversation between the family members had now ended. Beatrice had left the room as she wanted to digest this information and her parents let her have some space. Zhang Dong had a suspicion about what she wanted to ask him. Due to this, he was the first one to speak up.

“Don’t get blinded by rage child, that path leads only towards destruction.”

“But…”

“That doesn’t mean that you can’t get stronger. I can help you with that…”

Zhang Dong didn’t want to use a teenager bent on revenge for his own gains but he also needed to get this girl’s mana reserves up. She had to get stronger for him to be able to act in this world. If on the way there he would have to take care of corrupt nobles, then so be it.

“You can, great spirit?”

“Yes, but you will have to listen to my instructions. First, we have to get to that library…”

“Ah, yes.”

Beatrice replied as she had almost forgotten about that promise she made. The library that her family had wasn’t anything great but there were some books about magical theory here. Almost all noble houses that were related to magic had them.

“What do you wish to do here, great spirit?”

She pushed the large door open and was greeted by a dusty library. The lack of servants was showing.

“Can you go pick up one of the books?”

“Pick it up?”

Beatrice moved forward on a bookshelf and picked up one of the manuals for beginners. It was one that she had studied when she was a child.

“Like this?”

“Yes, just like that… now… do it with all the books in the library…”

Zhang Dong had absorbed the information the moment the girl touched the book. It was now in his system library along with all of his other knowledge. Now he just needed to get the girl to touch all the other books before he could start her training program. With more knowledge about this world's magical system, he was going to produce a fitting training regime and manual for his new host.

Chapter 276

“T-that’s the last one, great spirit…”

Beatrice called out while slumping against a tall bookshelf. She was stuck running through her noble house’s library touching every single book that was here. Even if it was a cookbook or one with poems, her summoned spirit requested her to give all the books a nudge.

The girl wasn’t sure what this was all about by the spirit gave her a demand and as his summoner, she had to take care of it. She knew that a spirit could hold a grudge if their summoners didn’t treat it properly, even more, if they were a highly intelligent one that could even speak directly to her.

“Was that it?... I guess this will do for now, when we return to that magic academy of yours we will have to go visit the library there.”

“The a-academy library?”

Beatrice went pale in the face, the library at the academy was many times larger than this. It would probably take her ten times longer to touch every book there. Those would also only be the books that she was allowed to browse as a lower tier student. If the gates to the better books were opened this time would be doubled.

“Sure, the more information I get the faster I can increase your mana capacity.”

“My mana capacity?”

“Oh, I guess I haven’t spoken to you about that part. How should I say this without hurting your feelings Beatrice… you’re kind of… behind your peers when it comes to many things, mana included…”

Beatrice flopped her head down in shame. She knew this fact well, her talent was mediocre at best. The three girls that were egging her on after the summoning ritual were all better than her when it came to mana and spells.

Even though she was a summoner there were certain low level spells that every mage type could learn. She had trouble maintaining those simple spells and she trailed behind most of the other students. The only way that she was able to make up for it was through slightly better grades that came at the expense of hard studying.

“Your mana capacity is too minuscule to summon me fully into this world, that is why at most I am able to materialize my body parts. Even then you probably noticed the headaches?”

Beatrice nodded with indignation, she had a suspicion that it was her fault that the spirit couldn’t fully appear. Though this brought another thing to light, just how strong was this heroic spirit? Even though her mana capabilities trailed behind most of her peers, it wasn’t by such a staggering amount. Adabelle was able to control her snake without much trouble, she felt like that would also be something that she could do.

“Yes… I’ll try to increase my mana, I’m sorry…”

“Don’t worry, I’ll take care of that. With these basic spellbooks I should be able to convert some of my own techniques… but you might have to prepare for some harsh training if you want to get stronger…”

When the word ‘stronger’ was uttered Beatrice thought back to what she and her parents discussed. Her grandfather had been disposed of by the main family that they were serving. Even if she didn’t want to admit it, in her heart there was only rage and vengeance.

“Don’t even think about that, at least not yet.”

“Great spirit?”

“We are connected, I know what you want but you won’t find any answers at the end of that road.”

“But…”

“Well, for now, go back to your family and rest. I have some work to do…”

The connection between the two was cut as if Zhang Dong turned off a phone. It seemed like she wouldn’t really be able to control this heroic spirit at least not till her mana somewhat matched his.

In his soul dimension, Zhang Dong looked at a tired Beatrice leaving the library. While she was touching the books he was able to absorb all the knowledge into his system. This knowledge was now part of his and thanks to it he already knew the situation in this world.

It wasn’t that different from where he came from, just as he thought before the noble houses here were analogs to clans in his own. The biggest difference was the size which was much lower, this world's planet was also much smaller than the immortal type world that he came from. It was about double the size of his old earth but compared to the giant landmass he traveled daily as a nascent soul master this place was quite tiny.

“I guess when the gaps in individual strength get large enough and a single person can topple governments by themselves, worlds like these are the results…”

He mumbled to himself while waving his finger around. As he did the scenery shifted to something more familiar, his old crafting abode. Instead of him now teleporting into it through the system it was created directly in this soul dimension. He needed the facilities here to combine a few things together, mainly some cultivation manuals with the magic manuals from this world.

“They are quite similar to the ones I’ve studied but it will be safer to do this through the system.”

Through the years he had become quite an expert but this didn’t mean that he was all-knowing. He had a general idea on how to boost Beatrice’s mana reserves through some soul arts but it was better to spend some points first. He had gained quite a bit of them after absorbing that corrupt cube.

Zhang Dong arrived at a familiar-looking desk with a lot of drawers. This was the device that he used to upgrade almost all of his and his sect’s techniques. With a little wave of his hand, he produced a book of magic. This one had the main mana technique that Beatrice’s branch family was using.

It didn’t seem like much out of the ordinary, he even tried emulating some of the spells that this place had to offer. With his massive amounts of spiritual energy, it wasn’t that hard to convert it into mana. It only required him to change a couple of things while using his soul as a medium to cast spells.

At least in theory as he was still doing this in his own soul dimension. He would also have to get the hang of this as he left, like utilizing his old techniques would be hard to reproduce in this world. Certain fundamental laws were different here but most of them were quite similar.

“I guess I’ll give her the old heavenly lightning treatment… it is my best technique…also there is also that one way… think it should speed things up a bit...”

He popped in the magical book into the shelf to put it up as the base while the other one had his Heavenly Lightning cultivation manual. He could add more points to get most out of it, things were dire so he decided to go all out. This wasn’t the time to be a miser, the faster the girl leveled up the sooner he would be able to go out into this world.

He still had no idea where one of those cubes could be at. Cultivators were people that lived long lives so he wasn’t panicking just yet. Before anything would be decided months or years could pass by. Everything depended on how well the Saint Fist Sect could hide the fact that they weren’t weakened.

Even then, the people from his own sect might not help them out if the Yggdrasil Sect came knocking. Which would give his family and friends more time, they were already quite strong without him. Qiang and Liena could somewhat contend with late stage cultivators and they would only get stronger.

“They will be fine… unless they offend someone…”

He shook his head while trying to bury his worries inside. The faster he got out of here, the better, it was time to see if he could get this girl up into fighting condition. If she was able to summon him fully, it would already be a victory in his eyes.

….............

Beatrice closed her eyes as she curled up in her large bed. The day went by quickly, after getting the library part done she took a long bath and then went straight to bed. She was tired but also couldn’t really sleep due to the big revelation today. The death of her grandfather was still on her mind.

Her parents weren’t going into much detail about it, not saying more than that the main family was responsible. They didn’t mention anyone in particular so she didn’t have a target to focus her anger on. The only thing on her mind now was to get stronger.

After rolling around in her bed for an hour her body finally gave out and she fell asleep. But what should have been a fast awakening in the morning turned into a strange dream event.

She found herself on some kind of tropical island with strange trees. Beatrice looked around and could see clear water everywhere. This all felt so real but something was off about it.

“Is this a dream… I never had a lucid dream like this before…”

This looked like a dream, the biggest telltale sign was the giant golden dragon in the distance. She could see it shaking its ass around like a cat before pouncing on some kind of strange monster fish.

“I’ve seen that you made it, we can begin the special training!”

Beatrice turned around to see a familiar figure. It was her summoned spirit but this time around he was regular sized. This didn’t mean that he wasn’t imposing, he was still a large man while she was a smaller girl.

“Training… how did …”

“Ah yes, you’re probably wondering how I brought you here? Well, let’s just say that this Leigong has his ways.”

He started talking while getting closer, she wasn’t sure about this spirit's motives but he didn’t seem like a bad person to her. He was also the only spirit that answered her call which made her see him in quite the good light.

“I’m not sure if you know this, but the mana techniques that you are using are just a form of soul manipulation… but the ones you are using are just imitating the real thing, quite ineffectively.”

Beatrice perked up as he continued to speak. This heroic spirit seemed quite wise so if he was sharing some of his knowledge with her, she would listen. She wasn’t really sure what he meant by soul manipulation.

Casting spells consisted mostly of drawing mana from the air and condensing it into magic circles. With the correct sequence of the circles, a spell would be produced. She never heard anything about the relation between magic and the soul so this was quite the interesting reveal.

“Well, it’s better to just show you… this isn’t your true body, I just pulled a shard of your true soul here… In theory, you should be fine…”

“Fine with what?”

She asked while Leigong her spirit moved over and gave her forehead a poke. The moment he did a jolt of electricity followed along with a torrent of information. This caused her pain followed by her face planting into the warm sand in front of her.

“Well… maybe not… but you are still here… so it was a success!”

The heroic spirit laughed while Beatrice was squirming on the beach sand while holding her head.

“Let us begin the training!”

Chapter 277

“L-like this, great spirit?”

A confused Beatrice asked while juggling two balls. These balls were created by her own mana after a short explanation from her summoned spirit.

“Yes like that, concentrate and visualize. The more of them you can juggle the more your spirit will increase… also don’t just stand there in one spot…”

Zhang Dong snapped his fingers and a wolf appeared out of nowhere. The creature howled before running towards Beatrice. It looked quite ferocious with its teeth bared at her. The way it was charging also looked very menacing which caused the poor girl to ask for help.

“G-great spirit?”

The girl tumbled forward and the balls that she was somehow managing to juggle hit the ground. The wolf jumped to bite her but before connecting with her it turned into cold water that splashed in her face.

“Concentrate Beatrice, mana is just the expression of your mind and your soul. If you can’t manage such an easy task how can you think about advancing as a summoner. Now do five laps around the island with at least two balls.”

The girl was drenched in water but she stood up. The moment Zhang Dong mentioned her advancing as a summoner her eyes showed fire in them. He watched as the girl took off running while trying to balance the items that she produced from her own mana. This whole thing might have looked silly from the outside but the better she got at it, the more mana she would have in her when she woke up in the morning.

‘This might take a while… but even without this training her soul is expanding.’

He noticed that the girl’s soul was slowly adapting to his own. It was slowly absorbing his high grade energies and getting stronger. Even without the training, her mana pool would keep increasing. This could be increased even further by some training though. By pulling the sleeping girl’s soul shard into his own soul world he could hasten the process.

This was already the second night that she was going through this drill. First, he needed her to visualize her soul into items. Only after being able to create one ball would the training continue. When this item was created it had to be maintained by concentrating. Thus by forcing her to move around the difficulty was increased, if she managed to get through this training her mana reserves would increase exponentially.

‘Think it’s time to go back to that school… this whole thing feels like one of those games for girls… there might be an otherworlder like me somewhere here…’

After thinking it through Zhang Dong came to the conclusion that this world was the same from which he came from. It was very possible for people from his original world to be here or them having been there. If such a person existed here he would need to ask them about the place they were summoned to. There he would probably find one of the cubes that was used as a teleportation beacon.

‘I should probably go through some of the myths… maybe there were some old summoned heroes or powerful kings. Any of them could have come from another world like me…’

There wasn’t much for him to do here. During the day he cultivated in his soul realm while during the night he helped his summoner progress. He also thought about certain ways of prolonging his stay in the outer world. For this, he told Beatrice to go to the yard and summon him when she woke up in the morning.

“I guess this is a tad better…”

Zhang Dong rubbed his chin while floating around, his upper body was fully visible but his legs didn’t make it through to the outside world. He had dropped his cultivation level as much as he could which lowered the requirements for him to be summoned dramatically. The most he could lower himself to was the early stage of foundation establishment, even his body refining had to deteriorate for this.

“Continue with your training, remember to perform the breathing exercises that I taught you!”

Beatrice nodded while Zhang Dong’s figure turned into many tiny blue particles. She was surprised by the progress she made. Even after only two days, she had already doubled her mana reserves and this wasn’t the end. The strange tasks that her summoned spirit was making her perform seemed odd at first but they were working. She had already caught up to some of the summoners that were miles ahead of her not too long ago.

Soon the academy sent a message for her to return. The date of the next tests had been decided on and every young student that passed the ritual was to participate. She was now standing at the gate to the estate with everything already in the carriage. Her parents were here and she was just getting a big hug from her overprotective mother.

“Take care dear.”

“Yes and remember Beatrice, try not to stand out…”

She looked to her father who had a stern expression on his face. Beatrice knew that things could get troublesome if that main house realized that her summon was special. They had already done something to her grandfather, it was possible that they would see her as a threat. If she could keep a low profile still remained to be seen.

The doors closed behind the carriage and she was off. The next stop would be the teleportation gate through which she would be transported back into the academy.

“Your father is right, it would be best for you not to stand out before your abilities advance further.”

Zhang Dong spoke out while taking a small break from his own cultivation.
“When your mana advances I’ll be able to teach you some spells…”

He commented as there was a certain special feature that summoners had with their spirits. Depending on the elemental affinity of that spirit the summoner would be able to learn spells from that school faster. This didn’t stop with only elemental spells, if a spirit was good at illusion magic then the caster would also progress fast in that school of magic.

The two chatted for a bit before each one resumed their own training. Beatrice was taught a breathing method that was akin to cultivation but especially transformed to fit this magical world. With it, her mana reserves could be boosted even further.

Soon Zhang Dong and his summoner were greeted by a wide-open room. This was the teleportation chamber of the magical academy and she wasn’t the only person that was nowhere. The students were required to go through the teleportation circle at the same time to save up on mana. Thus all of them ended up in this chamber, this meant that she would be bumping into the old bully trio again.

‘Better not to start any fights, keep a low profile, and bring me to your library.’

Zhang Dong spoke to Beatrice who was eyeballing Adabelle and her three friends. He could see the three bullies flinching a bit when they saw the blonde girl. It was clear that his previous appearance and him choking up that ‘danger noodle’ was still on their minds.

For now, he needed more information. The books back at Beatrice’s estate were good to show him the basics but the good stuff was probably hidden away in this school's library.

‘There shouldn’t be much trouble for the time being…’

Zhang Dong relaxed in his own soul dimension while sometimes glancing through Beatrice’s eyes. She was still a kid and was around other kids so he didn’t think that it should go out of hand. The small bullying incident was there but it was quickly resolved. In the future, he could just show himself as a floating hand to save on mana. The other summons didn’t seem to be too powerful, the snake he faced was at the qi condensation level.

It did seem that way as everyone got out of this large chamber without getting into fights. The further aptitude tests would be taking place on the next day so Beatrice was tasked with going into the library. She was still only seen as the lowest of low students so the books that she had access to weren’t that great.

She had to forget about her pride as she started going around and poking each book in the vicinity.

‘Great spirit, you never told me… but why do you wish me to touch these books?’

Finally, the question was raised. He expected the girl to get curious, he probably would too. For once he decided to tell her a bit of the truth as revealing this would probably show that he trusted her.

‘By touching the books I am able to absorb their knowledge.’

She stopped in her tracks and the revelation.

‘Just by touching them? How is that possible.’

This was an ability gained through the system so it did seem quite astonishing. Being able to absorb knowledge just by touching a book was probably every bookworm’s wet dream.

‘We spirits have our ways… I could even share the knowledge with you if you wish…’

Beatrice perked up at the offer.

‘Just go to a book that you wish to learn and touch it but you might want to choose a thin one at first.’

The girl went over to one bookshelf and picked out a book about another country's history. It was something that she was interested in but never had time for it due to all the magical theory classes that needed to be taken.

‘It’s a bit on the thicker side but it will do… this is going to sting a little bit…’

He performed his usual technique to share knowledge. The moment he did Beatrice felt a stinging sensation in her brain. It was painful enough for her to drop the book she was holding to the ground. This was a similar experience to the time he infused her with the previously made mana cultivation technique.

‘Even shortcuts have a price, Beatrice.’

Zhang Dong chuckled while the young summoner got over her headache. It didn’t take long but he could feel the girl’s bewilderment at receiving the information.

‘It worked?...’

‘Of course, it worked but this isn’t something you should abuse.’

People in this world were different, their bodies didn’t evolve as much as cultivators. A regular person like her wouldn’t be able to absorb thousands or million of books like he was able to. An attempt at something like that could cause long-lasting damage, memory loss or brain damage.

‘You can pick five books, for now, I’ll help you absorb the knowledge but only after we are done with this library.’

Beatrice looked at the building with many shelves with all sorts of books. One tiny spell could have a giant tome written about it and there were many theories as well. Even touching them with her fingertip could take a while.

‘Don’t ignore history books and others, even those could have some hidden knowledge left behind by an author.’

Zhang Dong knew that sometimes masters of the craft left parts of their knowledge hidden in riddles. With the help of his system, he would probably be able to find hidden treasures like that.

‘Now get to work, we need to finish this before your aptitude test!’

‘Yes, great spirit…’

Beatrice replied in a weak voice before moving forward, it was time to touch some books...